[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-01 23:07:04
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 日常 第16話
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,45,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.02,0:00:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！ 那么今天就这样结束吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.94,0:00:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为白天变得比较短了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.86,0:00:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在天黑之前回到家里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.32,0:00:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 玩去吧 玩去吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.28,0:00:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}玩什么去啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.62,0:00:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.62,0:00:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.83,0:00:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.42,0:00:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站前的那个 要去尝尝么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.83,0:00:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.75,0:00:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.96,0:00:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.21,0:00:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 美绪也一起去嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.38,0:00:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 已经回去了么…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.89,0:00:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 名乃…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.51,0:00:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.48,0:00:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一声没吭就走了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.31,0:00:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算不算是对相生同学做了件坏事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.69,0:00:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能再稍微 像普通的女生一样打招呼就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.16,0:00:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我… 我… 我叫东云名乃！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.07,0:01:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.74,0:01:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个听我说啊 那个… 这个发条啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.04,0:01:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为家附近的咖啡店改装了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.51,0:02:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以进去看了看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.22,0:02:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.35,0:03:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您点些什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.23,0:03:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来杯浓缩咖啡…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.53,0:03:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,T的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.49,0:03:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.62,0:03:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高杯的浓缩咖啡 可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.62,0:03:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}トール{\r\fs36}：Tall，指高杯，与{\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}透（とおる）{\r\fs36}同音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.41,0:03:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,透… 透明！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.87,0:03:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,透明？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.83,0:03:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,T是指… 透明么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.17,0:03:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 要喝T的浓缩咖啡吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.21,0:03:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.05,0:03:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 T的浓缩咖啡…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.97,0:03:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SMALL的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.05,0:03:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矮杯的浓缩咖啡 可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.05,0:03:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}ショート：{\r\fs36} Short，指矮杯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.06,0:03:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.23,0:03:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SMALL的短杯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.61,0:03:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.15,0:03:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好… 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.82,0:03:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是 浓缩咖啡…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.74,0:04:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.53,0:04:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有加热或者加冰的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.20,0:04:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就加热的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.62,0:04:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.75,0:04:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果点热的的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.79,0:04:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SIZE得是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.67,0:04:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SOLO或…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.92,0:04:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.92,0:04:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}DOPPIO：意大利语，相当于DOUBLE
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.89,0:04:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DO… DOPPIO！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.18,0:04:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.10,0:04:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO是什… 什… 么啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.77,0:04:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO x 3
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.39,0:04:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO是什么… 什么东西啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.23,0:04:31.90,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\fn黑体\b1\pos(662,475)\c&H8DAFED&}本日的咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.98,0:04:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.94,0:04:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啦 刚才忘啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.44,0:04:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想点这个“本日的咖啡”
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.28,0:04:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.58,0:04:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本日是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.58,0:04:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浓缩咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.29,0:04:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.21,0:04:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.75,0:04:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.79,0:04:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有SOLO和…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.01,0:05:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO的 请问您要哪种
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.93,0:05:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.84,0:05:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.97,0:05:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOPPIO的 请问您要哪种
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.98,0:05:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.69,0:05:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是啊～…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.36,0:05:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.28,0:05:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.32,0:05:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于那个 就请你适当看着办吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.58,0:05:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.17,0:05:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您久等啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.47,0:05:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您点的浓缩咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.82,0:05:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好小…！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.62,0:06:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级… 苦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.21,0:06:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢惠顾！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.43,0:06:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.81,0:06:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后还是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.22,0:06:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买自动售货机的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.23,0:06:43.99,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\frz270\shad2\pos(1180,360)\4c&HCED7D9&}CATCH BALL
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.98,0:06:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孙子小美过生日的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.36,0:06:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给他买了个手套作为礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.74,0:06:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷 我要扔了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.49,0:06:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶哦诶 小美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.91,0:06:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离那么远的话是够不到的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.83,0:06:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他竟然这么高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.96,0:06:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然孙子真是好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.92,0:06:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.38,0:06:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.92,0:07:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情地扔过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.05,0:07:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.76,0:07:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也想稍微展示一下帅气的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.18,0:07:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下坠球…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.52,0:07:16.19,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\frz270\bord5\blur8\pos(1220,360)}TICOMART
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.18,0:07:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H3D3E3C&\frz6.951\pos(632,154)}闷绝！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.18,0:07:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\shad0\bord0\c&H3D3E3C&\frz6.951\pos(286,383)}滚烫滚烫的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.18,0:07:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\shad0\bord0\c&H3D3E3C&\frz6.951\pos(308,498)}大厨的心血来潮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.18,0:07:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\shad0\bord0\c&H3D3E3C&\pos(554,652)}鸡肉棒——50元
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.65,0:07:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.73,0:07:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.52,0:07:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我来一根这个“闷绝滚烫滚烫大厨的心血来潮鸡肉棒”
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.11,0:07:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.40,0:07:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请您饶了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.68,0:07:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 小治郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.64,0:07:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.05,0:07:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要赶快 受理快要结…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.63,0:07:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美～绪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.30,0:07:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小 小佑…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.64,0:07:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.60,0:07:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.97,0:07:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班会开完之后 等我发现 你已经没了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.81,0:07:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是… 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.73,0:07:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始也不晚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.41,0:07:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.26,0:08:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是… 我接下来 有点事…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.61,0:08:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 什么什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.73,0:08:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.07,0:08:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 怎么说呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.40,0:08:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 说的这么重要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.70,0:08:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是… 怎么说呢… 嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.07,0:08:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说嘛 说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.12,0:08:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}可以打扰一下吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.62,0:08:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.62,0:08:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.71,0:08:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是抱歉啦——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.75,0:08:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 小佑！！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.63,0:08:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.21,0:08:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像 一不小心就道歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.76,0:08:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 我也吓了一跳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.63,0:08:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一上来就被人道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.30,0:08:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.39,0:08:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 有什么事情么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.68,0:08:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 最近有好几起自动售货机里出现假钞的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.56,0:08:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想问问你们看没看到什么可疑人物之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.61,0:08:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 你怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.06,0:08:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没怎么走过这边呐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.73,0:08:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据目击情报
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.57,0:08:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人带着一个有红色条纹的茶色手提袋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.53,0:08:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 怎么可能…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.08,0:08:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.87,0:08:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.37,0:08:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不寻常的反应！！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.54,0:08:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…带着么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.21,0:09:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假钞… 带着呢么！？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.31,0:09:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 怎么可能呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.96,0:09:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不要开玩笑了啊 美绪…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.90,0:09:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶！？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.80,0:09:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要自投罗网呢！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.80,0:09:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶哦诶 你带着假钞呢吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.72,0:09:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎… 怎么可能～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.47,0:09:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在做好姿势准备何时都能迎接排球的哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.89,0:09:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.98,0:09:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.61,0:09:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一 两个人包里面的东西都给我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.90,0:09:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 请
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.53,0:09:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.07,0:09:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.03,0:09:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿出来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.11,0:09:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把假钞拿出来啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.53,0:09:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.95,0:09:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到… 竟然真的带着啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.08,0:09:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样… 就请饶了我吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.67,0:09:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样请您 饶了我吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.21,0:09:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一张吗！？ 假钞？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.26,0:09:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才不是假钞！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.51,0:09:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是货真价实的贿赂！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.72,0:09:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不明白你说什么呢！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.64,0:09:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之给我看看你的包…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.93,0:09:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要抵抗！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.30,0:09:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是亲戚的啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.85,0:10:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这个包 是亲戚的！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.23,0:10:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.94,0:10:06.56,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\pos(766,210)\c&H666669&}真\N是\N笨\N蛋\N啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.94,0:10:06.56,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H666669&\pos(424,277)}啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.94,0:10:06.56,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H666669&\pos(670,485)}前\N辈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.94,0:10:06.56,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H666669&\frz90\pos(670,520)}…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.94,0:10:06.56,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H666669&\pos(603,503)}我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.94,0:10:06.56,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H666669&\frz90\pos(604,530)}…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.80,0:10:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1·2
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.09,0:10:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.79,0:10:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.75,0:10:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.58,0:10:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.34,0:10:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激情…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz343.741\pos(1087,267)}烧\N好\N像\N退\N了\N呐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz343.741\pos(682,330)}诶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz69.744\pos(674,352)}…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz343.741\pos(683,387)}才\N没\N有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz69.744\pos(668,433)}…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz343.741\pos(970,530)}发\N烧\N是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz69.744\pos(953,589)}——
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz343.741\pos(692,603)}因\N为\N热\N情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz343.741\pos(670,584)}才\N烧\N的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.38,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\b0\c&H4E4E50&\frz69.744\pos(654,629)}…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.03,0:11:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧好像退了呐…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.23,0:11:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}笨蛋×N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.04,0:11:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？ 怎么回事？ 事件？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.54,0:11:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 小治郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.99,0:11:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.25,0:11:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像刚生下来的样子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.01,0:11:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.63,0:11:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不吃饭么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.38,0:11:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要凉了哦~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.64,0:12:04.31,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H4E4E50&\frz314.898\pos(1067,451)\b1}四\N分\N五\N裂\N了\N哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.64,0:12:04.31,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H4E4E50&\frz314.898\b1\pos(643,566)}别
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.64,0:12:04.31,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H4E4E50&\frz314.898\b1\pos(664,477)}笨\N蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.64,0:12:04.31,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H4E4E50&\frz314.898\b1\pos(413,496)}笨\N蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.64,0:12:04.31,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H4E4E50&\frz314.898\b1\pos(256,293)}俊\N\N这\N是\N什\N么\N？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.18,0:12:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.01,0:12:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.56,0:12:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad3\c&H2C4C09&\4c&HE2E7E4&}小{\c&H280176&}治{\c&H09A7E8&}郎 {\c&H720CDE&}是{\c&H9966F7&}这{\c&H8F573F&}个{\c&H384B35&}样{\c&H343BB5&}子{\c&H9C7663&}的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.69,0:12:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在吃什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.49,0:12:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.16,0:12:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那么今天就到此为止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.06,0:12:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期中考试的范围 有张贴出来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.03,0:12:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以各自确认一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.18,0:12:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.06,0:12:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃总是一溜烟的回去呐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.26,0:13:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.94,0:13:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.34,0:13:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.24,0:13:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.03,0:13:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.58,0:13:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}再见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.58,0:13:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}好的 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.37,0:13:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰到盲点的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.66,0:13:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会想不懂装懂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.75,0:13:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是如此认为的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.10,0:13:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 借我橡皮好么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.02,0:13:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.06,0:13:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪边？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.73,0:13:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 借我橡皮呗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.94,0:13:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.15,0:13:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.65,0:13:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人形橡皮！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.07,0:13:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.99,0:13:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这哪能擦掉啊 只会越擦越脏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.04,0:13:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 借我橡皮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.04,0:13:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣也没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.87,0:13:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法呐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.42,0:13:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 哪边？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.50,0:13:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边×2
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.08,0:14:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行×N
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.26,0:14:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规则是你们一个一个来 刚才不算
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.51,0:14:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这规则什么时候才是头啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.26,0:14:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 从麻衣开始
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.47,0:14:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请 请
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.32,0:14:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请您自由调查
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.18,0:14:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫… 好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.56,0:14:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.27,0:14:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Damage攻击可是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.15,0:14:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 One Pena哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.63,0:14:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,One Pena是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.98,0:14:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}One Penalty：犯规一次
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.98,0:14:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,One Penalty哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.57,0:14:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯规一次的话会有什么后果么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.61,0:14:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请我23盒果汁！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.46,0:14:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还怀恨在心呐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.44,0:14:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.24,0:14:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Baby Star干脆面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.24,0:14:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}ベビースターラーメン{\r\fs36}：美绪手中拿着的食品的品牌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.87,0:14:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}译注：出自《般若波罗蜜多心经》
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.87,0:14:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观·自·在·菩·萨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.46,0:14:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行·深·般·若·波·罗·蜜·多·时
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.96,0:14:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照·既·五…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.05,0:14:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！ 好险…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.55,0:14:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点就松开手了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.84,0:14:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是照既五 是照见五
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.05,0:14:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为行得通来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.22,0:14:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 Two Pena了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.35,0:14:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头 剪子…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.39,0:14:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.85,0:14:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天真！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.43,0:14:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总不能出握着东西的那边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.89,0:14:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.56,0:14:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.77,0:14:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中计啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.27,0:14:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么小佑 橡皮拿来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.40,0:15:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好好好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.98,0:15:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 猜中了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.07,0:15:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用技能的人形橡皮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.86,0:15:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢惠顾！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.24,0:15:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人形橡皮果然擦不下去呐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.08,0:15:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.95,0:15:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是名乃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.00,0:15:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.92,0:15:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是觉得 名乃是机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.84,0:15:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你差不多点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.38,0:15:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃很不高兴哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.13,0:15:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 为什么不高兴呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.05,0:15:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器人 很厉害的嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.55,0:15:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.94,0:15:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\c&HD6A6FE&\pos(622,498)}与爱有关的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.87,0:15:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.04,0:15:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.37,0:15:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起跑回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.75,0:16:03.42,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\fad(520,0)\bord5\blur8\pos(100,360)}第\N十\N五\N年\N的\N真\N相
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.84,0:16:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.92,0:16:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.71,0:16:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的要戴上这个去街上么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.80,0:16:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得好丢人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.51,0:16:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然说…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.01,0:16:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢人？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.93,0:16:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个窝囊废草团子啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.40,0:16:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.74,0:16:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云 东云
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.43,0:16:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在这啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.20,0:16:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云研究所…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.12,0:16:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 原来是研究所啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.88,0:16:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帅气！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.67,0:16:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 打扰了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.26,0:16:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧？ 没人在家么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.09,0:16:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 马上过来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.93,0:16:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 久等…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.60,0:16:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.72,0:16:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎怎怎怎怎怎… 怎么办啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.98,0:17:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么相生同学来家里了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.27,0:17:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是见到了博士的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.65,0:17:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}来了～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.07,0:17:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器人的身份肯定会暴露的！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.15,0:17:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}啊 你好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.61,0:17:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}啊咧？ 名乃呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.19,0:17:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.86,0:17:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}名乃倒是就在那里…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.03,0:17:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.57,0:17:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}难道是名乃的同学么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.45,0:17:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定只是来给我送卷子或者什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.45,0:17:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}哦哦 快进来快进来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.74,0:17:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.78,0:17:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 就在玄关这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.20,0:17:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}请进 请进
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.75,0:17:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}请不用费心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.16,0:17:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.05,0:17:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然已经进来了那就没有办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.30,0:17:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好在博士乱说话之前就替相生同学把事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.18,0:17:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 肚子好…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.93,0:17:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.76,0:17:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.93,0:17:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 刚才的声音？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.64,0:17:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只叫阪本的猫 他能说话哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.89,0:17:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.31,0:17:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.94,0:17:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能的嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.73,0:17:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪… 阪本先生！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.11,0:17:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你快点说喵！ 说喵！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.15,0:17:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？ 为什么我到现在了还要…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.70,0:17:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说喵 阪本先生！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.32,0:17:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 喵…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.20,0:17:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧？ 就是只猫而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.16,0:17:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.49,0:17:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.45,0:18:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天有客人来了 你先去外面玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.91,0:18:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.42,0:18:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.01,0:18:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.97,0:18:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没有好好打个招呼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.47,0:18:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是相生佑子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.89,0:18:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 你是名乃的妹妹？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.18,0:18:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我是博士
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.81,0:18:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我制造了名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.02,0:18:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制造了？！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.23,0:18:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.90,0:18:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个孩子但是好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.19,0:18:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为博士是博士嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.07,0:18:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不… 不是哦 相生同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.03,0:18:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.03,0:18:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是亲戚的孩子 父母都在工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.41,0:18:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为到晚上都不能回来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.57,0:18:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮着照顾她到他们回来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.37,0:18:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.95,0:18:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吧？ 对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.33,0:18:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.29,0:18:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！！ 笨蛋——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.92,0:18:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我重新给你上点茶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.21,0:18:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 名乃 稍微等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.30,0:18:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茶的话 就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.10,0:18:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 请喝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.68,0:19:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.31,0:19:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉～～害！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.27,0:19:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边是枪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.77,0:19:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帅！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.77,0:19:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级帅——！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.52,0:19:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要 完蛋啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.86,0:19:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 接下来是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.70,0:19:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耍帅句子大对决！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.12,0:19:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 从不才佑子我来开始
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.52,0:19:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 开玩笑的吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.58,0:19:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快起来啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.75,0:19:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你快起来啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.29,0:19:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦～！ 好帅！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.71,0:19:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是博士！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.21,0:19:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.46,0:19:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独角仙～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.84,0:19:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帅！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.17,0:19:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相生同学到底是来干嘛的？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.11,0:19:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放上去了 放上去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.27,0:19:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认输了！认输了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.43,0:19:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好小！好小！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.72,0:19:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.23,0:19:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.23,0:19:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有事啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.47,0:19:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天多谢了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.85,0:19:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叨扰多时 抱歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.90,0:19:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.71,0:20:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 那个 相生同学
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.03,0:20:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.83,0:20:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊… 实际上…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.12,0:20:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在学习变戏法
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.87,0:20:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不是什么机器人…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.75,0:20:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我当然知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.25,0:20:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃不是机器人这回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.67,0:20:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃就是名乃嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.76,0:20:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不就可以了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.59,0:20:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就是来跟你说这个的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.09,0:20:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都差点忘记了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.14,0:20:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 回见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.56,0:20:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.13,0:20:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相生同学
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.66,0:20:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.93,0:20:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是 你再方便的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.16,0:20:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！！ 会来会来！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.96,0:20:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.73,0:20:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.50,0:20:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次画画吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.05,0:20:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要画鲨鱼的画！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.55,0:20:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}鲨鱼吗？ 好帅气啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.47,0:21:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很帅的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.72,0:21:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼 我喜欢～！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.55,0:21:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}鲨鱼～ 博士 你喜欢鲨鱼的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.26,0:21:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼 喜欢 因为鲨鱼很帅嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.26,0:21:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.43,0:21:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}鲨鱼！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.64,0:21:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼鲨鱼…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.85,0:21:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一次～！ 再来一次～！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.04,0:21:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来再来…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.99,0:21:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼鲨鱼…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.11,0:21:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士～ 我也要来！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.99,0:21:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼～！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.74,0:21:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帅啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.75,0:22:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 阪本啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.42,0:23:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.51,0:23:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.90,0:23:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 也好吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.72,0:23:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花螺丝钉 这个名字真好听
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.72,0:23:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}译注：日文是{\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}プラスネジ{\r\fs36}，前面的{\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}プラス{\r\fs36}等于Plus
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.12,0:23:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种积极向上的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.45,0:23:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生就是要 不管如何都要向前进
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.54,0:23:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话的日常是第十七话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.96,0:23:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.13,0:21:46.72,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}みんなで歌おう　心を一つにして
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.06,0:21:57.27,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}悲しい時も　つらい時も
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.98,0:22:08.49,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}みんなで歌おう　大きな声を出して
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.83,0:22:19.00,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}はずかしがらず　歌おうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.05,0:22:29.64,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}心燃える歌が　歌が　きっと君のもとへ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.93,0:22:40.48,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}きらめけ世界中に　僕の歌をのせて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.94,0:22:53.37,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\blur3}きらめけ世界中に　届け愛のメッセージ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.13,0:21:46.72,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}大家来歌唱吧 将心凝聚到一起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.06,0:21:57.27,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}在那悲伤的时候 在那艰难的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.98,0:22:08.49,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}大家来歌唱吧 放出洪亮的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.83,0:22:19.00,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}不要害羞 来歌唱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.05,0:22:29.64,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}唱一曲振奋心灵的歌 这一曲必将传至你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.93,0:22:40.48,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}在这闪耀的世界中 装载上我的歌
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.94,0:22:53.37,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\blur3}在这闪耀的世界中 传递爱的讯息

Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.32,0:01:15.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.61,0:01:16.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.16,0:01:19.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.70,0:01:25.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}はい　言っちゃいましょ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.08,0:01:26.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}キミは　Best Best Friend!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.84,0:01:29.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.13,0:01:31.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと　ふざけてみたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.21,0:01:31.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.50,0:01:33.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　ふざけ返してくる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.63,0:01:35.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.38,0:01:36.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:37.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいったら　ありゃしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.43,0:01:38.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.76,0:01:40.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イヤなことあったって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.81,0:01:41.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.10,0:01:43.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}そっこー　忘れちゃうんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.22,0:01:44.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.81,0:01:45.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.52,0:01:47.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃんじゃん　やりましょー！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.56,0:01:50.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}２４時間　一緒でも　問題ない！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.02,0:01:52.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}まるで　双子か　親子か　クローンさいぼー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.40,0:01:54.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}これじゃ　恋愛する　必要とか　なくなくない？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.65,0:01:57.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}それと　これとは　全く全く　別問題！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.57,0:01:57.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.91,0:01:59.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}ケンカしちゃったときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.99,0:02:00.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.32,0:02:02.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}かなり凹んだときも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.33,0:02:02.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.74,0:02:04.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}一人で　いたいよなときも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:09.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}ふと気づけば　近くにいるしなばもろともー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.79,0:02:12.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんでだろ　{\r}そばにいたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.80,0:02:15.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}キミと一緒なら　{\r}時計１００倍速！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.67,0:02:18.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}楽しいな　{\r}楽しすぎるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.59,0:02:19.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}さすが　最強Friend!　{\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.30,0:02:20.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.43,0:02:22.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんなのよ　{\r}やっばいシンクロ感
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.43,0:02:25.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}いつも大騒ぎ　{\r}かなり　ご近所迷惑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.22,0:02:27.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何時？　{\r}えっとね　ヨロレイヒー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:28.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}わけわかんないない！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.52,0:02:31.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ソーレードーシーラー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.11,0:02:33.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像以上！なんていうか最高！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.61,0:02:34.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}あーだーこーだー言ってても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.82,0:02:36.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}友達　わっしょい！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.03,0:02:37.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.19,0:02:38.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.74,0:02:42.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ちゃちゃら　ちゃらちゃちゃーん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.32,0:01:15.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.61,0:01:16.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.16,0:01:19.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.70,0:01:25.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}来 说出口来！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.08,0:01:26.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}你就是 Best Best Friend！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.84,0:01:29.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.13,0:01:31.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 跟你胡闹一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.21,0:01:31.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.50,0:01:33.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加 回敬我大闹一番
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.63,0:01:35.38,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.38,0:01:36.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:37.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提 有多爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.43,0:01:38.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.76,0:01:40.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算发生了一些不快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.81,0:01:41.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.10,0:01:43.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}赶快 将这事情忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.22,0:01:44.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.81,0:01:45.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.52,0:01:47.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要 精神满满！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.56,0:01:50.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}24小时 都在一起 也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.02,0:01:52.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}简直像 双胞胎 或亲子 克隆细胞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.40,0:01:54.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这一来 陷入爱河 岂不就是 没必没必要？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.65,0:01:57.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}那件事 跟这件事 完全完全 两码事！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.57,0:01:57.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.91,0:01:59.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算我们吵架的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.99,0:02:00.37,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.32,0:02:02.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算非常低落的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.33,0:02:02.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.74,0:02:04.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算一人 深感寂寞的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:09.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}不经意间发现 身旁的你可同我生与死都相随
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.79,0:02:12.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}这是为何 {\r}想要在你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.80,0:02:15.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}如果和你在一起 {\r}时间100倍速飞逝！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.67,0:02:18.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真快乐呐 {\r}有点快乐的过头啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.59,0:02:19.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}不愧是 最强Friend！ {\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.30,0:02:20.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.43,0:02:22.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}搞什么哦 {\r}同步率快要破表
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.43,0:02:25.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}总是太过于兴奋 {\r}周围都 相当受到困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.22,0:02:27.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何时？ {\r}那个啊 哟啰咧咿呵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:28.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真是莫名其妙！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.52,0:02:31.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sol Re Do Ti La
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.11,0:02:33.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像之外！ 无论如何最棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.61,0:02:34.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}说那说这不管怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.82,0:02:36.03,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}都是朋友 哇塞！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.03,0:02:37.19,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.19,0:02:38.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.74,0:02:42.03,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ChaChaRa ChaRaChaChan


