[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-03 13:12:42
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 日常 第11話
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 愛蘇喵x石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,58,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,53,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.09,0:01:02.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}たった今　初めて気づいた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.09,0:01:02.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}就在刚刚 才第一次注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.76,0:01:05.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋に落ちたのだなー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.76,0:01:05.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陷入恋情了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.43,0:01:07.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h キミ☆　キミ☆　キミ☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.43,0:01:07.97,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h 是你☆  是你☆  是你☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.97,0:01:09.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意識せざるをえません！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.97,0:01:09.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全部都是你！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.93,0:01:12.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}なんか　いつもと違う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.93,0:01:12.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}总觉得 和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.47,0:01:11.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.47,0:01:11.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.56,0:01:15.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}キミと　ぎこちない会話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.56,0:01:15.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}我与你 慌慌张张的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.02,0:01:13.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.02,0:01:13.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.23,0:01:18.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}まさか　いや　片思い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.23,0:01:18.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}难道说 不对 单相思
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.69,0:01:16.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両思い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.69,0:01:16.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.02,0:01:20.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やばい！　視線合っちゃった！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.02,0:01:20.19,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！ 跟他的眼睛对上了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.44,0:01:24.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}なになに！？このドキドキ！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.44,0:01:24.03,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}什么什么！？心里小鹿乱撞！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.65,0:01:29.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路　ぐっちゃぐちゃ　混線…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.65,0:01:29.78,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路 黏黏糊糊乱糟糟 串线…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.41,0:01:36.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}こんなこと　初めてだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.41,0:01:36.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这样的事情 第一次遇到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.08,0:01:41.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}熱でもあるのかなー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.08,0:01:41.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}是不是患上感冒了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.75,0:01:44.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急転直下　いらっしゃた　恋心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.75,0:01:44.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急转直下 悄无声息来的 春心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.63,0:01:47.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっちゅうま　顔　発火で　まっかっか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.63,0:01:47.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一会的时间 脸 像着火 通红通红的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.22,0:01:49.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}バ·バ…バカな！？　手が震えるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.22,0:01:49.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}笨·笨…笨蛋吗！？ 手正在发抖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.89,0:01:52.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが　俗に言う　「恋」　なの！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.89,0:01:52.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 俗话说的 “爱” 的啦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.64,0:01:55.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}やややっちゃった　会話　噛みまくり
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.64,0:01:55.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}要要要要坏菜了啊 对话 咬到舌头了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.22,0:01:57.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気まずい沈黙　マミムメモ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.22,0:01:57.89,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难为情的沉默 āōēīū
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.89,0:02:00.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}キミの　気持ち　知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.89,0:02:00.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}想知道 你现在 心里所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.48,0:01:58.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キミの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.48,0:01:58.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.56,0:02:03.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.56,0:02:03.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.44,0:02:06.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！　{\r}いつもの通学路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.44,0:02:06.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！ {\r}好像上学走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.36,0:02:09.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}ピカピカ光る　{\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.36,0:02:09.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}亮闪闪的发光 {\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.74,0:02:12.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}空も飛べそうさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.74,0:02:12.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}感觉好像能上天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.49,0:02:15.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.49,0:02:15.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.02,0:00:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.74,0:00:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底要拖欠房租到什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.66,0:00:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这个月就有6万元了的说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.22,0:00:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.89,0:00:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要道歉 要房租！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.49,0:00:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次我来的时候你们说过这个月一定会付的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.58,0:00:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给房租！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.50,0:00:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装睡也没用！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.52,0:00:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}狸寝入り{\r\fs36}：指在不好的时机故意装睡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.10,0:00:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你们给房租之前我是不会回去的！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.86,0:00:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.20,0:00:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只是很少的一点…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.20,0:00:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}{\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}雀の泪{\r\fs36}：直译为麻雀的眼泪，表示很少的一点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.69,0:02:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}１洪都拉斯木纹龟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.96,0:02:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}２南部锦箱龟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.22,0:02:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}３圆澳龟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.29,0:02:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选２
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.88,0:02:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}答案是 ３哦 全世界…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.80,0:02:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.47,0:02:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你还没睡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.93,0:02:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒好了么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.06,0:02:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了哟～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.47,0:02:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那从明天开始要去学校了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.43,0:02:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上也要考试了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.44,0:02:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.44,0:02:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都请了三天假了 所以回学校了要好好问问同学们哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.65,0:02:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试的范围啦 课程内容什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.65,0:02:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.65,0:03:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要敷衍我！之前的考试也没取得好成绩的！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.59,0:03:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到没！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.66,0:03:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的 老妈真是啰嗦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.33,0:03:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且期末考试的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.41,0:03:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是明天吗！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.66,0:03:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38\bord0\shad0\frz6.572\pos(716,366)\c&H3A525F&}中\N奖\N了\N\N才\N怪\N呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.63,0:03:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…太迟了！！你的忠告来的太迟了啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.50,0:03:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你老是躺在被窝里没学习吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.36,0:03:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我学了啊！边睡边学了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.55,0:03:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你学了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.19,0:03:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.09,0:03:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底学没学啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.09,0:03:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是在讨论你忠告来迟了的问题吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.35,0:03:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我忠告你之后你会学吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.01,0:03:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.64,0:03:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是挂科的话老娘就灭了你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.23,0:03:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太极端了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.15,0:03:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Super Ultra Great Delicious Wonderful完蛋了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.15,0:03:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}译注：又是森林好小子中洛基的Super Ultra Great Delicious Wonderful Punch的捏他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.63,0:03:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 放手一搏吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.92,0:03:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离去学校的时间大概还有10小时
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.70,0:04:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸运的是明天的考试是英语和音乐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.15,0:04:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话就能把精力集中到英语一科上了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.60,0:04:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 现在我需要的是和昨天废柴的我告别&集中力！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.56,0:04:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了能毫无遗憾的送走今天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.94,0:04:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑着度过明天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.57,0:04:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算昨天滴落过泪水
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.90,0:04:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算至今无数次被击垮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.24,0:04:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也绝不放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.08,0:04:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直笑着面对这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.67,0:04:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乘着往远处的船
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.50,0:04:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向着远处的光辉不断奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.88,0:04:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是奔跑 奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.88,0:04:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是解开束缚的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.22,0:04:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.10,0:04:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.76,0:04:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一首好诗啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.52,0:04:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得很帅的东西！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.61,0:05:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.57,0:05:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工厂大叔的羞涩一笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.70,0:05:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先碰碰运气吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.16,0:05:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在不知道英语考试范围的现在 只有赌一把了！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.70,0:05:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是英语单词的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.83,0:05:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 参上！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.50,0:05:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Attempt 尝试
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.00,0:05:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Love把我的爱~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.59,0:05:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Always 总会别离
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.38,0:05:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Confirmation(组成)你的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.43,0:05:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,teleportation (传送) 现在正穿越时空
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.57,0:05:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.22,0:05:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Cosmos(宇宙) 穿过无尽的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.85,0:05:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Midnight submarine(午夜潜艇) 想与你一起乘坐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.10,0:05:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Forever 永远的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.11,0:05:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Forever 与你永远在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.77,0:05:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Forever直到时间尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.65,0:05:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.82,0:05:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是诗么！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.78,0:05:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的 我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.58,0:05:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在学习已经太迟了什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.04,0:05:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜呼 真是的完蛋了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.28,0:05:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会被老妈杀了的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.71,0:06:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么偏偏今天感冒好了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.21,0:06:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒明明比被杀好上一百倍的说！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.78,0:06:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少… 多感冒三天嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.39,0:06:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.89,0:06:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话我赢定了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.64,0:06:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.82,0:06:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想考试的话 只要重新得感冒就行了嘛～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.57,0:06:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔！好痛！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.53,0:06:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是… 这样的话肯定能成
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.45,0:06:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是在病刚好的时候就洗冰水澡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.29,0:06:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旧病肯定会复发的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.25,0:06:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来！快来~！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.92,0:06:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很顺利嘛!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.84,0:06:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是要忍耐的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.55,0:06:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有度过了这个难关…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.47,0:06:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能走上胜利的康庄大道！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.59,0:06:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要重新发烧 就是我的胜利了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.64,0:06:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上吃刨冰…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.98,0:07:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把房间冷气开到最强
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.87,0:07:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不盖被子说晚安~☆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.11,0:07:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我竟然完全没事哪！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.21,0:07:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 快起来！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.34,0:07:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.55,0:07:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体温计！火柴！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.01,0:07:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等于 升温!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.47,0:07:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}你已经起来了么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.89,0:07:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}要去学校的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.12,0:07:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的神啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.93,0:07:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.29,0:07:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫 好烫 烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.06,0:07:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.39,0:07:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发…发烧了！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.94,0:07:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像又旧病复发了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.81,0:07:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少度？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.11,0:07:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.36,0:07:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8… 88.8度
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.07,0:07:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛弄坏它啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.49,0:07:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啊 是感冒了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.12,0:07:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是很精神么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.58,0:08:04.08,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\fs66\pos(800,360)\blur8\bord2}大\N工\N财\N阀\N的\N力\N量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.83,0:08:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}水肯定很好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.31,0:08:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢啦 提交社团申请书的截止日期是今天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.63,0:08:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点就要废部了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.30,0:08:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是就算申请通过了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.22,0:08:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去也会因为成员不足而真的废部啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.22,0:08:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件事的话不用担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.14,0:08:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说这个了 明天我请你喝果汁当谢礼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.43,0:08:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 举手之劳而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.69,0:08:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 别客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.90,0:08:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜~
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.69,0:08:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去的路上顺便买搅拌机和苹果吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.99,0:08:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.67,0:08:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是大工财阀的力量么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.10,0:08:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没绳子了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.13,0:08:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就不能做放到校长鞋柜里的稻草人了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.89,0:09:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来… 没有最重要的稻草
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.47,0:09:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想去买… 又没有钱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.81,0:09:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我零花钱的老婆不在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.31,0:09:07.94,XD,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs50\pos(631,421)}老婆、同窗旅行中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.11,0:09:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了但是米没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.40,0:09:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候真想喝白兰地一醉方休
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.90,0:09:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 肝脏刚动过刀子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.99,0:09:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪神队又输了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.49,0:09:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知是为了环保还是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.82,0:09:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买个芝士牛肉汉堡发现没有芝士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.95,0:09:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己主页的留言板完全没人来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.66,0:09:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来昨天我组织的聊天大会也是参加的人一个都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.52,0:09:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人来这事让我想起来…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.86,0:09:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天我坐的巴士也是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.19,0:09:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上车之后 所有人都下车了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.53,0:10:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部人都下车了这事 让我想起来…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.74,0:10:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中时的修学旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.99,0:10:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}老师~
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.78,0:10:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)\shad0\bord0\c&H2D3134&\fs30\frz32.13\pos(757,340)}修学旅行指南\N\N\N\N\N\N借宿于镰仓民家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.54,0:10:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了熄灯的时间关了灯之后2分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.58,0:10:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问了一句“大家都还醒着么”之后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.13,0:10:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现所有人都睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.51,0:10:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡着了这事 让我想起最近貌似有点失眠
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.51,0:10:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了逼着自己睡着不停地在睡前吃东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.85,0:10:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然都长奶油肚了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.85,0:10:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物什么的 让我想起上个月的生日礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.48,0:10:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然… 只有一个黄油卷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.53,0:10:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.86,0:10:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种悲观的想法都给我闪开
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.03,0:10:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该想想快乐的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.37,0:10:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？是谁呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.83,0:10:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.46,0:10:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 原来是君子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.34,0:10:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈去旅行了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.34,0:10:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想着给你过来做饭
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.13,0:10:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 真是得救了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.88,0:11:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午安
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.64,0:11:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午安 小美又长大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.43,0:11:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是嘛  今天就啥也别想陪孙子玩一天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.81,0:11:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那个 刚才我在公园做了个团子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.52,0:11:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你吃也行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.28,0:11:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.15,0:11:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肚子饿了吧 给你吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.82,0:11:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.07,0:11:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部是用巧克力做的哦 快吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.62,0:11:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛是嘛 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.96,0:11:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哭什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.88,0:11:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸的泪腺真是松呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.42,0:11:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 厨房借用一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.51,0:11:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.47,0:11:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生不是只有不幸的事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.59,0:11:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有这样的好事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.76,0:11:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 全部是巧克力做的啦 快吃啦~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.18,0:11:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那个 快吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.56,0:11:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃的~快吃哦~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.90,0:11:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.06,0:11:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.19,0:11:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点啦~呐 快点啦~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.28,0:11:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫不犹豫地吃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.61,0:11:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.24,0:12:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.70,0:12:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.41,0:12:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很幸福的泥土味道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.87,0:12:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 外公倒下了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.22,0:12:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.71,0:12:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.78,0:12:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定 淡定
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.64,0:12:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么过不去的坎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.57,0:13:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是要杀了我么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.78,0:13:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好了~~！！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.26,0:13:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么玩意儿？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.46,0:13:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强力浆糊~
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.34,0:13:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.74,0:13:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为很强力嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.28,0:13:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.24,0:13:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个倒在走廊上…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.50,0:13:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让名乃和阪本动弹不得~
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.00,0:13:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又在做这种奇怪的恶作剧了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.92,0:13:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说谁会落入这种明显得不行的陷阱…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.38,0:13:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.59,0:13:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是上钩吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.68,0:13:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.84,0:13:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.72,0:13:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把我弄出来！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.10,0:13:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等下还有事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.14,0:13:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗噗 只要泼上水就能解开啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.77,0:13:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就快给我水啊 快去拿水过来！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.81,0:13:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 到了吃点心的时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.64,0:14:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说话！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.02,0:14:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那博士就先去吃点心了 告退了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.95,0:14:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧…？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.86,0:14:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧… 啊咧咧…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.53,0:14:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧…？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.16,0:14:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 现在咋办
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.70,0:14:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是糟透了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.70,0:14:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗 阪本你真像蟑螂清啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.75,0:14:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是笑我的时候么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.29,0:14:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不是跟我差不多！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.04,0:14:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 啊咧 啊咧咧~~
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.63,0:14:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 活该
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.59,0:14:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是天谴吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.76,0:14:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 真是奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.80,0:14:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 你一直一直都在做坏事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.89,0:14:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 啊咧咧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.02,0:14:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本 咋办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.72,0:14:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 阪本不见了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.36,0:14:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本…？阪本…？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.06,0:14:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本~~
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.54,0:15:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有水的话就解不开…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.04,0:15:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话就不能吃点心了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.83,0:15:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 说不定这样下去肚子会饿…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.67,0:15:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且不能吃饭 说不定会死的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.35,0:15:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会死的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.14,0:15:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样确实会死的啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.68,0:15:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了——
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.39,0:15:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是名乃啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.24,0:15:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.11,0:15:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说外面有35度呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.27,0:15:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在干什么呢！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.82,0:15:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 咱刚才拿着的浆糊咻地自己跑出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.86,0:15:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要泼上水的话呢 就能解开了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.45,0:15:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要泼上水的话… 名乃 名乃~~
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.41,0:15:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}水?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.45,0:15:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊～～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.50,0:15:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先站起来吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.75,0:15:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便在走廊躺着会把衣服弄脏的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.54,0:15:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.80,0:15:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊 这个？！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.92,0:15:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.26,0:15:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.47,0:15:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…手！！我的手！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.39,0:16:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是什么啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.43,0:16:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的手 手——
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.11,0:16:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H454746&\fs36\pos(878,555)}祝\N贺\N\N围\N棋\N足\N球\N部\N出\N征\N县\N大\N赛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.11,0:16:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H454746&\fs36\pos(538,411)}目\N标\N日\N本\N第\N一\N！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.70,0:16:18.12,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\blur8\bord2\pos(200,360)\frz270}MONEY
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.08,0:16:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部长？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.71,0:16:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是… 大工财阀的力量么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.84,0:16:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscy110\fad(900,0)\fs66\c&HFAF9FB&\blur20\t(0,900,1\blur1)\bord0\shad4\pos(640,550)\4c&H74907A&\3c&HE0E7E1&}差强人意的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.67,0:16:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}啊 终于下雨了 真是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.62,0:17:04.54,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\fs54\pos(1220,360)\shad2\4c&HE2E7E9&}接\N下\N来\N‵\N轮\N到\N阪\N本\N了\N哦\N
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.27,0:17:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜我是谁~~
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.98,0:17:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\c&H222A23&\fs36\pos(548,594)}陀思妥耶夫斯基
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.57,0:17:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是… 是博士么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.95,0:17:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜对了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.49,0:17:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿 露馅了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.20,0:17:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 与其说是露馅…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.41,0:17:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如说是只有博士会做这种事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.50,0:17:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这次换名乃来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.58,0:17:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 诶…好吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.67,0:17:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜我是谁~
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.71,0:17:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道！名乃！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.88,0:17:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云一家今天也很平静~
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.92,0:17:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 名乃 我猜对了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.44,0:17:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 猜对了哦~
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.01,0:18:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那那 下次还轮到我了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.60,0:18:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.16,0:18:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.12,0:18:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.96,0:18:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.38,0:18:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从第一问开始就完全不懂！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.80,0:18:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个像中了抹杀光线要消失一样的角色是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.13,0:18:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用什么单词形容啊?!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.80,0:18:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}注：ニフラム“抹杀光线”：勇者斗恶龙3~7里能让对方整队消失在天际的咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.68,0:18:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.35,0:18:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个问题…我好像做过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.81,0:18:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么来着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.52,0:18:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像我问过樱井老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.18,0:18:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.07,0:18:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.48,0:18:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.15,0:18:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}这个跟中了抹杀光线要消失了一样的角色？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.86,0:18:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}是老师画的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.73,0:18:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}这个跟中了抹杀光线要消失一样的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.40,0:18:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了！就是中了抹杀光线要消失了的东西！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.61,0:19:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔！！不是这一段啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.45,0:19:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先冷静下来！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.66,0:19:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静啊小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.04,0:19:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慌张的话会的问题都会变得不会的！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.00,0:19:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.29,0:19:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在飞的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.12,0:19:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,fly… 么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.04,0:19:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对不对不对…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.17,0:19:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话冲击力太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.27,0:19:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是什么怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.88,0:19:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Monster?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.97,0:19:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 这已经不是考英语了是在考推理啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.89,0:19:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在的我能做到的只有这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.22,0:19:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  下一个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.94,0:19:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样的怪物拿着网球拍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.48,0:19:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话刚才的那题就不是Monster了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.82,0:19:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么微妙的关联啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.90,0:19:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把刚才的答案擦掉 换个方向思考吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.91,0:19:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃呃！ 橡皮擦什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.37,0:19:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惨无人道啊！！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.25,0:19:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎 怎 怎么办啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.42,0:19:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 我只好用手指擦掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.30,0:20:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻…麻衣酱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.47,0:20:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然最值得拥有的还是朋友啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.60,0:20:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是钢笔擦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.02,0:20:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会擦破的 这样的话纸会被擦破的啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.06,0:20:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是扯淡的时候啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.98,0:20:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣酱 有没有普通的橡皮…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.79,0:20:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 睡着了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩十分钟哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.49,0:20:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间啊 时间不够了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.57,0:20:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 淡定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.62,0:20:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 淡定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.96,0:20:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.67,0:20:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将心…归于无…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.13,0:20:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归于无……
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.68,0:20:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 结束了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.01,0:20:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南无阿弥陀佛啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.00,0:21:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雨…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.69,0:21:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在心里一直下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.23,0:23:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}早安…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.19,0:23:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\fs18\b0\pos(603,439)\c&H423E39&}振 翅 吧 ！ ！ \N\h\h\h\h\h总 之 就 是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.52,0:23:06.15,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\blur8\bord2\pos(100,360)}打\N开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.93,0:23:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.94,0:23:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 早安
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.95,0:23:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧 里面有封情书啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.45,0:23:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧不会吧！！从哪来的？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.36,0:23:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面写着Q班的田中呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.24,0:23:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！！ 去看看吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.55,0:23:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是泥巴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.13,0:23:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是铁球
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.22,0:23:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我像泥土一样沉睡着~呼呼~
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.89,0:23:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在烈火中铸就~叮堂~
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.68,0:23:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回的日常是第十二话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.85,0:23:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.78,0:21:43.70,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}朝起きて　歯を磨いて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.95,0:21:46.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あっという間　午後10時
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.08,0:21:50.00,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　たくさん　笑ったなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.17,0:21:52.75,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}たくさん　ときめいたなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.30,0:21:56.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}友達と　バカみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.38,0:21:59.13,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}騒いでる　時にも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.47,0:22:02.47,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}チラチラって　目が合う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.60,0:22:05.18,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}…偶然、だよね。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.39,0:22:08.64,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋なんて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.85,0:22:11.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キャラじゃないんだもんっ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.98,0:22:17.82,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ねえ　あしたも会えるよね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.07,0:22:20.91,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}まぶたを　閉じると
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.16,0:22:24.12,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キラキラ　キミだらけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.28,0:22:27.41,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　楽しかったね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.50,0:22:31.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あー　恋　してんだなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.88,0:22:39.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}うれしいな　うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.01,0:22:42.80,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}はじめまして　こいごころ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.14,0:22:46.01,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あした　まだ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.26,0:22:48.68,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.39,0:22:53.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ゆめで　すぐ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.06,0:22:59.61,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.78,0:21:43.70,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}早晨睡醒后 起床刷牙来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.95,0:21:46.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}不知不觉间 已到晚十点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.08,0:21:50.00,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天也遇到 很多欢乐事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.17,0:21:52.75,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}也有非常多 刺激与紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.30,0:21:56.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}和闺中密友 像笨蛋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.38,0:21:59.13,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}大声吵又闹 偶尔会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.47,0:22:02.47,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶尔瞥向你 四目便相接
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.60,0:22:05.18,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}这也不过是 偶然事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.39,0:22:08.64,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋什么的难以说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.85,0:22:11.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}因为我不是这样的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.98,0:22:17.82,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}呐 我们明天 也会相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.07,0:22:20.91,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}将我的双眼 合上了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.16,0:22:24.12,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}脑海中只有 亮晶晶的你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.28,0:22:27.41,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天的我也 开心又愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.50,0:22:31.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}啊 陷入恋爱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.88,0:22:39.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}真的好开心 真的好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.01,0:22:42.80,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}第一次见面 我的爱慕心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.14,0:22:46.01,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}到明天的话 我们又见面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.26,0:22:48.68,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.39,0:22:53.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}在梦中很快 我们会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.06,0:22:59.61,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}现在晚安吧


