[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-03 13:22:39
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,45,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.34,0:00:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪闪发光啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.54,0:00:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 你在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.08,0:00:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.89,0:00:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以去那边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.57,0:00:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生最近掉毛很严重吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.88,0:00:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛会黏到衣服上的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.81,0:00:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啊 小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.07,0:00:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌我麻烦吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.56,0:00:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要换衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.55,0:00:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你稍微出去一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.36,0:02:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.53,0:02:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看看 正合身！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.86,0:02:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 那是因为按你的尺寸做的 自然合身啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.74,0:02:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.16,0:02:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 挺适合你的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.20,0:02:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那方面 不是那方面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.33,0:02:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来… 像普通的… 女孩子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.30,0:02:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 看起来跟外面的小姑娘一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.80,0:02:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生～！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.43,0:02:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真喜欢你～！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.47,0:02:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生～！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.30,0:02:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢你了～！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.93,0:03:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 黏到毛了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.93,0:03:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底想怎样啊 你啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.73,0:03:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校哦 学校！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.89,0:03:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会交到朋友的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.35,0:03:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驴唇不对马嘴啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.19,0:03:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“对啦 名乃”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.61,0:03:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“放学回去时要不要去吃冰淇淋？”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.03,0:03:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“啊 诶 去啊 去啊”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.24,0:03:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“那之后要去唱卡拉OK么？”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.49,0:03:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“诶？ 诶…”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.58,0:03:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“但是 我…”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.29,0:03:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“从来没去过！”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.91,0:03:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“我会教给你哒～”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.58,0:03:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“大家一起去嘛～”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.00,0:03:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“啊… 好… 好的”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.08,0:03:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}“那么…”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.79,0:03:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之类的对话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.30,0:03:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.47,0:03:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}啊 博士！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.51,0:03:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.88,0:03:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看看 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.18,0:03:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样啊？ 适合我么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.72,0:03:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的诶…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.14,0:03:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯！好漂亮！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.27,0:03:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.15,0:03:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件睡衣 也很适合博士哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.69,0:03:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.65,0:03:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 超漂亮的～！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.05,0:03:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是跟平时一样嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.91,0:03:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本～～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.37,0:04:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本也超帅的～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.70,0:04:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\}你也来啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.66,0:04:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手帕没问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.83,0:04:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生证没问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.25,0:04:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教科书没问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.37,0:04:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笔记本没问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.41,0:04:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铅笔盒没问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.50,0:04:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自动铅笔没问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.71,0:04:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自动铅笔芯没问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.60,0:04:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！没有落下东西！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.55,0:04:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗噗噗～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.13,0:04:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.17,0:04:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有落下的东西哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.84,0:04:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？诶 什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.99,0:04:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.72,0:04:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了的话…？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.69,0:04:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SNICKERS！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.93,0:04:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士～！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.64,0:04:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厨房里准备好早饭和午饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.81,0:04:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请记得吃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.23,0:04:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.36,0:04:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 洗好的衣服 等我回来了再拿进来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.86,0:04:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不用做就可以
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.99,0:04:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 学校什么时间结束啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.70,0:04:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三点半左右吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.04,0:04:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来的时候还要买晚饭的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.33,0:04:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家大概五点钟吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.85,0:04:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五点…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.09,0:04:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.34,0:04:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前没说过的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.21,0:04:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五点 那都晚上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.47,0:05:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对… 但是这是学校嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.22,0:05:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我走…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.39,0:05:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 博士？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.06,0:05:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不想让你去！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.97,0:05:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 刚才不还说可以去的嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.44,0:05:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以去！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.06,0:05:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}不可以 名乃 不可以去！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.90,0:05:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样… 都要迟到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.07,0:05:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把包还给我…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.94,0:05:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左手！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.86,0:05:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}滚啊滚×N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.86,0:05:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 小鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.78,0:05:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那么无理取闹！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.58,0:05:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.12,0:05:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 要不这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.66,0:05:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天晚饭做博士最喜欢的蛋包饭！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.33,0:05:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.42,0:05:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上回来的时候给你买鲨鱼蛋糕！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.01,0:05:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶… 那…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.47,0:05:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再加上草莓果汁！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.34,0:05:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚啊滚×N
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.85,0:05:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.35,0:05:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.64,0:05:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芥川奖也…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.39,0:05:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可办不到啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.56,0:05:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\c&HDECDA2&\pos(598,107)}鸡蛋豆腐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.52,0:05:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一时都不知道该怎么办了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.07,0:06:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸亏博士总算是让步了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.57,0:06:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来我也能迈出做普通人的第一步…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.16,0:06:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.25,0:06:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘得干干净净啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.67,0:06:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背上的发条…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.13,0:06:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.59,0:06:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅气的东西！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.60,0:06:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～的 大干一场吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.56,0:06:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！ 干劲满满的前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.40,0:06:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.98,0:06:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想了好久… 也想不出答案
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.69,0:06:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果就来到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.85,0:06:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 现在给大家介绍转校生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.95,0:06:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云同学
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.62,0:06:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.17,0:07:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果… 果然大家都很在意发条…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.72,0:07:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云同学 请自己写下名字
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.56,0:07:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发条 非常显眼…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.23,0:07:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不做点什么蒙混过去的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.15,0:07:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我… 我… 我叫东云名乃！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.02,0:07:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.66,0:07:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个听我说啊 那个… 这个发条啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.99,0:07:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 那个… 实际上…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.24,0:07:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在来的途中被插上去的！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.08,0:07:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.54,0:07:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷场啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.58,0:07:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 哎呀 那个听我说啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.12,0:07:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之就是 其实吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.04,0:07:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是骗你们的！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.21,0:07:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.63,0:07:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在解释些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.55,0:07:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃啊 怎么办啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.30,0:07:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.05,0:07:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 就是说啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.89,0:07:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不是像拇指是USB之类的 那种机器人似的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.68,0:07:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不行啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.86,0:08:03.94,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\pos(800,360)}占\N卜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.11,0:08:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希～望明天～是个好～天气
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.47,0:08:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 关口
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.79,0:08:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要光在看书 一起玩吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.37,0:08:16.08,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\pos(691,384)}围\N棋\N足\N球\N部
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.58,0:08:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易买来了人生游戏的啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.12,0:08:19.96,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1020,0)\bord1\shad2\fn黑体\fs40\c&HF2F2F2&\3c&H7A818A&\4c&H525D6C&\pos(328,60)}围棋足球部  部长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.08,0:08:19.96,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn黑体\fs45\bord1\shad2\frz314.985\pos(99,613)\c&H6269E0&\3c&HECEAE9&}人\N生\N游\N戏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.00,0:08:23.25,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1020,0)\bord1\shad2\fn黑体\fs40\c&HF2F2F2&\3c&H7A818A&\4c&H525D6C&\pos(947,60)}围棋足球部  部员
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.00,0:08:23.25,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1020,0)\bord1\shad2\fn黑体\fs36\3c&H7A818A&\4c&H525D6C&\pos(947,155)\c&HF1FCF8&}关口尤利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.67,0:08:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛～ 真无聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.84,0:08:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在围棋足球部才能玩珍珑棋局啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.93,0:08:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说我不会玩围棋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.39,0:08:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了——
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.35,0:08:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.52,0:08:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是围棋足球部吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.19,0:08:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.23,0:08:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要入部
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.57,0:08:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级欢迎啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.20,0:08:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同学 你叫什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.45,0:08:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一年级的樱井诚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.28,0:08:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.45,0:08:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是二年级的部长 大工健三郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.87,0:08:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是一年级的关口君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.87,0:09:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 嘛 坐吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.38,0:09:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.63,0:09:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 怎么玩？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.59,0:09:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩人生游戏么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.55,0:09:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.63,0:09:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不进行练习么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.68,0:09:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.57,0:09:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,围棋足球的练习
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.45,0:09:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实围棋足球这个名字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.81,0:09:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我创造的传说中的社团活动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.35,0:09:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种竞技实际上并不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.27,0:09:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上 就是大家在一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.44,0:09:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 说起来就是娱乐部吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.03,0:09:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.28,0:09:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初中的时候参加围棋足球部了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.41,0:09:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前一直不知道这个学校有围棋足球部来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.20,0:09:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 前段时间校舍上不是悬挂标语了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.58,0:09:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad0\fad(600,0)\c&H41403E&\pos(310,506)}目\N标\N日\N本\N第\N一\N！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.37,0:09:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才注意到的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.37,0:09:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.71,0:09:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中学的时候是MVP来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.22,0:09:58.56,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\shad2\pos(1150,360)\4c&HC2C1BE&}在\N意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.36,0:10:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东… 东云同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.89,0:10:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 到！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.23,0:10:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.44,0:10:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是非常在意…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.90,0:10:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 后背的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.69,0:10:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这… 这…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.85,0:10:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 啊… 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.45,0:10:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 那个… 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.74,0:10:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}哎呀… 那个… 这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.95,0:10:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.37,0:10:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓的围棋足球部 在做些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.95,0:10:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔—— 口头说明的话有些困难啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.67,0:10:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那给你来段个人表演吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.21,0:10:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是颠球
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.01,0:10:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从颠球…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.73,0:10:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.72,0:10:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.93,0:10:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从棋子…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.60,0:10:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单人德式拱桥摔！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.41,0:10:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此乃雪崩棋谱 三连星是也！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.40,0:10:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么情况啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.78,0:10:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来随随便便创了一个部…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.41,0:11:00.04,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\pos(691,384)}围\N棋\N足\N球\N部
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.70,0:10:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.24,0:11:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得超有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.87,0:11:06.21,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\shad1\pos(200,360)\4c&HC2C1BE&}鞋\N子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.26,0:11:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说… 等一下啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.76,0:11:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这突然是 怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.64,0:11:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪里啊 帕蒂？！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.35,0:11:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.03,0:11:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本～～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.79,0:11:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}阪本×N
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.28,0:11:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 我说… 住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.66,0:11:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是问我怎么回事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.41,0:11:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是不停的转来转去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.34,0:11:55.84,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\bord2\blur3\pos(100,360)\4c&HC2C1BE&}帕\N蒂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.79,0:12:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才第一天就出那么大的差错…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.74,0:12:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在怀疑我是怪小孩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.71,0:12:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 名乃你带便当来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.01,0:12:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 啊… 是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.76,0:12:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.51,0:12:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是带便当吃的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.22,0:12:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 是！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.10,0:12:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很普通的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.73,0:12:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你看看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.57,0:13:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很… 很漂亮… 呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.91,0:13:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.79,0:13:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了啊 小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.37,0:13:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午休这都快结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.58,0:13:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.83,0:13:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 回来的时候 被车和狗把鞋子抢走了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.38,0:13:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,费了好大劲去追
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.13,0:13:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然听不出来是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.51,0:13:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之貌似是件大事啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.01,0:13:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 但是平安无事的拿到便当比什么都强
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.39,0:13:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧？ 小佑你的午饭呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.27,0:13:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,边走边吃完了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.19,0:13:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？吃什么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.98,0:13:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回锅肉便当
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.61,0:13:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好牛！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.40,0:13:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回锅…什么的 嘛 算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.74,0:13:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 名乃 要来这边一起吃么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.45,0:13:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.62,0:13:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于名乃的事情多讲给我听听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.45,0:13:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有认为我是普通的女孩子啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.21,0:13:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难… 难道说… 想要做朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.58,0:13:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 名乃背后的那个是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.84,0:13:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这… 这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.17,0:14:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不是什么可疑的东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.01,0:14:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.47,0:14:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}难道说名乃是机器人？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.76,0:14:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 说什么蠢话呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.18,0:14:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉啊 小佑很笨的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.77,0:14:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 要没时间了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.73,0:14:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.06,0:14:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要赶快吃完了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.07,0:14:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.21,0:14:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 小佑 这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.80,0:14:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧青花鱼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.72,0:14:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你给我带的是？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.39,0:14:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是烧青花鱼么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.60,0:14:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炒面啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.60,0:14:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs34}译注：烧青花鱼{\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}（焼きさば）{\r\fs34}、炒面{\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7\fs30}（焼きそば）{\r\fs34}音很近
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.14,0:14:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.23,0:14:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说… 听错了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.61,0:14:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歉抱歉抱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.31,0:14:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是装装可爱就能解决的问题哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.77,0:15:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是特别的问题哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.36,0:15:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么？ 这很接近啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.78,0:15:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看只有一个字的差别嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.74,0:15:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也不能…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.37,0:15:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是够了 只能这样了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.49,0:15:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 米饭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.41,0:15:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.33,0:15:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白米饭啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.17,0:15:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.08,0:15:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…虽说是这么回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.59,0:15:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一个菜我怎么吃啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.76,0:15:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.55,0:15:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 因为美绪你自己说的烧青花鱼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.47,0:15:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炒面啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.18,0:15:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炒过的 面条 啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.68,0:15:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.97,0:15:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你看 这种事件 写到博客里面作为笑点给大家看的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.35,0:15:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有电脑哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.81,0:15:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不要这么怒发冲冠啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.90,0:15:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道啦 现在再给你去买吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.53,0:15:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿钱来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥我还要给你钱啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.91,0:15:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我没有钱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.83,0:15:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.25,0:15:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了的话赶紧给我买回来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.58,0:15:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午休就要结束了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.12,0:15:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK OK
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.72,0:16:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩 这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.42,0:16:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩了一个比索啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.97,0:16:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前想着留下来作为纪念
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.43,0:16:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩阿根廷比索了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.10,0:16:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩阿根廷 比索了啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.85,0:16:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿根廷 比索！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.60,0:16:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说明明是小佑出错了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.48,0:16:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该小佑你出钱啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.98,0:16:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了 我刚才买了自己的便当 没有钱了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.98,0:16:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那—— 我的午饭怎么办啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.32,0:16:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.07,0:16:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不 吃青花鱼！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.07,0:16:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青你妹——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.74,0:16:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.12,0:16:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}青花鱼？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.53,0:16:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说之前小佑你就很令人烦躁啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.29,0:16:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次每次都抄别人的作业啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.75,0:16:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己稍微做一做会怎样啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.12,0:16:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个笨蛋！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.25,0:16:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个笨蛋跟美绪吃不了午饭是不是完全没关？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.96,0:16:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全有关系哟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.34,0:16:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥关系？ 说出来看看哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.88,0:16:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是个笨蛋 所以听错了对吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.07,0:16:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 听错这种程度的事谁都会有的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.06,0:16:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这事唧唧歪歪唧唧歪歪 你心眼太小了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.73,0:17:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早饭也没吃 事关生死哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.91,0:17:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正笨蛋是不能理解呐！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.98,0:17:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是笨蛋！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.11,0:17:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你都承认你是笨蛋了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.15,0:17:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事先说明啊 这{\fsp8}次{\b1\fs54\bord2\shad2}绝对{\fs48\b0\bord3\shad3}{\fsp0}不会借你作业了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.74,0:17:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 不用 不用
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.57,0:17:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪你忘了我也不会借给你抄的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.62,0:17:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要看你那破作业哟！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.50,0:17:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说你都给我买错了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.08,0:17:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连一个道歉也没有么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.00,0:17:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我下跪道歉啊！下跪！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.21,0:17:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好好好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.55,0:17:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下跪道歉就可以了吧 下跪道歉！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.63,0:17:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 真是非常对不起！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.59,0:17:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看！ 我道歉了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.97,0:17:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以了吧？ 这样！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.60,0:17:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？！ 那根本不是下跪吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.52,0:17:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 对哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.56,0:17:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是下跪哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.68,0:17:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是身体前倾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.02,0:17:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前·倾！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.15,0:17:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥不给我下跪哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.27,0:17:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为姐怒了哟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.24,0:17:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 美绪才是笨蛋吧！？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.36,0:17:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊那是 之前的那个 奇怪的插画啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.16,0:17:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 奇怪的插画
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.24,0:17:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢…蠢啊你！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.79,0:18:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.37,0:18:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 那些插画？！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.50,0:18:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫名其妙啊 莫名其妙啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.75,0:18:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我画的易懂点啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.17,0:18:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还眼镜呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.25,0:18:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢啊你！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.71,0:18:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢啊你！ 蠢啊你！ 蠢啊你！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.34,0:18:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.34,0:18:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画个白痴似的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.80,0:18:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才蠢吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.97,0:18:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.14,0:18:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.68,0:18:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧给我吃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.81,0:18:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你点的这个烧青花鱼！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.47,0:18:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我点的是炒面！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.23,0:18:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我下跪道歉！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.60,0:18:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头深深的低下去！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.48,0:18:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经买了的东西 没有办法了吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.56,0:18:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我身为人类的道歉啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.07,0:18:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个人渣！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.82,0:18:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.28,0:18:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让你见识见识 真正的下跪吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.16,0:18:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是… 真正的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.41,0:18:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下跪道歉啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.54,0:18:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还少一句“买成烧青花鱼了真是抱歉”呢！？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.08,0:18:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你下跪谢罪对吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.12,0:18:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 说啊你！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.08,0:18:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说“买成烧青花鱼了真是抱歉”
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.46,0:18:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 赶紧说吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.67,0:18:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说“我是个笨蛋真是对不起”
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.59,0:18:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诚心道歉啊 你这个人渣！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.18,0:18:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 赶紧的！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.59,0:18:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点说！ 笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.22,0:18:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧道歉 白痴！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.89,0:19:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渣滓！ 白痴！ 笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.16,0:19:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 一直说笨蛋笨蛋的 美绪你好吵啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.83,0:19:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你交往了半年了 你了解我些什么啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.45,0:19:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也是 哪里懂我的画啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.71,0:19:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然知道啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.71,0:19:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画得那么好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.09,0:19:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去做漫画家多好！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说… 说什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.47,0:19:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟个笨蛋似的！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.68,0:19:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说别人笨蛋的人才是笨蛋吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.55,0:19:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.64,0:19:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自己在说笨蛋吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.31,0:19:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没说哟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.81,0:19:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.60,0:19:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你的那种特质 我倒也不讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.65,0:19:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈… 哈！？ 说什么呢！？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.32,0:19:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子明明很好！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.36,0:19:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真… 真啰嗦呐 你个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.49,0:20:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑脸的天才！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.74,0:20:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什… 什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.87,0:20:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是！ 亏你画画那么好！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.62,0:20:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦！ 亏你跑得那么快！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.37,0:20:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你脑子那么好！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.67,0:20:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你那么乐观！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.00,0:20:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你脑子那么好！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.38,0:20:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是 亏你脑子那么好！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.71,0:20:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.48,0:20:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad0\c&H8C928E&\pos(670,245)}围棋！！足球部
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.48,0:20:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad0\c&H8C928E&\pos(901,537)}那\N是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.48,0:20:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad0\c&H8C928E&\pos(851,609)}棋\N子\N和
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.48,0:20:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad0\c&H8C928E&\pos(803,627)}足\N球\N的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.48,0:20:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad0\c&H8C928E&\pos(752,611)}故\N事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.66,0:20:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.66,0:20:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\c&H7F8387&\fs40\fad(680,680)\bord0\shad0\pos(442,236)}黑与白的\N魂！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.62,0:20:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}我… 好不甘！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.20,0:20:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}别哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.08,0:20:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}你还有明年呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.03,0:20:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}一定！前辈的份也一起加油！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.54,0:20:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}太好啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.59,0:20:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前的事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.09,0:21:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.39,0:21:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上学有趣么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.85,0:21:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.60,0:21:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了好多事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.72,0:21:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.93,0:21:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呐？怎么说呐？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.31,0:21:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友啊 真的好赞啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.32,0:21:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真赞！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.57,0:21:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 我说 莫名其妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.28,0:21:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了！怎么了！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.04,0:21:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.87,0:21:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.37,0:21:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请帮我把后背的发条拿下来！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.00,0:21:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.88,0:21:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.50,0:21:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在学校的生活会有各种各样的情况…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.26,0:21:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也是 被人怀疑是机器人来的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.39,0:21:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话就交不到朋友了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.01,0:21:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能交到哦 因为很可爱嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.02,0:21:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不可爱呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.60,0:21:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可爱哦 发条
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.24,0:21:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样都好啦 赶紧做饭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.19,0:21:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士～！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.16,0:23:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是足球…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.95,0:23:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踢啊踢啊 被各种踢 踢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.99,0:23:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踢啊 踢坏了 踢到死
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.79,0:23:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就长眠了！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.12,0:23:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话日常是第十五话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.92,0:23:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.68,0:22:14.78,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}いま私の願いごとが
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.69,0:22:25.95,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\blur3}かなうならば　翼がほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.31,0:22:34.88,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,300)\blur3}この背中の　鳥のように
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.26,0:22:48.31,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}白い翼つけてください
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:53.94,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}この大空に　翼をひろげ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.11,0:22:58.82,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}飛んで行きたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.28,0:23:04.24,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}悲しみのない　自由な空へ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.41,0:23:12.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}翼はためかせ　行きたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.68,0:22:14.78,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}如今对我来讲心中所愿所想
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.69,0:22:25.95,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,500)\blur3}能够实现的话 真想要一双翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.31,0:22:34.88,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,300)\blur3}在我的后背上 像那鸟儿一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.26,0:22:48.31,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}请赐予我一双洁白无瑕的翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:53.94,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}在这广阔蓝天上 张开这一双翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.11,0:22:58.82,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}向着远方振翅翱翔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.28,0:23:04.24,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}忘却所有的悲伤 朝着自由的天上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.41,0:23:12.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\blur3}随风挥舞着那翅膀 向着远方

Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.42,0:00:45.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.71,0:00:46.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.26,0:00:49.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.80,0:00:55.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}はい　言っちゃいましょ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.18,0:00:56.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}キミは　Best Best Friend!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.94,0:00:59.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.23,0:01:01.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと　ふざけてみたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.31,0:01:01.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.60,0:01:03.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　ふざけ返してくる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.73,0:01:05.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:06.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.15,0:01:07.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいったら　ありゃしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.53,0:01:08.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.86,0:01:10.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イヤなことあったって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.91,0:01:11.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.20,0:01:14.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}そっこー　忘れちゃうんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.32,0:01:14.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.91,0:01:15.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.62,0:01:17.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃんじゃん　やりましょー！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.66,0:01:20.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}２４時間　一緒でも　問題ない！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.12,0:01:22.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}まるで　双子か　親子か　クローンさいぼー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.50,0:01:25.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}これじゃ　恋愛する　必要とか　なくなくない？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.75,0:01:27.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}それと　これとは　全く全く　別問題！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.67,0:01:28.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.01,0:01:30.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}ケンカしちゃったときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.09,0:01:30.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.42,0:01:32.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}かなり凹んだときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.43,0:01:32.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.84,0:01:34.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}一人で　いたいよなときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.89,0:01:39.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}ふと気づけば　近くにいるしなばもろともー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.89,0:01:42.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんでだろ　{\r}そばにいたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.90,0:01:45.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}キミと一緒なら　{\r}時計１００倍速！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.77,0:01:48.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}楽しいな　{\r}楽しすぎるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.69,0:01:49.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}さすが　最強Friend!　{\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.40,0:01:50.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.53,0:01:52.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんなのよ　{\r}やっばいシンクロ感
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.53,0:01:55.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}いつも大騒ぎ　{\r}かなり　ご近所迷惑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:57.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何時？　{\r}えっとね　ヨロレイヒー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.33,0:01:58.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}わけわかんないない！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.62,0:02:01.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ソーレードーシーラー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.21,0:02:03.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像以上！なんていうか最高！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.71,0:02:04.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}あーだーこーだー言ってても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.92,0:02:06.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}友達　わっしょい！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.13,0:02:07.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.29,0:02:08.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.84,0:02:12.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ちゃちゃら　ちゃらちゃちゃーん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.42,0:00:45.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.71,0:00:46.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.26,0:00:49.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.80,0:00:55.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}来 说出口来！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.18,0:00:56.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}你就是 Best Best Friend！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.94,0:00:59.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.23,0:01:01.31,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 跟你胡闹一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.31,0:01:01.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.60,0:01:03.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加 回敬我大闹一番
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.73,0:01:05.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:06.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.15,0:01:07.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提 有多爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.53,0:01:08.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.86,0:01:10.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算发生了一些不快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.91,0:01:11.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.20,0:01:14.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}赶快 将这事情忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.32,0:01:14.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.91,0:01:15.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.62,0:01:17.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要 精神满满！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.66,0:01:20.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}24小时 都在一起 也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.12,0:01:22.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}简直像 双胞胎 或亲子 克隆细胞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.50,0:01:25.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这一来 陷入爱河 岂不就是 没必没必要？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.75,0:01:27.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}那件事 跟这件事 完全完全 两码事！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.67,0:01:28.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.01,0:01:30.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算我们吵架的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.09,0:01:30.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.42,0:01:32.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算非常低落的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.43,0:01:32.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.84,0:01:34.89,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算一人 深感寂寞的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.89,0:01:39.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}不经意间发现 身旁的你可同我生与死都相随
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.89,0:01:42.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}这是为何 {\r}想要在你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.90,0:01:45.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}如果和你在一起 {\r}时间100倍速飞逝！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.77,0:01:48.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真快乐呐 {\r}有点快乐的过头啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.69,0:01:49.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}不愧是 最强Friend！ {\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.40,0:01:50.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.53,0:01:52.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}搞什么哦 {\r}同步率快要破表
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.53,0:01:55.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}总是太过于兴奋 {\r}周围都 相当受到困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:57.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何时？ {\r}那个啊 哟啰咧咿呵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.33,0:01:58.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真是莫名其妙！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.62,0:02:01.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sol Re Do Ti La
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.21,0:02:03.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像之外！ 无论如何最棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.71,0:02:04.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}说那说这不管怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.92,0:02:06.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}都是朋友 哇塞！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.13,0:02:07.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.29,0:02:08.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.84,0:02:12.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ChaChaRa ChaRaChaChan







































