[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-03 13:29:51
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 日常 第13話
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,58,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.99,0:02:12.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}たった今　初めて気づいた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.66,0:02:15.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋に落ちたのだなー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.33,0:02:17.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h キミ☆　キミ☆　キミ☆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.87,0:02:19.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意識せざるをえません！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.83,0:02:22.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}なんか　いつもと違う
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.37,0:02:21.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.46,0:02:25.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}キミと　ぎこちない会話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.92,0:02:23.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.13,0:02:27.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}まさか　いや　片思い
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.59,0:02:26.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両思い
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.92,0:02:30.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やばい！　視線合っちゃった！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.34,0:02:33.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}なになに！？このドキドキ！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.55,0:02:39.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路　ぐっちゃぐちゃ　混線…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.31,0:02:45.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}こんなこと　初めてだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.98,0:02:51.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}熱でもあるのかなー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.65,0:02:54.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急転直下　いらっしゃた　恋心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.53,0:02:57.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっちゅうま　顔　発火で　まっかっか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.12,0:02:59.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}バ·バ…バカな！？　手が震えるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.79,0:03:02.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが　俗に言う　「恋」　なの！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.54,0:03:05.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}やややっちゃった　会話　噛みまくり
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.12,0:03:07.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気まずい沈黙　マミムメモ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.79,0:03:10.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}キミの　気持ち　知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.38,0:03:08.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キミの
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.46,0:03:13.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.34,0:03:16.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！　{\r}いつもの通学路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.26,0:03:19.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}ピカピカ光る　{\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.64,0:03:22.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}空も飛べそうさ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.39,0:03:25.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.99,0:02:12.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}就在刚刚 才第一次注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.66,0:02:15.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陷入恋情了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.33,0:02:17.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h 是你☆  是你☆  是你☆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.87,0:02:19.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全部都是你！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.83,0:02:22.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}总觉得 和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.37,0:02:21.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.46,0:02:25.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}我与你 慌慌张张的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.92,0:02:23.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.13,0:02:27.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}难道说 不对 单相思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.59,0:02:26.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.92,0:02:30.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！ 跟他的眼睛对上了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.34,0:02:33.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}什么什么！？心里小鹿乱撞！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.55,0:02:39.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路 黏黏糊糊乱糟糟 串线…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.31,0:02:45.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这样的事情 第一次遇到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.98,0:02:51.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}是不是患上感冒了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.65,0:02:54.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急转直下 悄无声息来的 春心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.53,0:02:57.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一会的时间 脸 像着火 通红通红的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.12,0:02:59.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}笨·笨…笨蛋吗！？ 手正在发抖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.79,0:03:02.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 俗话说的 “爱” 的啦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.54,0:03:05.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}要要要要坏菜了啊 对话 咬到舌头了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.12,0:03:07.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难为情的沉默 āōēīū
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.79,0:03:10.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}想知道 你现在 心里所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.38,0:03:08.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.46,0:03:13.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.34,0:03:16.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！ {\r}好像上学走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.26,0:03:19.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}亮闪闪的发光 {\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.64,0:03:22.14,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}感觉好像能上天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.39,0:03:25.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.61,0:00:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好饿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.15,0:00:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.71,0:00:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是拿她没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.56,0:00:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 这种程度的陷阱我就中一下好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.75,0:00:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连猎物都没变
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.15,0:00:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中招了！ 中招了！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.59,0:00:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.83,0:00:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挨了一闷棍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.15,0:00:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这明明是准备中午吃的菜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.00,0:00:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没有菜了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.22,0:00:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.58,0:00:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是共犯哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.09,0:00:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为阪本说想吃才…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.89,0:00:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.16,0:00:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没说过哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.34,0:00:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.34,0:00:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼你乱说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.46,0:00:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你都吃了嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.94,0:00:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}今天好热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.27,0:00:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}是好热呐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.97,0:01:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}回去的路上去站前吃冰淇淋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.00,0:01:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}好啊 好啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.52,0:01:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.74,0:01:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姑娘想去学校吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.97,0:01:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不想让你去呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.40,0:01:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么突然这个样子？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.40,0:01:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说名乃你要去别的地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.76,0:01:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？谁说的这些话啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.44,0:01:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.69,0:01:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的才不是那回事呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.18,0:01:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 你要去哪里么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.69,0:01:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是准备上午去买东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.99,0:01:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午饭的菜都没有了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.57,0:01:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士我也要去 要去～！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.07,0:01:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}我什么都不买哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.65,0:01:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买鲨鱼巧克力吧～！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.55,0:01:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不买
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.21,0:01:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}买吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.42,0:01:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}鲨鱼巧克力…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.83,0:01:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不会买的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.56,0:01:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买吧 买吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.02,0:01:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}才不会买！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.38,0:01:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本都说买吧了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.18,0:01:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没说哟！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.85,0:03:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.20,0:03:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.70,0:03:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了 小佑！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.75,0:03:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摇摇晃晃的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.78,0:03:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从早上起来…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.50,0:03:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么一说的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.67,0:03:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…唔…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.26,0:03:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 语法形式都崩坏了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.06,0:03:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像也有点发烧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.98,0:03:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么身体状况都这样了还来上学啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.51,0:03:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不… 你看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.01,0:03:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前不是说过了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.58,0:04:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想 要给你变个魔术什么的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.37,0:04:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.73,0:04:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种是我第一次听到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.55,0:04:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}呕——
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.56,0:04:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 现在不是说魔术的时候吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.57,0:04:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易练习来着…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.38,0:04:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了我的魔术的话一定要大吃一惊哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.07,0:04:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.20,0:04:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呕——
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.63,0:04:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话我现在就大吃一惊了哟！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.03,0:04:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先回到座位…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.75,0:04:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.33,0:04:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.48,0:04:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.00,0:04:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到道具了啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.74,0:04:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先装作什么都没看到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.68,0:04:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟身体都这样了还要硬撑着来…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.95,0:04:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是小佑…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.42,0:04:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备连续放出什么大招呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.18,0:04:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.43,0:04:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出出 出出 出来了啊——！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.71,0:04:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道具都跑出来了啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.04,0:05:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞跑啦——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.20,0:05:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擤鼻涕纸——
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.50,0:05:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好·的 那开始了哦——
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.02,0:05:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,O… OK～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.94,0:05:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔哇 我在做什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.66,0:05:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉就藏起来了哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.04,0:05:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那——个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.00,0:05:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么… 首先是——
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.92,0:05:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没有注意到鸽子和手杖…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.29,0:05:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底多虚弱了哟… 你啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.93,0:05:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先来个烟穿百元币
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.86,0:05:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开着呢！！洞啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.99,0:05:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经…看见了！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.74,0:05:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.64,0:05:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是红桃A啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.48,0:06:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.91,0:06:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么… 从嘴里面…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.98,0:06:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞出来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.76,0:06:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.98,0:06:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.82,0:06:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了些… 什么手脚…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.34,0:06:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.83,0:06:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.48,0:06:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.79,0:06:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请好好睡觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.30,0:06:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我去超市了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.26,0:06:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！博士也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.21,0:06:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你捣蛋来着 今天什么都不给你买哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.65,0:07:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本 你真可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.00,0:07:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在说你啊 你啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.36,0:07:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 咱们走吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.42,0:07:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃你要买什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.24,0:07:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯… 还是鱼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.88,0:07:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士买些什么呢～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.52,0:07:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶！？ 博士今天不可以哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.04,0:07:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶～？ 那不买零食了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.14,0:07:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零食之外的东西也不可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.52,0:07:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不知道买什么好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.81,0:07:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之就是想买东西呐…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.84,0:07:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(606,558)\shad1\c&H6FFDFA&\3c&H4590E7&\4c&H132E50&}鲨鱼蛋糕
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.88,0:07:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～ 是鲨鱼蛋糕！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.60,0:07:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个临时摊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很好吃的样子 买来吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.45,0:07:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你忘了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.57,0:07:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不可以！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.98,0:07:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶～？你看 我想给阪本一份礼品来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.93,0:07:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生也跟着捣乱来着所以不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.25,0:07:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是想给名乃的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.87,0:07:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才说错了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.43,0:07:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了不可以就是不可以的！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.28,0:07:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在要是太宠她的话 以后又会做出同样的事情来呐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.00,0:08:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.31,0:08:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.44,0:08:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}给我买…×N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.92,0:08:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}给我买…×N
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.97,0:08:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}给我买…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.06,0:08:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}给我买…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.34,0:08:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}给我买…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.80,0:08:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在一定要狠下心来！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.71,0:08:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在该…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.31,0:08:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 不行不行…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.49,0:08:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一点点的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.82,0:08:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！不行！！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.02,0:08:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.68,0:08:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 不行不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.62,0:08:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.80,0:08:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.40,0:08:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.42,0:08:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是给她买了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.87,0:08:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 败给她了…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.05,0:08:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小鬼不管别人说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.25,0:08:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都爱乱使性子恣意妄为啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.79,0:08:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是该给她提个醒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.05,0:08:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.23,0:08:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多你也该学学怎么忍耐了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.70,0:08:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.28,0:08:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白你妹哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.06,0:09:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云家 今天也很和睦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.20,0:09:18.95,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\fs70\pos(1200,195)}80\N分
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.20,0:09:18.95,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\fs70\frz270\pos(1200,428)}Mongolian
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.20,0:09:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}注：这里的Mongolian指Mongolian chop 双手同时打击对方锁骨的一种拳击招式
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.10,0:09:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害哦 得了80分！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.15,0:09:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认真点的话你也很厉害嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.48,0:09:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀～ 啊哈哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.68,0:09:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么 得高分的秘诀是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.44,0:09:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没没没 哪有什么秘诀啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.87,0:09:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.82,0:09:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶～？可以的吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.37,0:09:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教教我秘诀嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.97,0:09:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑… 我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.94,0:09:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}80分 哎呦喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.63,0:09:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手…好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.01,0:09:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.39,0:09:41.89,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\bord4\blur8\pos(1100,360)}秘\N\N诀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.41,0:09:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.27,0:09:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我教给你得80分的秘诀吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.03,0:09:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,省了吧 我得了96分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.32,0:09:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,80分
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.94,0:09:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.84,0:09:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持不懈的努力和…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.37,0:09:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HEART哟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.10,0:09:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.74,0:10:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscy110\fad(900,0)\fs66\c&HFAF9FB&\blur20\t(0,900,1\blur1)\bord0\shad4\pos(640,550)\4c&H74907A&\3c&HE0E7E1&}差强人意的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.41,0:10:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H424043&}“相生”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.75,0:10:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H424043&}“唔唔唔唔…”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.93,0:10:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H424043&}“诶…？”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.26,0:10:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H424043&}“诶诶…？”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.56,0:10:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\c&H424043&}“太好啦——！！”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.69,0:10:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\shad0\bord0\c&H424043&\frz25.389\move(338,212,281,224)}国语小测
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.57,0:10:45.95,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\bord4\blur9\pos(800,360)}现\N\N实
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.07,0:10:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.23,0:10:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你做饭来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.65,0:10:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 还在旅行中吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.27,0:10:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 帮大忙啰！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.72,0:10:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.38,0:10:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 小美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.38,0:10:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 今天就陪孙子玩一天
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.42,0:10:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘掉厌烦的现实吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.62,0:11:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美 今天玩点什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.82,0:11:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊那个啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.09,0:11:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个先别管了 印章在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.98,0:11:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 印章在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.80,0:11:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏在哪里了啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.43,0:11:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 告诉我嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.79,0:11:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这书架上吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.17,0:11:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 印章在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.10,0:11:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}呐呐 在哪里呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.42,0:11:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这… 比现实更加过分啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.86,0:11:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}哪里哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.31,0:11:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}快出来——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.52,0:11:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好慢哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.69,0:11:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为定的几点见面啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.94,0:11:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.40,0:11:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着乘公交车去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.65,0:12:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果乘上时代之洪流了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.74,0:12:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.20,0:12:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样子…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.07,0:12:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走到御徒町站算了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.07,0:12:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}御徒盯站：位于东京都台东区的东日本旅客铁道的一站
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.06,0:12:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.90,0:13:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐～ 名乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.15,0:13:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.19,0:13:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.49,0:13:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神马事啊？博士…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.00,0:13:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉有点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.78,0:13:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要去尿尿
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.70,0:13:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃也一起去吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.09,0:13:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐～ 去吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.04,0:13:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.33,0:13:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 去吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.92,0:13:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐～ 名～乃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.29,0:13:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 呐～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.01,0:13:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼呼呼呼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.26,0:13:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 才不对哟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.18,0:13:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么不对？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.68,0:13:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俄罗斯红菜汤是食物哟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.39,0:13:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 不是那件事啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.52,0:14:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去尿尿吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.48,0:14:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 名乃～ 名乃 呐～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.20,0:14:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去啊！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.47,0:14:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你… 难道…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.83,0:14:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题 只有一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.75,0:14:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 你赶紧去厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.35,0:14:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.19,0:14:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去啊！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.56,0:14:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为担心她而没有说出来的阪本是也
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.40,0:14:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是 没有办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.24,0:14:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才说小鬼啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.95,0:14:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这深夜狂风里一个人去厕所更加不可能啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.70,0:14:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.92,0:15:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就应该
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.46,0:15:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她说我跟着一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.59,0:15:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让这家伙再次认识到我的可贵之处吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.42,0:15:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.97,0:15:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法呐 我跟你一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.93,0:15:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本又小又很弱的样子 还是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.78,0:15:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姑娘想去学校吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.33,0:15:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.42,0:15:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 过来这边了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.50,0:15:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.09,0:15:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去尿尿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.47,0:15:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了 我倒是不太想去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.26,0:15:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍微有点害怕啊 一起去吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.52,0:16:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 把我叫起来不就好了么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.90,0:16:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫了你好多遍了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.53,0:16:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“咚咚”的好响…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.70,0:16:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能有人来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.50,0:16:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是上面的烟囱在响吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.13,0:16:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过说起来雨还真大啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.47,0:16:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃？怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.26,0:16:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.64,0:16:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 呐～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.02,0:16:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.44,0:16:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打雷了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.88,0:16:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有博士在呢没关系的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.74,0:16:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧完事 回到被窝里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.66,0:16:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.60,0:17:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是… 一个人的话有点可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.23,0:17:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起的话好像就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.08,0:17:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来也是呐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.51,0:17:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃… 想去学校么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.10,0:17:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我会一直待在家里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.45,0:17:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是阪本说名乃想去学校
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.48,0:17:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯… 是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.83,0:18:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅气的东西！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.14,0:18:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,80分！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.13,0:18:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.36,0:18:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(900,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0}只言片语
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.34,0:18:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明一个月很快
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.75,0:18:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星期日却很远
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.59,0:18:35.17,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\shad2\pos(100,360)\4c&HE4E4E4&}兴\N致\N勃\N勃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.67,0:18:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一站是～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.67,0:18:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,80分 80分～～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.38,0:18:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在～右侧下车～～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.74,0:18:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.97,0:18:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来给你唱80年代的曲目哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.51,0:18:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只唱80分 噗噗噗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.31,0:18:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.06,0:18:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,80分 哎呦喂…x3
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.94,0:18:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我坠入伊甸吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.19,0:18:56.15,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord4\blur8\pos(800,360)}伊\N\N甸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.57,0:18:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 静一静啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.28,0:19:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在发表这一次的平均分
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.20,0:19:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次是——
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.99,0:19:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,92分！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.24,0:19:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.99,0:19:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.04,0:19:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.54,0:19:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.32,0:19:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.87,0:19:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这一下子的干嘛啊 小鬼？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.67,0:19:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是在做什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.67,0:19:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别玩了 来帮忙整理洗好的衣服吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.80,0:20:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开始 你可以去学校了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.73,0:20:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.56,0:20:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.90,0:20:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然间这是怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.03,0:20:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是博士我的妙计
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.24,0:20:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好啦——！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.25,0:20:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来白天吃多少零食都不会被骂啰…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.88,0:20:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 博士…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.26,0:20:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话就不能背双背带书包了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.89,0:20:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去上高中哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.35,0:20:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是博士
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.56,0:20:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把发条拿下来的话 去学校就…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.48,0:20:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是名乃的制服
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.67,0:21:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢博士了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.05,0:21:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃×N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.26,0:21:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士×N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.80,0:21:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃×N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.89,0:21:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士×N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.52,0:21:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃×N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.77,0:21:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士×N
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.98,0:21:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～～      博士～～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.73,0:21:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～～      博士～～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.40,0:21:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃名乃～～      博士博士～～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.44,0:21:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～～      博士～～
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.97,0:23:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是万国旗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.22,0:23:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常会听到BANKOKKI和BANKOKUKI两种念法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.84,0:23:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但好像两种念法都是正确的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.38,0:23:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸最后说过“细节就不要在意了”…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.65,0:23:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话是第十四话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.74,0:23:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.81,0:22:08.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}朝起きて　歯を磨いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.98,0:22:11.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あっという間　午後10時
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.11,0:22:15.03,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　たくさん　笑ったなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.19,0:22:17.78,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}たくさん　ときめいたなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.32,0:22:21.24,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}友達と　バカみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.41,0:22:24.16,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}騒いでる　時にも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.49,0:22:27.50,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}チラチラって　目が合う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.62,0:22:30.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}…偶然、だよね。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.42,0:22:33.67,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋なんて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.88,0:22:36.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キャラじゃないんだもんっ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.01,0:22:42.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ねえ　あしたも会えるよね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.09,0:22:45.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}まぶたを　閉じると
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.18,0:22:49.14,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キラキラ　キミだらけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.31,0:22:52.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　楽しかったね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.60,0:22:56.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あー　恋　してんだなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.91,0:23:04.87,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}うれしいな　うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.03,0:23:07.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}はじめまして　こいごころ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.16,0:23:11.04,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あした　まだ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.29,0:23:13.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.42,0:23:18.46,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ゆめで　すぐ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.09,0:23:24.64,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.81,0:22:08.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}早晨睡醒后 起床刷牙来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.98,0:22:11.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}不知不觉间 已到晚十点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.11,0:22:15.03,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天也遇到 很多欢乐事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.19,0:22:17.78,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}也有非常多 刺激与紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.32,0:22:21.24,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}和闺中密友 像笨蛋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.41,0:22:24.16,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}大声吵又闹 偶尔会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.49,0:22:27.50,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶尔瞥向你 四目便相接
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.62,0:22:30.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}这也不过是 偶然事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.42,0:22:33.67,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋什么的难以说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.88,0:22:36.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}因为我不是这样的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.01,0:22:42.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}呐 我们明天 也会相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.09,0:22:45.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}将我的双眼 合上了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.18,0:22:49.14,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}脑海中只有 亮晶晶的你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.31,0:22:52.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天的我也 开心又愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.60,0:22:56.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}啊 陷入恋爱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.91,0:23:04.87,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}真的好开心 真的好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.03,0:23:07.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}第一次见面 我的爱慕心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.16,0:23:11.04,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}到明天的话 我们又见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.29,0:23:13.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.42,0:23:18.46,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}在梦中很快 我们会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.09,0:23:24.64,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}现在晚安吧


