[Script Info]
;  This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
;  For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;  go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;  or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;  
;  Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
;  http://www.anime-fansubs.org
;  
;  For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
;  or email gabest@freemail.hu
;  
;  Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
;  
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-02 12:28:34
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,58,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,53,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.02,0:00:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近校内的风纪乱起来了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.52,0:00:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱井老师你身为学生指导
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.94,0:00:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能再稍微严管些
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.53,0:00:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.61,0:00:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我会加油的！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.19,0:00:32.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}たった今　初めて気づいた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.19,0:00:32.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}就在刚刚 才第一次注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.86,0:00:35.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋に落ちたのだなー
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.86,0:00:35.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陷入恋情了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.53,0:00:38.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h キミ☆　キミ☆　キミ☆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.53,0:00:38.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h 是你☆  是你☆  是你☆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.07,0:00:39.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意識せざるをえません！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.07,0:00:39.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全部都是你！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.03,0:00:42.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}なんか　いつもと違う
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.03,0:00:42.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}总觉得 和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.57,0:00:41.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.57,0:00:41.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.66,0:00:45.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}キミと　ぎこちない会話
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.66,0:00:45.28,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}我与你 慌慌张张的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.12,0:00:44.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.12,0:00:44.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.33,0:00:48.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}まさか　いや　片思い
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.33,0:00:48.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}难道说 不对 单相思
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.79,0:00:46.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両思い
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.79,0:00:46.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.12,0:00:50.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やばい！　視線合っちゃった！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.12,0:00:50.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！ 跟他的眼睛对上了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.54,0:00:54.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}なになに！？このドキドキ！？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.54,0:00:54.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}什么什么！？心里小鹿乱撞！？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.75,0:00:59.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路　ぐっちゃぐちゃ　混線…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.75,0:00:59.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路 黏黏糊糊乱糟糟 串线…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.51,0:01:06.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}こんなこと　初めてだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.51,0:01:06.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这样的事情 第一次遇到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.18,0:01:11.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}熱でもあるのかなー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.18,0:01:11.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}是不是患上感冒了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.85,0:01:14.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急転直下　いらっしゃた　恋心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.85,0:01:14.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急转直下 悄无声息来的 春心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.73,0:01:17.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっちゅうま　顔　発火で　まっかっか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.73,0:01:17.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一会的时间 脸 像着火 通红通红的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.32,0:01:19.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}バ·バ…バカな！？　手が震えるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.32,0:01:19.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}笨·笨…笨蛋吗！？ 手正在发抖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.99,0:01:22.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが　俗に言う　「恋」　なの！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.99,0:01:22.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 俗话说的 “爱” 的啦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.74,0:01:25.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}やややっちゃった　会話　噛みまくり
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.74,0:01:25.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}要要要要坏菜了啊 对话 咬到舌头了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.32,0:01:27.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気まずい沈黙　マミムメモ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.32,0:01:27.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难为情的沉默 āōēīū
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.99,0:01:30.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}キミの　気持ち　知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.99,0:01:30.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}想知道 你现在 心里所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.58,0:01:29.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キミの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.58,0:01:29.04,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.66,0:01:33.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.66,0:01:33.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.54,0:01:36.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！　{\r}いつもの通学路
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.54,0:01:36.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！ {\r}好像上学走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.46,0:01:39.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}ピカピカ光る　{\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.46,0:01:39.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}亮闪闪的发光 {\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.84,0:01:42.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}空も飛べそうさ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.84,0:01:42.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}感觉好像能上天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.59,0:01:45.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.59,0:01:45.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.01,0:01:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 我是为了改变我自己才成为学生指导教师的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.52,0:01:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要严管学生们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.03,0:02:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊！这么突然是怎么回事啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.37,0:02:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不可以 胆怯是不可以的！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.74,0:02:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.04,0:02:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.00,0:02:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思 那个啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.38,0:02:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,边走边吃东西举止有点不端庄 什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.47,0:02:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失敬！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.47,0:02:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为早晨没有吃饭 肚子这家伙不停的在嘶叫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.43,0:02:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在立刻取下来 真是失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.35,0:02:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思 可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.60,0:02:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能够明白的话 那就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.94,0:02:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 说了的话还是能够理解我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.86,0:02:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.20,0:02:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何等的美味啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.50,0:03:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么美味啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.88,0:03:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走廊里喊什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.38,0:03:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你稍微考虑一下风纪会怎么样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.80,0:03:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个 那个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.67,0:03:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱过来是不…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.51,0:03:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美里 走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.80,0:03:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹原 午休的时候有话要跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.22,0:03:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在教室待着哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.86,0:03:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实 风纪可能很乱啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.98,0:03:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失敬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.52,0:03:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立花美里也没有恶意的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.98,0:03:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.07,0:03:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好的 不好意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.16,0:03:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.20,0:03:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.99,0:03:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脖子上带的很多花边的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.04,0:03:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这个么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.60,0:03:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 觉得很可爱什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.79,0:03:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们每天过的日常生活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.23,0:03:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定实际上是奇迹的连续
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.31,0:04:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说 可能就是那么一回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.19,0:04:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 所以说那个很多花边的东西是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.45,0:04:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳过这个问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.83,0:04:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你 有机会再讲给你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.85,0:04:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.89,0:04:49.86,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\pos(100,360)\bord5\blur20}学\N生\N指\N导
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.56,0:04:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思 中之条同学
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.57,0:04:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.32,0:04:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没什么 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.57,0:05:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在学校梳这个发型 有点那个啊 什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.04,0:05:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 就是有点 就是有点 什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.00,0:05:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}…不出来啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.24,0:05:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 有点没有听清 可以再说一遍么…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.30,0:05:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}旁边的部分
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.63,0:05:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁边的部分长不出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.47,0:05:29.98,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\fad(520,520)\pos(1180,360)\bord5\blur20}围\N棋\N足\N球\N部\N1
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.47,0:05:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不·倒·翁·公·公——
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.47,0:05:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}译注：“不倒翁公公倒了”是一种小孩的游戏，玩法与国内的\N“红灯绿灯小白灯”、“红绿灯”“木头人”（各地区不同的叫法）等很像。
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.65,0:05:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.44,0:05:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 都回去了

Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.78,0:05:40.74,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs27\pos(725,194)}请\N向\N前\N一\N千\N步
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.58,0:05:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.93,0:05:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是青梅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.42,0:05:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想着今年在家做些梅干吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.25,0:05:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅干 好酸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.46,0:05:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅子对身体有益哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.38,0:06:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且放到饭团里面 饭就不会坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.89,0:06:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\c&H6A50D7&\shad0\pos(556,371)}薯\N片
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.06,0:06:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.64,0:06:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.18,0:06:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士还什么都没有说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.85,0:06:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜点不是之前刚买了好多么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.23,0:06:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先把那些吃了 吃光了再来买
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.19,0:06:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs27\bord0\shad0\c&H596C5D&\pos(131,259)}大促销\N随意挑选\N3个\N{\fs36\c&H8D94D5&}350元{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.82,0:06:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.03,0:06:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以哦 今天还有那位猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.66,0:06:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.24,0:06:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.56,0:06:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 说好了还要给阪本先生买饭的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.66,0:06:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜点的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.84,0:06:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.67,0:06:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.46,0:06:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么可以为您效劳的么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.80,0:06:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.55,0:06:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是雪人 今天刚进货的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.56,0:06:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的话请选购
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.06,0:06:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜点？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.40,0:06:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似刨冰之类的东西吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.53,0:06:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好凉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.16,0:07:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好便宜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.16,0:07:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要买么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.58,0:07:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 只是看看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.25,0:07:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是雪人么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.66,0:07:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.75,0:07:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.18,0:07:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.13,0:07:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不买那个的话就让给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.81,0:07:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我买了！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.43,0:07:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明名乃可以买名乃的 却说博士不可以买博士的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.56,0:07:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 都说了这个是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.57,0:07:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么名乃可以买名乃的 所以博士也可以买博士的！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.49,0:07:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}想要想要 想要嘛 想要…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.24,0:07:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 只能买一个哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.03,0:07:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.37,0:07:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢名乃了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.67,0:08:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就买那种东西了么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.34,0:08:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 又可爱 凉凉的又很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.26,0:08:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 做好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.99,0:08:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好——
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.19,0:08:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 再来些…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.73,0:08:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.57,0:08:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.24,0:08:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我的饭在哪里了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.25,0:08:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刨冰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.33,0:08:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种饭 卡哧卡哧的 什么的

Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.51,0:08:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先出石头 接下来是布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.06,0:08:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石剪布可不带哟 石头剪子布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.94,0:09:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝上走了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.03,0:09:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发条！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.33,0:09:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\move(680,185,221,185)\c&HD4E6D2&}期中考试
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.99,0:10:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO NO
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.29,0:10:45.92,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\pos(1250,285)}募\N集\N爵\N士\N空\N手\N道\N!!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.28,0:10:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 考试结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.67,0:10:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天——呀！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.60,0:11:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是假发
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.27,0:11:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.91,0:11:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想别人在追求什么的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.15,0:11:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为“别人”太多了 所以想不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.25,0:11:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想自己在追求什么的话 好像行得通不是么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.54,0:11:19.66,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\frz32.361\c&H122E53&\pos(529,342)}站前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.66,0:11:19.79,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\frz32.361\c&H122E53&\pos(642,431)}站前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.79,0:11:19.91,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\frz32.361\c&H122E53&\pos(694,471)}站前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.91,0:11:20.37,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\frz32.361\c&H122E53&\pos(731,514)}站前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.17,0:11:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的只有向某处的神明祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.96,0:11:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.42,0:11:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来某处的神明 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.68,0:11:43.81,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\fad(520,520)\pos(1180,360)\bord5\blur20}围\N棋\N足\N球\N部\N2
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.68,0:11:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不·倒·翁·公·公——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.11,0:11:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.61,0:11:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不罢手么…？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.54,0:12:05.04,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&\pos(1080,360)}鹦\N鹉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.04,0:12:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又被罚站了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.86,0:12:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个身体也 相当 适应了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.76,0:12:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是看着嘴里面就好多口水了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.16,0:12:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.46,0:12:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 阪本先生 这是梅干哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.08,0:12:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以哦 还没做好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.62,0:12:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这个跟阪本玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.71,0:12:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 逗猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.00,0:12:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本 阪本
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.67,0:12:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 小鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.74,0:12:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我加上“先生”哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.09,0:12:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对哦 抱歉 阪本
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.89,0:13:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你耍我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.60,0:13:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 一不小心… 对不起啊 阪本
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.39,0:13:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫故意的吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.57,0:13:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我去买东西了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.03,0:13:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.53,0:13:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这帮人真是没教养啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.04,0:13:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 阪本 不是故意的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.87,0:13:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了 不是阪本！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.46,0:13:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 阪本 给你口香糖
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.05,0:13:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要让我说多少遍啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.71,0:13:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说你啊 哪有给猫口香糖的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.42,0:13:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢货 啊啊啊……
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.56,0:13:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我差不多点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.10,0:13:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.31,0:13:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 之前我也说过了 我比你们年长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.36,0:13:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,称呼年长的人要好好 加上“先生”  那个
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.74,0:13:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.16,0:14:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之就是 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.99,0:14:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说那个啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.54,0:14:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 那个… 要说那个的话啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.67,0:14:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.58,0:14:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去尿尿可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.25,0:14:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦 快去吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.42,0:14:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尿尿哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.55,0:14:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.27,0:14:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如所见
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.79,0:14:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个家里面果然只住着那两个小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.44,0:14:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.48,0:14:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才这么没有教养
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.50,0:14:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.01,0:14:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个家里面我就是最年长的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.29,0:14:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.78,0:14:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然麻烦 还是我来做他们的家长吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.68,0:14:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我也是被一家不得了的捡去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.03,0:15:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 超开心啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.59,0:15:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本 你在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.81,0:15:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.69,0:15:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是被知道我在玩橡皮什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.85,0:15:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为家长的威严就…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.42,0:15:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威严就…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.31,0:15:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威严就……
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.49,0:15:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像 有点睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.07,0:15:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪睡得真是多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.45,0:15:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 就是那么回事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.79,0:15:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么那么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.00,0:15:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那么回事 跟你说了这么多就是那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.29,0:15:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先 要从尊敬年长的人 开始 对吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.71,0:15:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 超开心——
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.89,0:15:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本 再来一次 再来一次
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.69,0:15:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本 阪本啊 快点快点 阪本啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.52,0:15:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}不是 不对 刚才那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.43,0:15:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}我说 我不是说过了嘛 给我加上“先生”
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.69,0:15:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.60,0:15:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全垒打！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.22,0:16:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈？！

Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.03,0:16:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…倒翁公公 倒…了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.45,0:16:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不倒…翁公公…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.83,0:17:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣又装了一个这么难懂的傻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.50,0:17:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法 总之先吐槽了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.80,0:17:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣啊 那不是ON THE BOOK么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.05,0:17:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 再也不要吐这个槽了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.35,0:17:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这么好得吐了槽的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.44,0:17:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我装傻的部分就会被忽视的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.65,0:17:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 就是那个啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.24,0:17:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了不小心就会蹦出英语的年龄了 什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.08,0:17:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个“ON THE BOOK”
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.42,0:17:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是本来的样子还是在装傻很难懂哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.04,0:17:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 怎么说呢 反过来吐槽 什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.08,0:17:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难懂…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.79,0:17:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在认真地说么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.05,0:17:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是因为是小佑…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.14,0:17:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是小佑 所以我以为你会懂我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.83,0:18:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 头疼了啊 没想到你这么看我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.40,0:18:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是被信任了还是很高兴的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.65,0:18:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信任？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.20,0:18:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.07,0:18:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以信任没信任什么的这些话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.04,0:18:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能算了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.55,0:18:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挚友之间 是无需多言的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.39,0:18:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.39,0:18:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.46,0:18:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是挚友 多说说话不也可以嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.14,0:18:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.90,0:18:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太粘我的话 我很困扰的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.11,0:18:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.36,0:18:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.57,0:18:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.66,0:18:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说这种话的话 对小佑你…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.33,0:18:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对小佑你…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.50,0:19:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会变得 更加喜欢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.09,0:19:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.72,0:19:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是很好么 变得喜欢了 是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.14,0:19:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挚友 哟 挚友！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.94,0:19:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.44,0:19:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是异性
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.44,0:19:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却把你看作是异性…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.41,0:19:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 不能很好的表达出来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.92,0:19:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什 什…么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.03,0:19:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就觉得 今天 有点不对劲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.73,0:19:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 因为
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.50,0:19:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时她也没这么多话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.17,0:19:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有说离着太近的话会怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.93,0:19:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部 都是为了说这些话么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.79,0:20:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 从什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.23,0:20:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从什么时候 开始那样…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.81,0:20:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我 我 我说 麻 麻 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.18,0:20:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎 怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.53,0:20:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情 不是很好 之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.45,0:20:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事还是太早了 之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.37,0:20:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是高中生 之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.49,0:20:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我是在装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.28,0:20:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Super Ultra Bullet Wonderful 难以理解啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.28,0:20:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}译注：此处捏森林好小子（燃える！お兄さん）中洛基的招式—\N—Super Ultra Bullet Wonderful Punch 该动画中文配音版中译成超级金刚无敌拳
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.92,0:20:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 奇怪的演技什么的少来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.38,0:20:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都相信了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.10,0:20:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.29,0:20:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为 因为是小佑 脑子转得很快所以会明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.36,0:20:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 还是稍微明白了一些的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.32,0:20:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.85,0:20:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不是 骗你什么的 怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.90,0:20:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子“哔”的开始工作什么的 回转什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.83,0:20:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 仔细想想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.49,0:21:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你说的本身就很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.33,0:21:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才 你不是说你相信了么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.60,0:21:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最讨厌说谎了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.10,0:21:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.38,0:21:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那也是装傻…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.18,0:21:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经什么都察觉不到了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.47,0:21:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有察觉到么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.34,0:21:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实还有一处
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.02,0:21:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不知道啊 是哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.02,0:21:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑脑子转得很快 的那个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.36,0:21:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该吐槽“根本不快”的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.28,0:21:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.17,0:21:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 只有那个地方非常 容易懂哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.81,0:22:07.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}朝起きて　歯を磨いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.81,0:22:07.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}早晨睡醒后 起床刷牙来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.98,0:22:10.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あっという間　午後10時
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.98,0:22:10.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}不知不觉间 已到晚十点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.11,0:22:14.03,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　たくさん　笑ったなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.11,0:22:14.03,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天也遇到 很多欢乐事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.19,0:22:16.78,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}たくさん　ときめいたなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.19,0:22:16.78,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}也有非常多 刺激与紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.32,0:22:20.24,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}友達と　バカみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.32,0:22:20.24,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}和闺中密友 像笨蛋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.41,0:22:23.16,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}騒いでる　時にも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.41,0:22:23.16,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}大声吵又闹 偶尔会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.49,0:22:26.50,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}チラチラって　目が合う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.49,0:22:26.50,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶尔瞥向你 四目便相接
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.62,0:22:29.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}…偶然、だよね。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.62,0:22:29.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}这也不过是 偶然事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.42,0:22:32.67,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋なんて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.42,0:22:32.67,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋什么的难以说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.88,0:22:35.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キャラじゃないんだもんっ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.88,0:22:35.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}因为我不是这样的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.01,0:22:41.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ねえ　あしたも会えるよね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.01,0:22:41.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}呐 我们明天 也会相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.09,0:22:44.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}まぶたを　閉じると
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.09,0:22:44.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}将我的双眼 合上了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.18,0:22:48.14,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キラキラ　キミだらけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.18,0:22:48.14,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}脑海中只有 亮晶晶的你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.31,0:22:51.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　楽しかったね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.31,0:22:51.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天的我也 开心又愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.60,0:22:55.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あー　恋　してんだなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.60,0:22:55.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}啊 陷入恋爱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.91,0:23:03.87,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}うれしいな　うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.91,0:23:03.87,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}真的好开心 真的好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.03,0:23:06.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}はじめまして　こいごころ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.03,0:23:06.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}第一次见面 我的爱慕心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.16,0:23:10.04,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あした　まだ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.16,0:23:10.04,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}到明天的话 我们又见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.29,0:23:12.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.29,0:23:12.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.42,0:23:17.46,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ゆめで　すぐ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.42,0:23:17.46,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}在梦中很快 我们会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.09,0:23:23.64,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.09,0:23:23.64,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.93,0:23:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经有40年历史了哦 这个社区
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.23,0:23:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用汉字写一个“团地妻”试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.23,0:23:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}译注：团地 相当于国内的社区 团地妻即指社区主妇\N至于为什么有特别的魅力 搜索一下 你就懂了= =
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.77,0:23:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 马上就会有一种特别的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.56,0:23:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话的日常是 第五话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.44,0:23:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待


