[Script Info]
;   This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
;   For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;   go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;   or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;   
;   Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
;   http://www.anime-fansubs.org
;   
;   For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
;   or email gabest@freemail.hu
;   
;   Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
;   
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-02 12:11:00
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,58,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,53,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1
[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.53,0:00:08.57,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(650,800)\pos(1130,280)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}干\N劲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.82,0:00:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.61,0:00:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干劲各种提不起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.95,0:00:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.37,0:00:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是高中生哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.62,0:00:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是新学期了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.41,0:00:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干劲什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.45,0:00:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始做的话自然就提起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.08,0:00:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是连提起干劲的热情都没有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.75,0:00:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要提起对干劲的热情的话该怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.76,0:00:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对干劲的热情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.72,0:00:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 总之一定要干起来！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.18,0:00:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.39,0:00:41.36,XD,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1195,544)}{\1a&HFF\t(0,270,1\1a&H00)}真\N{\1a&HFF\t(270,540,1\1a&H00)}是\N{\1a&HFF\t(540,810,1\1a&H00)}个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.35,0:00:41.36,XD,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(87,482)}{\1a&HFF\t(0,200,1\1a&H00)}单\N{\1a&HFF\t(200,400,1\1a&H00)}纯\N{\1a&HFF\t(400,600,1\1a&H00)}的\N{\1a&HFF\t(600,800,1\1a&H00)}笨\N{\1a&HFF\t(800,1000,1\1a&H00)}蛋\N{\1a&HFF\t(1000,1200,1\1a&H00)}啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.03,0:00:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 差不多请起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.21,0:01:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.75,0:01:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.55,0:01:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的早饭是烤鱼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.97,0:01:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 我想要蛋包饭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.80,0:01:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天不是吃了么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.10,0:01:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鱼里面有很多营养的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.10,0:01:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.64,0:01:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜不喜欢的东西都要吃才能长大
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.15,0:01:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那是重要的早饭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.16,0:01:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.58,0:01:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这绝对不是机器人什么的东西的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.00,0:01:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.50,0:01:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 跑掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.63,0:01:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.13,0:01:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.72,0:01:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定 那只猫也不容易啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.14,0:02:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 要撞上了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.20,0:03:57.11,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,0)\fs60\pos(620,680)}小木偶人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.61,0:03:59.53,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,0)\fs60\pos(620,680)}红牛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:02.79,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,0)\fs60\pos(620,680)}鲑鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.41,0:04:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 selamat pagi
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.41,0:04:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}译注：印尼语早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.25,0:04:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小佑 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.59,0:04:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊 忘带学生证了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.38,0:04:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 不吐selamat pagi的槽么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.30,0:04:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望不会被高年级同学叫出去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.26,0:04:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种时候 说我是高三的 不就可以了么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.14,0:04:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也解决不了问题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.48,0:04:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 打雷了么 明明天还很晴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.32,0:04:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定突然就下起来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.40,0:04:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷阵雨啊 冰雹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.78,0:04:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上掉 小木偶人了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.91,0:04:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 没关系哦 小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.58,0:04:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟然是小木偶人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.25,0:04:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓死我了 从哪里掉下来的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.25,0:04:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.33,0:04:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 人生中被小木偶人砸着的机会也不多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.01,0:04:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种人 非常稀少的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.30,0:05:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是没有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.80,0:05:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定反而是运气好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.72,0:05:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不好…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.81,0:05:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.40,0:05:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟然是红牛哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.86,0:05:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红牛…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.44,0:05:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 不是运气不好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.78,0:05:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么考虑的话就可以哦 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.36,0:05:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好砸着我的都不是鲜食品
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.16,0:05:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么考虑的话就是不幸中的万幸了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.09,0:05:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲑鱼啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.60,0:05:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.64,0:05:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.57,0:05:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.78,0:05:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,selamat pagi
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.57,0:06:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.90,0:06:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 你在读什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.11,0:06:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于房地产的杂志
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.03,0:06:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 麻衣你要搬家么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.95,0:06:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.04,0:06:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 跳过selamat pagi吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.00,0:06:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法 这个词就当做今天的摇篮曲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.05,0:06:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.47,0:06:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,selamat malam
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.47,0:06:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}译注：印尼语晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.18,0:06:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 应该是selamat pagi吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.27,0:06:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 什么语？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.77,0:06:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班会要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.24,0:06:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 今天早晨来到学校
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.74,0:06:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现鞋箱里面有个这个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.32,0:06:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁放进去的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.58,0:06:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个 要是有谁知道什么的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.33,0:06:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请告诉我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.13,0:07:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 这能是谁干的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.76,0:07:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶作剧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.34,0:07:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是喜欢老师的学生什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.76,0:07:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话是不会放弥勒菩萨的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.26,0:07:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 但是那种对自己配不上的人憧憬的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.31,0:07:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是不能理解的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.44,0:07:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 就像那个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.90,0:07:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像美绪对笹原前辈的心情那样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.86,0:07:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你个笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.28,0:07:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里 是哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.21,0:07:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须得回去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.55,0:07:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士也肯定在担心我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.88,0:07:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且炭炉就那么开着很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.82,0:08:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 下不去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.07,0:08:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 筷子没了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.07,0:08:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖鞋也没了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.99,0:08:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.83,0:08:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃啊 手也没了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.96,0:08:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器人的事要暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.42,0:08:25.51,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx95\pos(1095,150)}雪\N飘
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.42,0:08:25.51,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnArial\fs27\pos(1173,150)}flsnow
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.34,0:08:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.80,0:08:31.51,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(550,0)\frz270\pos(233,358)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}Wonderful
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.03,0:08:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.91,0:08:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 再不快点吃的话就要开始第五堂课了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.91,0:08:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 你不是喜欢吃香肠么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.71,0:09:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便当要在最后才吃最好吃的东西 这是最基本的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.75,0:09:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 大喊着“好吃”结束这顿饭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.47,0:09:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 现在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.34,0:09:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要开吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.72,0:09:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿过去啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.51,0:09:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没完呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.52,0:10:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.57,0:10:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没完呢啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.44,0:10:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.15,0:10:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.70,0:10:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.25,0:10:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全上垒！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.75,0:10:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？ 出局了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.46,0:10:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼哼 讨厌啊美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.76,0:10:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三秒规则哦 三秒规则
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.01,0:10:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不是 我总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.47,0:10:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说也是出局了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.69,0:10:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.31,0:10:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑真是 笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.65,0:10:53.65,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx95\pos(105,150)}雪\N飘
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.65,0:10:53.65,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnArial\fs27\pos(183,150)}flsnow
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.07,0:11:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先出石头 接下来是布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.58,0:11:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使出力量 石头剪刀布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.09,0:11:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.47,0:11:23.52,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx95\pos(105,150)}雪\N飘
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.47,0:11:23.52,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnArial\fs27\pos(183,150)}flsnow
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.56,0:11:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 同学们 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.39,0:11:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年之计在于春
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.57,0:11:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在还挺冷的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.49,0:11:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我比大家更冷一些呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.99,0:11:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之大家千万不要得感冒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.79,0:11:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好哦 这是跟校长的约定哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.08,0:11:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家要是不听我的话的话校长我就…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.55,0:11:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去别的学校当校长了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.72,0:12:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.39,0:12:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么 说话的话会被训哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.10,0:12:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊 校长先生没注意到自己的笑话太老了么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.69,0:12:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑话每次都没被接受这个事实
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.03,0:12:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得本人应该是最清楚不过的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.45,0:12:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 怎么回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.66,0:12:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是想让现代那些有很多摩擦的年轻人们看看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.62,0:12:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那明知笑话不被接受但反过来更加努力的姿态么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.17,0:12:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.84,0:12:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个校长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.13,0:12:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是技艺高超啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.80,0:12:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣！？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.26,0:12:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.43,0:12:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 那种老掉牙的笑话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.56,0:12:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.93,0:12:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且麻衣笑成这样是我第一次见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.56,0:12:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 这里就先这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.03,0:12:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.90,0:12:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.70,0:13:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.91,0:13:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一种现在在这说出来的话就会失去所有的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.49,0:13:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.79,0:13:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.01,0:13:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是 在她发现之前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.93,0:13:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别拿下来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.47,0:13:26.97,XD,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz10.081\c&H31302E&\pos(1029,218)}{\1a&HFF\t(0,150,1\1a&H00)}乌\N{\1a&HFF\t(150,300,1\1a&H00)}贼\N{\1a&HFF\t(300,450,1\1a&H00)}触\N{\1a&HFF\t(450,600,1\1a&H00)}手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.40,0:13:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么接下来由樱井老师发言对学生指导
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.61,0:13:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱井老师 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.07,0:13:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 樱井老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.41,0:13:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.03,0:13:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我是学生指导教师樱井
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.25,0:13:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.21,0:13:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人这么多果然还是会紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.30,0:14:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.17,0:14:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到什么时候也不会接近我理想中的教师的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.59,0:14:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得该出手时就出手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.35,0:14:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.64,0:14:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近校园里总能看见山羊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.56,0:14:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要往学校里带山羊了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.94,0:14:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山羊 山羊哪里不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.24,0:14:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐着山羊上学放学的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.24,0:14:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有违反校规吧——
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.87,0:14:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.00,0:14:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 那是笹原学长吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.42,0:14:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 是么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.26,0:14:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可 可以带山羊来！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.64,0:14:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驳回哦 驳回！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.31,0:14:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对驳回哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.89,0:14:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山羊什么的怎么可以带来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.40,0:14:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽这么说 立花美里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.15,0:15:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我非得慌慌张张的步行来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.94,0:15:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说 身为笹原家的长子…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.91,0:15:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹原家的长子个屁啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.99,0:15:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们家就是户普通的农家吧！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.41,0:15:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.70,0:15:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为长子说自己是长子有什么错误么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.62,0:15:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？笹原君家原来是农家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.79,0:15:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有种被骗了的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.42,0:15:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来那头在停自行车的地方的山羊是笹原先辈的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.97,0:15:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐着白羊的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.47,0:15:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹原学长来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.93,0:15:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迎接我…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.98,0:15:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}啊 Happy New Year！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.40,0:15:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}Me… Me too
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.86,0:15:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 美绪！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.70,0:15:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 边骑自行车边用手机是非常危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.00,0:16:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家千万不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.59,0:16:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 最后
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.46,0:16:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早晨 有人在我的鞋箱里面放了一个弥勒菩萨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.26,0:16:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做这种恶作剧 我觉得很不好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.39,0:16:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 借过一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.64,0:16:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥勒菩萨？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.56,0:16:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 不要突然停下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.98,0:16:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这边 可能是既视感吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.61,0:16:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是谁干的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.07,0:16:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会生气的 请把手举起来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.57,0:16:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不站出来的话 今天就这么一直站着早会了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.12,0:16:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊 你给我出去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.80,0:16:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 因为听说樱井老师过生日了所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.84,0:16:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.81,0:16:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥勒菩萨不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.94,0:17:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是出于好心而送的生日礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.15,0:17:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但弥勒菩萨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.57,0:17:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.65,0:17:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校长
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.41,0:17:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天的早会就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.08,0:17:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校长 至今以来非常感谢您
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.58,0:17:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教头！？

Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.92,0:17:26.92,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20\shad1\4c&HFFFFFF&\pos(643,421)}用力按下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.67,0:17:29.30,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(700,500)\pos(60,358)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}按\N钮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.30,0:17:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个消防栓的按钮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.13,0:17:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一股让人很想按下去的魔力哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.59,0:17:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.10,0:17:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按下去试试呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.35,0:17:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前按下去了也没出什么声
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.10,0:17:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 真的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.73,0:17:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,着火了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.94,0:17:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧！？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.81,0:17:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么办啊 要跑么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.82,0:17:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同学们 总之赶紧去操场
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.86,0:17:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫 干嘛从后面推我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.32,0:17:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你丫在推我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.36,0:17:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫说什么呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.07,0:17:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说为什么你丫一直那么令人火大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.41,0:17:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吵了啊 可能要死了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.00,0:17:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.00,0:18:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会再接着吵
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.25,0:18:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赫维提卡标准
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.25,0:18:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}译注:Helvetica是一种广泛使用的西文字体\N 是瑞士图形设计师马克斯?米耶丁格（Max Miedinger）于1957年设计的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.42,0:18:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.84,0:18:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 KY是什么东西啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.47,0:18:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.18,0:18:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 KY是什么意思啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.39,0:18:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 请告诉我一些关于KY的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.10,0:18:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.48,0:18:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队长 KY是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.86,0:18:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是KY哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.86,0:18:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}译注：KY是撷取自日语的“{\fs32\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7}空気が読めない{\r}{\fs36\an8}（发音kuuki ga yomenai 直译为‘不会读取气氛’）”的首字母\N意思是没眼色、不会按照当时的气氛和对方的脸色做出合适的反应
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.20,0:18:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二年P班 笹原幸治郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.87,0:18:43.71,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&\pos(1195,357)}要\N事\N和\N事\N情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.20,0:18:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧急 请到办公室富冈老师那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.50,0:18:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是 没有违反校规啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.92,0:18:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有人会带山羊来吧 山羊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.26,0:18:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能换一个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.01,0:18:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不喜欢徒步的话自行车也可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.51,0:18:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不是山羊的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.47,0:18:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.35,0:19:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是富冈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.60,0:19:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富冈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.56,0:19:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我加上老师
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.43,0:19:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.73,0:19:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以不叫它山羊 叫它笹原幸治郎么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.24,0:19:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是在说山羊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.54,0:19:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫东云名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.79,0:19:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和我住在一起的博士造出来的机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.96,0:19:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士好像在做什么研究 整天都呆在家里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.55,0:19:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天都在帮助她中度过
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.89,0:19:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 牛奶热好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.15,0:19:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有优秀的机能 但还是会有痛觉的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.15,0:19:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.44,0:19:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博 博士 小脚趾 小脚趾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.28,0:20:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小 小 小脚趾 趾 趾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.33,0:20:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之这样就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.38,0:20:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有优秀的机能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.42,0:20:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小脚指好像可以拿下来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.18,0:20:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 这个发条是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.89,0:20:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没有拧过么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.23,0:20:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是 虽然偶尔会转
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.73,0:20:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是要这么做的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.36,0:20:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.07,0:20:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 优秀的机能很多
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.74,0:20:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 很好玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.83,0:20:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 发条 只是为了这个么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.46,0:20:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.08,0:20:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 发条 只是为了这个么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.05,0:20:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.17,0:20:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我拿下来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.38,0:20:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.26,0:20:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发条什么的很可爱嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.97,0:21:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的请给我拿下来！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.09,0:21:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 明明很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.89,0:21:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望能更普通一点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.06,0:21:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能像普通人那样坐在椅子上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.81,0:21:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在床上翻来翻去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.23,0:21:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 连学校也去不了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.53,0:21:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干脆不是人形机器人就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.95,0:21:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.29,0:21:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假的 那是骗你的哟 骗你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.33,0:21:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的啊 博士啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.17,0:21:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那给我拿来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.05,0:21:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去把芥川奖拿回来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.01,0:21:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.30,0:21:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去拿去拿…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.38,0:21:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样的每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.68,0:21:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里 是哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.99,0:23:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好 我是名乃的大脚趾
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.62,0:23:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,容量是1GB
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.54,0:23:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点遗憾呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.67,0:23:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话的日常是 第二话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.50,0:23:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.71,0:22:08.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}朝起きて　歯を磨いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.88,0:22:11.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あっという間　午後10時
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.01,0:22:14.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　たくさん　笑ったなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.09,0:22:17.68,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}たくさん　ときめいたなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.22,0:22:21.14,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}友達と　バカみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.31,0:22:24.06,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}騒いでる　時にも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.39,0:22:27.40,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}チラチラって　目が合う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.52,0:22:30.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}…偶然、だよね。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.32,0:22:33.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋なんて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.78,0:22:36.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キャラじゃないんだもんっ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.91,0:22:42.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ねえ　あしたも会えるよね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.99,0:22:45.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}まぶたを　閉じると
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.08,0:22:49.04,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キラキラ　キミだらけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.21,0:22:52.34,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　楽しかったね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.50,0:22:56.76,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あー　恋　してんだなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.81,0:23:04.77,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}うれしいな　うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.93,0:23:07.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}はじめまして　こいごころ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.06,0:23:10.94,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あした　まだ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.19,0:23:13.61,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.32,0:23:18.36,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ゆめで　すぐ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.99,0:23:24.54,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.71,0:22:08.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}早晨睡醒后 起床刷牙来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.88,0:22:11.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}不知不觉间 已到晚十点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.01,0:22:14.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天也遇到 很多欢乐事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.09,0:22:17.68,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}也有非常多 刺激与紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.22,0:22:21.14,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}和闺中密友 像笨蛋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.31,0:22:24.06,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}大声吵又闹 偶尔会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.39,0:22:27.40,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶尔瞥向你 四目便相接
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.52,0:22:30.11,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}这也不过是 偶然事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.32,0:22:33.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋什么的难以说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.78,0:22:36.74,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}因为我不是这样的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.91,0:22:42.74,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}呐 我们明天 也会相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.99,0:22:45.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}将我的双眼 合上了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.08,0:22:49.04,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}脑海中只有 亮晶晶的你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.21,0:22:52.34,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天的我也 开心又愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.50,0:22:56.76,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}啊 陷入恋爱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.81,0:23:04.77,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}真的好开心 真的好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.93,0:23:07.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}第一次见面 我的爱慕心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.06,0:23:10.94,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}到明天的话 我们又见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.19,0:23:13.61,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.32,0:23:18.36,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}在梦中很快 我们会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.99,0:23:24.54,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.99,0:02:35.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}たった今　初めて気づいた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.66,0:02:38.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋に落ちたのだなー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.33,0:02:40.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h キミ☆　キミ☆　キミ☆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.87,0:02:42.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意識せざるをえません！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.83,0:02:45.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}なんか　いつもと違う
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.37,0:02:44.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.46,0:02:48.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}キミと　ぎこちない会話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.92,0:02:46.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.13,0:02:50.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}まさか　いや　片思い
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.59,0:02:49.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両思い
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.92,0:02:53.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やばい！　視線合っちゃった！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.34,0:02:56.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}なになに！？このドキドキ！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.55,0:03:02.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路　ぐっちゃぐちゃ　混線…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.31,0:03:08.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}こんなこと　初めてだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.98,0:03:14.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}熱でもあるのかなー
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.65,0:03:17.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急転直下　いらっしゃた　恋心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.53,0:03:20.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっちゅうま　顔　発火で　まっかっか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.12,0:03:22.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}バ·バ…バカな！？　手が震えるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.79,0:03:25.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが　俗に言う　「恋」　なの！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.54,0:03:28.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}やややっちゃった　会話　噛みまくり
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.12,0:03:30.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気まずい沈黙　マミムメモ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.79,0:03:33.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}キミの　気持ち　知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.38,0:03:31.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キミの
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.46,0:03:36.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.34,0:03:39.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！　{\r}いつもの通学路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.26,0:03:42.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}ピカピカ光る　{\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.64,0:03:45.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}空も飛べそうさ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.39,0:03:48.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.99,0:02:35.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}就在刚刚 才第一次注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.66,0:02:38.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陷入恋情了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.33,0:02:40.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h 是你☆  是你☆  是你☆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.87,0:02:42.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全部都是你！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.83,0:02:45.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}总觉得 和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.37,0:02:44.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.46,0:02:48.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}我与你 慌慌张张的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.92,0:02:46.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.13,0:02:50.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}难道说 不对 单相思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.59,0:02:49.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.92,0:02:53.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！ 跟他的眼睛对上了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.34,0:02:56.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}什么什么！？心里小鹿乱撞！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.55,0:03:02.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路 黏黏糊糊乱糟糟 串线…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.31,0:03:08.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这样的事情 第一次遇到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.98,0:03:14.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}是不是患上感冒了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.65,0:03:17.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急转直下 悄无声息来的 春心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.53,0:03:20.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一会的时间 脸 像着火 通红通红的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.12,0:03:22.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}笨·笨…笨蛋吗！？ 手正在发抖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.79,0:03:25.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 俗话说的 “爱” 的啦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.54,0:03:28.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}要要要要坏菜了啊 对话 咬到舌头了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.12,0:03:30.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难为情的沉默 āōēīū
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.79,0:03:33.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}想知道 你现在 心里所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.38,0:03:31.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.46,0:03:36.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.34,0:03:39.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！ {\r}好像上学走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.26,0:03:42.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}亮闪闪的发光 {\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.64,0:03:45.14,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}感觉好像能上天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.39,0:03:48.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花


