[Script Info]
;  This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
;  For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;  go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;  or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;  
;  Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
;  http://www.anime-fansubs.org
;  
;  For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
;  or email gabest@freemail.hu
;  
;  Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
;  
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-03 12:50:36
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,58,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,53,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1
Style: title-B,方正黑体_GBK,48,&H000F0F0F,&H000000D5,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,96,100,8,0.00,1,0,2,2,15,15,70,134
[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.79,0:00:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.86,0:00:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名～乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.68,0:00:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.19,0:00:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯～？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.62,0:00:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.87,0:00:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯～？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.87,0:00:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.18,0:00:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.54,0:00:31.15,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)\pos(750,360)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}的\N喵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.51,0:00:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.05,0:00:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看 快看
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.41,0:00:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.65,0:00:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.18,0:00:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本也快看 快看
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.34,0:00:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.24,0:00:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.31,0:00:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.26,0:00:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样子可能
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.37,0:00:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当萌啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.53,0:00:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.25,0:00:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.80,0:01:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.00,0:01:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好萌
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.87,0:01:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.28,0:01:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好萌！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.40,0:01:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.89,0:01:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好萌！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.25,0:01:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵喵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.55,0:01:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}好萌！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.62,0:01:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好萌！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.78,0:01:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是博士喵喵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.44,0:01:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云家 今天也很和谐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.55,0:01:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}好萌！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.70,0:02:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球为什么是圆的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.45,0:03:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火箭为什么能飞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.58,0:03:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么磁铁能互相吸引呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.84,0:03:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界上的东西 全部都能用科学证明
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.34,0:03:19.68,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(867,553)}坟\N墓
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.87,0:03:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们讨论的死后的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.66,0:03:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幽灵、鬼故事之类的灵异现象
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.45,0:03:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种令人想睡觉的东西怎么可能有！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.44,0:03:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 不可以有的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.77,0:03:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.33,0:03:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通灵者 根本不能信！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.33,0:03:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs27\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7}イタコ{\r\fs36}：日本东北一种能招魂的巫女，多弱视；青森县的恐山夏季举行的游客\N现场聆听通灵者招魂的恐山大祭很出名；通灵王中的恐山安娜就是一名{\fs30\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7}イタコ{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.83,0:03:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我利用休息日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.68,0:03:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花了八小时踏上了恐山的土地
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.87,0:03:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随着越来越接近山顶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.92,0:03:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心中的跃动也愈加强烈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.76,0:03:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有通灵者么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.12,0:03:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的话在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.30,0:03:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人住在这种地方么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.40,0:03:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.71,0:03:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.56,0:04:00.77,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1075,463)}通\N灵\N者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.11,0:04:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.99,0:04:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧让她召唤一次试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.99,0:04:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.30,0:04:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.53,0:04:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.42,0:04:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,召唤一下石碱吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.16,0:04:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.34,0:04:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是石碱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.50,0:04:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 啊 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.92,0:04:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦克测试 麦克测试 滋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.27,0:04:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麦克测试 测试 测试 滋 滋滋滋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.46,0:04:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 这种完全没有办法的感觉…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.76,0:04:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 真有叫“石碱”的这么个人…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.98,0:04:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,测试 测试 测试 滋 滋 嘘 嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.32,0:04:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 哈 石 石 石碱 石碱 石碱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.26,0:04:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是石碱 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.71,0:04:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不能有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.15,0:04:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问些什么的话 肯定会出现一些矛盾的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.98,0:05:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提问
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.40,0:05:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石碱是什么血型的？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.29,0:05:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 谁知道啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.43,0:05:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是叫一些简单的人物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.02,0:05:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.13,0:05:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信长 召唤一下织田信长吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.82,0:05:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饶了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.04,0:05:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,召不召唤之前就拒绝了这…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.83,0:05:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 多少也是上了年纪的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.20,0:05:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有健康状况的原因吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.24,0:05:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能因为这个责怪她
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.76,0:05:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.00,0:05:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.62,0:05:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是无法责怪别人的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.56,0:05:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是明白这一点 不也是一种收获吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.88,0:05:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这位小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.89,0:06:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五千元哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.86,0:06:24.53,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx95\pos(1095,150)}雪\N飘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.86,0:06:24.53,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnArial\fs27\pos(1173,150)}flsnow
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.20,0:06:31.75,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(100,360)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}敲\N不\N倒\N翁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.14,0:06:31.77,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs20\fad(600,600)}敲不倒翁：だるま落とし，在不倒翁下面重叠着几个薄圆柱体\N横向用木槌敲击，首先使不倒翁落地的人获胜。
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.22,0:06:50.15,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}100分
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.74,0:06:55.13,title-B,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(80,245)\fad(600,0)}喷\N\N嚏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.89,0:07:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.08,0:07:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  男生们…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.52,0:07:23.00,title-B,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(40,300)\fad(600,0)}日\N常\N之\N20
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.98,0:07:22.91,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}第二堂课  \NTHE  自习
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.02,0:07:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.58,0:07:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头 剪子 布
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.09,0:07:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对啊 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.35,0:07:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才不是说明过了么！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.00,0:07:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了的话就要敲对方啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.62,0:07:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好狠哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.54,0:07:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好狠的做法哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.07,0:07:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从另一个层面说比敲我更过分哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.47,0:07:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说好了哦 就像刚才说明的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.00,0:07:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输了的话就要防御 赢了的话就要敲对方哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.37,0:07:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\c&H86F8FB&\3c&H000000&\bord2\shad0\b1\frz353.178\pos(1167,185)}猛击
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.30,0:07:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在打你妹啊！ 为毛现在打我！？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.16,0:08:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 刚才不是赢了么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.81,0:08:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是现在 是刚才！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.52,0:08:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那个瞬间哦 就那个瞬间生效哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.01,0:08:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是那种生物哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.25,0:08:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 接下来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.37,0:08:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清零重新开始哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.01,0:08:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头 剪刀 布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.13,0:08:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干劲是零啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.40,0:08:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小丑啊 没想到是个小丑啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.27,0:08:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神上的打击 也是有的啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.37,0:08:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我说 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.71,0:08:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.73,0:08:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 那个 怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.93,0:08:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雕了一个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.17,0:08:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 我还以为重生过来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.74,0:08:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个 放这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.01,0:08:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉 她好像非常高兴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.99,0:09:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 那种东西怎么样都可以啦 继续吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.79,0:09:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 石头 剪刀 布
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.34,0:09:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.60,0:09:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.50,0:09:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是石剪布嘛！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.70,0:09:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\3c&H000000&\bord2\shad0\b1\pos(1201,221)\c&H8CF4F6&}暴击!!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.97,0:09:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么… 这么残忍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.62,0:09:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.54,0:09:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不带的哦 不带的 不带石剪布的！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.79,0:09:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后也不带用佛像敲的！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.92,0:09:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.75,0:09:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先出石头
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.76,0:09:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头 剪刀 布
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.52,0:09:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.48,0:09:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了对了 就是这样哦麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.15,0:09:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊真是的 你这不是也可以嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.86,0:09:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 继续了哦 继续
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.82,0:10:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 先出 石…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.74,0:10:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs33}Gascoigne貌似是人名，加斯科因
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.08,0:10:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GOD IS DEAD
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.29,0:10:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神 死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.59,0:10:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 为什么打我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.71,0:10:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 刚才玩的不是好好的么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.30,0:10:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.39,0:10:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不想玩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.31,0:10:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥勒菩萨 可以借我看看么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.23,0:10:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.78,0:10:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我去图书馆还书去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.95,0:10:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好看家哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.62,0:10:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好~
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.67,0:10:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord0\fs24\c&H525351&\pos(135,594)}雪糕\N果汁\N不能吃\N太多哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.84,0:10:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\fs24\c&HB8ECE0&\pos(1073,623)}鲨鱼型的巧克力\N为什么这么好吃！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.55,0:11:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么名乃的不倒翁只有一个眼睛呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.97,0:11:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啦 博士把眼睛好好画上去的话 说不定会被夸奖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.81,0:11:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定 名乃会说吃好多点心也可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.00,0:11:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有点弄错了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.21,0:11:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是名乃的 怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.72,0:11:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定 会被骂…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.57,0:11:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}博士暂时不许吃点心！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.16,0:11:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 这样 这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.82,0:11:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.03,0:11:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本 怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.24,0:11:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.45,0:12:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊这是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.49,0:12:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么了啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.32,0:12:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 是那小姑娘的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.12,0:12:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 没有眼睛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.80,0:12:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法呐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.67,0:12:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照我说的办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.23,0:12:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.02,0:12:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你保重哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.14,0:12:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.49,0:12:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 阪本先生你要出去么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.66,0:12:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.07,0:12:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要选新借的书 所以回来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.37,0:12:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.04,0:12:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 博士 怎么回事啊 你的肚子！？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.46,0:12:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶嘿 嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿 诶嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.25,0:12:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是“诶嘿嘿”
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.26,0:13:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我要生了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.76,0:13:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对不对不对 不可能这么回事吧！？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.81,0:13:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是要生了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.31,0:13:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}我要生了！我要生了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.51,0:13:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 啊 是什么游戏么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.60,0:13:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢 名乃的弟弟要生出来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.12,0:13:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.21,0:13:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.76,0:14:30.01,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)\pos(750,360)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}狐\N狗\N狸\N先\N生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.55,0:14:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.97,0:14:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.27,0:14:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来玩“狐狗狸先生”吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.81,0:14:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.89,0:14:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 美绪你竟然不知道啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.06,0:14:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔知…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.15,0:14:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就 稍微给你说明一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.15,0:14:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先 准备一张像这样 在正中间画一个鸟居
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.15,0:14:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}鸟居：神社入口的牌坊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.57,0:14:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写着“是”和“不是”还有五十音图的纸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.45,0:14:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.24,0:14:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不同的地方也有给神画上油炸豆腐比较好的说法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.24,0:14:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}译注：日本人普遍认为狐狸爱吃油炸豆腐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.04,0:14:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就只画最简单的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.79,0:14:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.50,0:15:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 为了让狐狗狸先生能够进来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.25,0:15:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把北边的窗子开启
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.63,0:15:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.38,0:15:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 把这个十元硬币 放在这个鸟居的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.35,0:15:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人一起把手指放上面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.35,0:15:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提问想问的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.27,0:15:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人的秘密 喜欢的人的事情 烦恼的事情之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.77,0:15:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.56,0:15:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 明明什么都没做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.65,0:15:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十元硬币却自己来回动 狐狗狸先生会回答你的问题哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.95,0:15:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.15,0:15:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 很厉害吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.66,0:15:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 有几条禁止事项
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.70,0:15:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先 不能自己一个人玩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.12,0:15:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 不能开玩笑的玩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.70,0:15:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为会被低级妖怪盯上的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.16,0:15:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.96,0:15:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 中途停止的话也会被盯上的 一定要注意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.21,0:15:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.50,0:15:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个感觉 还是一个挺有危险的游戏哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.72,0:15:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我们来玩玩试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.80,0:15:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.09,0:15:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～咧～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.90,0:16:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那么今天就这样结束吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.16,0:16:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天要进行小测验 大家要好好学习哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.37,0:16:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 延期吧 延期吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.04,0:16:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫不管怎么延期结果都一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.46,0:16:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\bord0\shad0\c&HE5FBE2&\pos(265,545)}小\N测\N验
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.83,0:16:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.88,0:16:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱井老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.34,0:16:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相生同学 怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.30,0:16:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点事想问…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.63,0:16:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.59,0:16:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关于之前做的那个测试的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.60,0:16:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.64,0:16:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那个是FLY哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.69,0:16:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不是 不是想问答案
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.52,0:16:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个好像会被抹杀光线消灭的小怪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.52,0:16:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs33\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7}ニフラム{\r\fs36}：勇者斗恶龙中用光束抹杀敌人的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.19,0:16:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是老师你画的么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.27,0:16:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.73,0:16:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得如果放点画上去的话 考试会变得温柔一些之类的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.90,0:16:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师画的画很有意思哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.82,0:16:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.95,0:16:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我画画很差的 很难理解吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.91,0:17:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.42,0:17:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那老师 下一次把我画的画放上去吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.63,0:17:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会画一些超帅的画的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.59,0:17:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.80,0:17:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.72,0:17:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快听 快听 我画的话要放到考试里面去哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.93,0:17:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.35,0:17:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师说会给我放进去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.93,0:17:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪现在也开始画的画 说不定会全都放上去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.06,0:17:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是全都放上去还是会漏一些的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.40,0:17:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 你不画么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.02,0:17:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我就算了吧 不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.78,0:17:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得赶紧把这个还回去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.53,0:17:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.90,0:17:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那我来画一笔帅哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.00,0:17:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.92,0:17:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好帅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.67,0:17:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相生同学画画真好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.84,0:17:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人敬仰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.05,0:18:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 我啊 厉害吧 什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.35,0:18:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一提名字就叫做“五月雨乔治”
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.90,0:18:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜啊 更加更加帅了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.90,0:18:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅！？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.95,0:18:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等一下 二位
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.66,0:18:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般说的帅…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.50,0:18:24.00,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\frz21\pos(408,413)\c&H767378&}忧\N郁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.62,0:18:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是这样吧！？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.41,0:18:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜啊 好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.96,0:18:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像漫画一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.92,0:18:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长野原同学 你有在画漫画什么的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.30,0:18:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没有 就一点点而已
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.26,0:18:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 下次请给我看看哟
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.84,0:18:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那可有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.80,0:18:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？ 不可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.60,0:18:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想看 请给我看看吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.64,0:18:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 啊 但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.73,0:18:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微借我一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.73,0:18:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的会更帅的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.19,0:18:53.69,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs27\bord0\shad0\c&H767378&\frz324.472\pos(442,255)}忧\N\N郁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.04,0:18:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就是抄袭么！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.82,0:18:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有抄袭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.03,0:18:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是抄袭哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.57,0:19:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名叫抄袭的致敬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.78,0:19:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承认了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.62,0:19:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好帅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.62,0:19:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么样的都可以吗？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.17,0:19:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 这样的怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.26,0:19:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.18,0:19:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又知性又酷的形象到哪个时代都是女性的憧憬对象！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.39,0:19:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 眼镜哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.52,0:19:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛不太好么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.19,0:19:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴隐形眼镜不就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.44,0:19:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这群人完全不能理解我！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.53,0:19:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我的就…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.24,0:19:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.87,0:19:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,架在耳朵下面了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.74,0:19:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你这也是抄袭吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.95,0:19:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是太阳镜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.08,0:19:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好帅~
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.83,0:19:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差别对待啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.79,0:19:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 这样子如何！？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.46,0:19:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.21,0:19:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从迎接到泡红茶 已经让人有千金小姐的感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.42,0:19:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受大吉岭的魔力吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.42,0:19:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}大吉岭：指大吉岭红茶 印度大吉岭地区产的红茶 被誉为“茶中香槟”
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.88,0:20:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 啊 还是眼镜？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.54,0:20:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我看不太懂这种
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.68,0:20:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不听隐形眼镜的忠告
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.73,0:20:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪你不能理解啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.98,0:20:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊 真正的帅气这个东西是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.35,0:20:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.66,0:20:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.99,0:20:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 给我等等 这货…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.83,0:20:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑着呢么！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.58,0:20:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很快 好帅啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.66,0:20:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太扯了——
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.13,0:20:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅气这种东西是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.21,0:20:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅气这种东西是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.46,0:20:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅气这种东西是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.17,0:20:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,符合常识… 符合常识的考虑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.39,0:20:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅气这种东西是——
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.77,0:20:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西吧！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.61,0:21:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋啦……
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.91,0:21:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑啦～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.04,0:21:17.13,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\c&HF1F1F1&\pos(400,482)}1-Q讲台前
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.04,0:21:17.13,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\c&HF1F1F1&\pos(185,553)}长野原美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.04,0:21:17.13,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs50\shad0\bord0\c&HF0F0F0&\pos(301,573)}击沉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.68,0:21:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.19,0:21:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,边听爵士乐边画的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.11,0:21:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.45,0:21:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 老师 您早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.42,0:21:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是老师啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.00,0:21:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 接下来发一下早晨小测的卷子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.92,0:21:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家传一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.54,0:21:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.32,0:21:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来想将画画这件事情保密来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.97,0:22:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟然画出来那种画了…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.32,0:22:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.88,0:22:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我暴走了 但只停留在那个级别的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.85,0:22:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也算是不幸中的万幸了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.93,0:22:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能想着勉强还算好事吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.06,0:22:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 两三天之内会被小佑一直嘲笑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.27,0:22:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 要忘记这个问题 向前进！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.99,0:22:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪老师 快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.99,0:22:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.08,0:22:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.00,0:22:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.14,0:24:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 初次见面哪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.05,0:24:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是拟声词
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.05,0:24:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs42\fn方正卡通_GBK}英：Onomatopoeia 法：Onomatopee
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.53,0:24:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,cock-a-doodle-doo是让人很想说的日语啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.92,0:24:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是日语
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.45,0:24:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话是日常的第六话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.06,0:24:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.99,0:01:33.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}たった今　初めて気づいた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.66,0:01:36.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋に落ちたのだなー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.33,0:01:38.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h キミ☆　キミ☆　キミ☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.87,0:01:40.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意識せざるをえません！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.83,0:01:43.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}なんか　いつもと違う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.33,0:01:42.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.46,0:01:46.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}キミと　ぎこちない会話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.92,0:01:44.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.13,0:01:48.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}まさか　いや　片思い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.59,0:01:47.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両思い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.92,0:01:51.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やばい！　視線合っちゃった！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.34,0:01:54.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}なになに！？このドキドキ！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.56,0:02:00.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路　ぐっちゃぐちゃ　混線…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.31,0:02:06.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}こんなこと　初めてだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.98,0:02:12.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}熱でもあるのかなー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.66,0:02:15.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急転直下　いらっしゃた　恋心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.53,0:02:18.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっちゅうま　顔　発火で　まっかっか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.12,0:02:20.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}バ·バ…バカな！？　手が震えるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.79,0:02:23.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが　俗に言う　「恋」　なの！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.54,0:02:26.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}やややっちゃった　会話　噛みまくり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.13,0:02:28.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気まずい沈黙　マミムメモ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.80,0:02:31.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}キミの　気持ち　知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.38,0:02:29.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キミの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.47,0:02:34.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.34,0:02:37.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！　{\r}いつもの通学路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.26,0:02:40.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}ピカピカ光る　{\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.64,0:02:43.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}空も飛べそうさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.35,0:02:46.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.99,0:01:33.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}就在刚刚 才第一次注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.66,0:01:36.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陷入恋情了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.33,0:01:38.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h 是你☆  是你☆  是你☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.87,0:01:40.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全部都是你！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.83,0:01:43.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}总觉得 和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.33,0:01:42.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.46,0:01:46.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}我与你 慌慌张张的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.92,0:01:44.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.13,0:01:48.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}难道说 不对 单相思
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.59,0:01:47.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.92,0:01:51.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！ 跟他的眼睛对上了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.34,0:01:54.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}什么什么！？心里小鹿乱撞！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.56,0:02:00.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路 黏黏糊糊乱糟糟 串线…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.31,0:02:06.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这样的事情 第一次遇到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.98,0:02:12.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}是不是患上感冒了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.66,0:02:15.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急转直下 悄无声息来的 春心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.53,0:02:18.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一会的时间 脸 像着火 通红通红的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.12,0:02:20.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}笨·笨…笨蛋吗！？ 手正在发抖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.79,0:02:23.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 俗话说的 “爱” 的啦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.54,0:02:26.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}要要要要坏菜了啊 对话 咬到舌头了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.13,0:02:28.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难为情的沉默 āōēīū
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.80,0:02:31.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}想知道 你现在 心里所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.38,0:02:29.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.47,0:02:34.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.34,0:02:37.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！ {\r}好像上学走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.26,0:02:40.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}亮闪闪的发光 {\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.64,0:02:43.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}感觉好像能上天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.35,0:02:46.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.67,0:22:51.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}朝起きて　歯を磨いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.88,0:22:54.59,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あっという間　午後十時
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.01,0:22:57.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日もたくさん　笑ったな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.05,0:23:00.68,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}たくさんときめいたな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.18,0:23:04.10,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}友たちと　バカみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.31,0:23:07.02,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}騒いでる　時にも
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.48,0:23:10.40,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}チラチラって　目が合おう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.52,0:23:13.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶然だよね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.32,0:23:16.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋なんて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:19.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キャラじゃないんだもん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.91,0:23:25.75,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ねぇ 明日も会えるよね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.00,0:23:28.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}まぶたを　閉じると
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.04,0:23:32.00,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キラキラ君だらけ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.17,0:23:35.34,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も楽しかったね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.42,0:23:39.51,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ああ どうしてだな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.55,0:23:43.14,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,660)\fad(100,200)\blur3\fs32}Please come true
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.89,0:23:47.77,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}うれしいな　うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.98,0:23:50.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}はじめまして　恋ごころ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.06,0:23:53.90,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}明日まだ　会えるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.15,0:23:56.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.32,0:24:01.37,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}夢ですぐ　会えるね
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.99,0:24:07.54,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.67,0:22:51.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}早晨睡醒后 起床刷牙来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.88,0:22:54.59,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}不知不觉间 已到晚十点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.01,0:22:57.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天也遇到 很多欢乐事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.05,0:23:00.68,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}也有非常多 刺激与紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.18,0:23:04.10,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}和闺中密友 像笨蛋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.31,0:23:07.02,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}大声吵又闹 偶尔会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.48,0:23:10.40,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶尔瞥向你 四目便相接
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.52,0:23:13.11,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}这也不过是 偶然事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.32,0:23:16.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋什么的难以说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:19.74,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}因为我不是这样的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.91,0:23:25.75,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}呐 我们明天 也会相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.00,0:23:28.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}将我的双眼 合上了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.04,0:23:32.00,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}脑海中只有 亮晶晶的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.17,0:23:35.34,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天的我也 开心又愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.42,0:23:39.51,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}啊 这又是为何
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.89,0:23:47.77,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}真的好开心 真的好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.98,0:23:50.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}第一次见面 我的爱慕心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.06,0:23:53.90,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}到明天的话 我们又见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.15,0:23:56.11,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.32,0:24:01.37,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}在梦中很快 我们会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.99,0:24:07.54,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}现在晚安吧


