[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-01 23:11:41
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 日常 第16話
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,45,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.25,0:00:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能心算呐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.71,0:00:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.84,0:00:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.09,0:00:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得她身为机器人 该有些机器人似的功能么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.47,0:00:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.93,0:00:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能是机器人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.85,0:00:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？！ 你看背后都插着发条哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.73,0:00:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？！ 就因为这个你就认为她是机器人么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.27,0:00:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.11,0:00:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 你仔细想想嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.28,0:00:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器人哦 机器人！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.91,0:00:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很厉害吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.16,0:00:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得 很厉害吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.29,0:00:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是什么啊 完全不能作为理由吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.62,0:00:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之呢 咱们来调查一下名乃是不是机器人吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.71,0:00:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 算了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.88,0:00:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.09,0:00:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是有所计划哒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.78,0:02:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.99,0:02:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.41,0:02:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提问
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.49,0:02:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.37,0:02:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3260+260÷320是多少？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.00,0:02:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.09,0:02:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.84,0:02:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3260加…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.38,0:02:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是觉得难的话… 咳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用一下机能倒也可以…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.47,0:02:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咳咳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.76,0:02:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 小佑 作战原来就是那个啊！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.77,0:02:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉 那就恭敬不如从命…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.60,0:02:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.11,0:02:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是算盘！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.86,0:02:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部清零重新开始～～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.69,0:02:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来真的啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.86,0:03:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.53,0:03:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1、2、3…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.78,0:03:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新…×N 新手啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.16,0:03:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.41,0:03:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3260加上…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.92,0:03:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没在用算——盘！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.21,0:03:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我… 我说 小佑！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.96,0:03:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相… 相生同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.88,0:03:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧…？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.51,0:03:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 没事…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.88,0:03:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是各种意义上都觉得名乃是神算啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.72,0:03:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 都跟你说了她不是机器人了嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.10,0:03:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.39,0:03:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要喝点喝的么！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.11,0:03:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.44,0:03:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个… 难道说！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.57,0:03:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.82,0:03:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是油啊——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.12,0:03:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疙瘩汤啊！！ 我倒！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.29,0:03:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.08,0:03:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.38,0:03:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 水上同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.71,0:04:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.14,0:04:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了一发直球啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.68,0:04:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一罐油！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.26,0:04:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.35,0:04:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 啊 可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.85,0:04:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.19,0:04:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.73,0:04:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打空啦——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.48,0:04:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也给你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.39,0:04:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔球！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.08,0:04:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扳手！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.25,0:04:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.83,0:04:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.75,0:04:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.79,0:04:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打空啦——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.28,0:04:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我… 我说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.84,0:04:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都差不多点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.22,0:04:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃很困扰的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.39,0:04:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肌肤之亲…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.01,0:04:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.93,0:04:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 想要跟你交个朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.56,0:04:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这哪是在接近她啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.27,0:04:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本就是一直在疏远嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.27,0:04:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱… 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.15,0:04:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.98,0:05:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 请不必这么在意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.44,0:05:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.20,0:05:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.86,0:05:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不要疙瘩汤的话我喝了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.12,0:05:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 名乃都这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.49,0:05:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.37,0:05:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}银牙能拿下来么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.87,0:05:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在名乃的立场上考虑考虑哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.34,0:05:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是笨啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.65,0:05:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs39\bord0\c&H110C06&\4c&HFFFFFF&\pos(553,554)}没\N有\N去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.65,0:05:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs39\bord0\c&H110C06&\4c&HFFFFFF&\pos(712,534)}扫\N除
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.20,0:05:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.29,0:05:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么能做出来那么高性能的东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.13,0:06:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前几天转学来的 东云名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.26,0:06:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那存在感…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.17,0:06:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 那个发条
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.09,0:06:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看都是机器人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.22,0:06:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么那种机器人不在学会发表
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.73,0:06:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而满不在乎的让她来上学…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.77,0:06:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想调查…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.61,0:06:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想调查一下她…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.28,0:06:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.90,0:06:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想让她成为我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.62,0:06:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中村老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.00,0:06:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托我的书我拿来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.62,0:06:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.37,0:06:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 要坚决实行哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.50,0:06:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.92,0:06:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云 稍等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.88,0:06:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？ 要不要喝一杯咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.30,0:06:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 不…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.55,0:06:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用您费心了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.93,0:06:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说这么见外的话嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.31,0:06:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚放进去的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.52,0:07:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你帮我搬书至少给你点回礼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.89,0:07:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝下去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.44,0:07:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 那就只喝一杯好了……
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.32,0:07:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先要试验一下催眠药管用不管用
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.28,0:07:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个要是不起作用的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.53,0:07:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让昨天做的回路SHORT君从背后把她吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.29,0:07:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.00,0:07:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.05,0:07:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝下去啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.48,0:07:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍住…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.48,0:07:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍住…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.49,0:07:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.07,0:07:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少 让回路SHORT君…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.83,0:08:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让回路SHORT君…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.04,0:08:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.79,0:08:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理科的中村 好像倒下了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.67,0:08:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是总倒下呐 中村
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.68,0:08:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.94,0:08:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 相生同学和水上同学 都是很好的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.11,0:08:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 能够做朋友么…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.74,0:08:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃我一记…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.49,0:08:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火箭拳！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.24,0:08:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.14,0:08:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是火箭拳的最大火力！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.01,0:08:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 博士！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.26,0:08:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 欢迎回家～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.60,0:09:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 名乃 欢迎回家～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.81,0:09:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 为什么要说两遍啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.02,0:09:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 比起那种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.86,0:09:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点帮我把这个拿下去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.24,0:09:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.07,0:09:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还问为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.20,0:09:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为… 又难做到椅子里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.99,0:09:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又被大家以为我很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.20,0:09:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还被人拍摄了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.70,0:09:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这样我总算还是糊弄过去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.50,0:09:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.02,0:09:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.00,0:09:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着发条的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.40,0:09:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家不是都不把我当作普通的女孩子了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.96,0:09:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对会很有人气的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.88,0:09:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不愿意～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.43,0:09:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要过普通的学校生活…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.09,0:10:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要装上这样一个武器啊～～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.63,0:10:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸亏没有在学校拿下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.42,0:10:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃为什么不想暴露自己是个机器人呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.60,0:10:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自然是因为那样很不可爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.93,0:10:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器人很可爱哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.77,0:10:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.60,0:10:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.02,0:10:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这把枪也是吗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.52,0:10:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.52,0:10:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次的拇指USB也是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.90,0:10:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.94,0:10:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额头上出来小甜面包呢！？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.70,0:10:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱嘛！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.45,0:10:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.37,0:10:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士你是疯狂博士！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.95,0:10:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很·可·爱·嘛！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.66,0:10:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢更普通点！！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.27,0:11:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇～是竹轮啊～～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.27,0:11:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}竹轮：日式食品 圆筒状鱼糕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.15,0:11:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竹轮很好吃啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.68,0:11:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.60,0:11:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.64,0:11:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.64,0:12:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}4点了…4点了…4点了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.71,0:12:17.21,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\pos(1200,360)\bord4\blur8}大\N福\N展\N览\N会\N１
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.84,0:12:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 大福哦——
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.34,0:12:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便宜了哦——
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.84,0:12:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大福哦——
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.13,0:12:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 中之条先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.09,0:12:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.52,0:12:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个大福 给我闭嘴！！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.78,0:12:45.78,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\pos(80,360)\bord4\blur8}大\N福\N展\N览\N会\N２
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.32,0:12:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.61,0:12:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.65,0:12:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是以半吊子的觉悟带着这面具的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.95,0:12:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定 赌上性命！！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.71,0:12:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要让我说第二遍！！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.50,0:12:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.42,0:12:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一次失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.42,0:13:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来用催眠药还是太轻率啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.80,0:13:04.80,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs60\fad(520,520)\bord5\blur8\pos(1200,360)}中\N村\N先\N生\N‘\N回\N路\N\N\N\N\N\N君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.80,0:13:04.80,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs60\fad(520,520)\bord5\blur8\frz270\pos(1200,540)}SHORT
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.17,0:13:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说她可是机器人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.09,0:13:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不来一发强烈的她可昏迷不了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.76,0:13:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下就是这个登场啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.35,0:13:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前没能用上的 对机器人用——
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.06,0:13:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回路SHORT君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.98,0:13:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这个让她气绝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.06,0:13:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在今天 我要把你捕获
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.19,0:13:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间快到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.81,0:13:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑！！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.73,0:13:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 中村老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.94,0:14:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我… 我说！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.44,0:14:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最上面的钮扣一定要扣上哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.07,0:14:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.57,0:14:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 随便我怎样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.47,0:14:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.08,0:14:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是学生指导哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.08,0:14:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 真的假的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.50,0:14:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就你还能当上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.62,0:14:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真失礼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.71,0:14:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 我给你扣一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.75,0:14:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己会扣的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.38,0:14:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人害羞啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.71,0:14:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\bord0\shad0\c&H384642&\frx0\fry28}乌鸦\N多发
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.71,0:14:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\an7\bord0\shad0\c&H384642&\frx0\fry28\pos(106,12)}风\N纪\N委\N员\N会\N宣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.79,0:14:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.84,0:14:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神马情况？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.72,0:14:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为小真你自己弄不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.58,0:14:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.85,0:14:35.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小真？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.39,0:14:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.64,0:14:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.60,0:14:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\bord8\shad0\c&H1AE1EF&\3c&H2F2F2F&\move(1220,0,1220,310,0,400)}你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.81,0:14:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.10,0:14:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了啦 我给你扣上啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.48,0:14:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\bord8\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&HC777FA&\move(70,880,70,580,0,520)}我\N给\N你\N扣\N上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.48,0:14:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你！？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.78,0:14:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你扣上！？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.24,0:14:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.78,0:14:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在学校不要纠缠我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.45,0:14:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纠…纠缠！？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.29,0:15:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.47,0:15:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}他们什么关系？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.13,0:15:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 都掉下来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.54,0:15:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}什么关系…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.34,0:15:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那正好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.21,0:15:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我还有事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.34,0:15:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.47,0:15:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那副不成体统的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.38,0:15:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被大家笑话的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.97,0:15:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.35,0:15:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在家不也穿的不成体统的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.22,0:15:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.18,0:15:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿… 穿… 穿的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.48,0:15:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿的不成体统的！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.27,0:15:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不成体统的穿着！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.32,0:15:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.19,0:15:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对不对不对！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.19,0:15:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么真棒 我是白痴么！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.07,0:15:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么旗袍是不成体统的穿着哟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.24,0:15:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是普通点的不成体统的穿着吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.24,0:15:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.37,0:15:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为教师不觉得很可耻么！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.58,0:15:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通点的不成体统的穿着哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.25,0:15:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.77,0:15:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不成体统的穿着！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.96,0:15:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Enough！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.72,0:15:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Enough什么的 白痴！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.17,0:15:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.86,0:15:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.05,0:15:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 扣子呢！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.17,0:15:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad2\4c&HFEF6F3&\c&H4D6327&}O{\c&H31DCE0&}g{\c&H5E372A&}u{\c&H37B475&}r{\c&H266CAB&}i {\c&H9167CA&}C{\c&H2972D2&}a{\c&H45AB9D&}p{\c&H9D69F4&}是{\c&H3F6982&}这{\c&H8A5237&}个{\c&H324731&}样{\c&H3035B5&}子{\c&H9F7661&}的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.81,0:16:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白… 白痴！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.15,0:16:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.99,0:16:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.24,0:16:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 扣子呢！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.07,0:16:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要… 要追咯！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.53,0:16:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高崎老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.70,0:16:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中之条君在理科室昏迷了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.75,0:16:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.42,0:16:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望您马上来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.83,0:16:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.08,0:16:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.59,0:16:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着啊… 好好听着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.26,0:16:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.64,0:16:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中之条他并没有昏迷！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.31,0:16:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶诶——！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.35,0:16:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啦！！ 他可能是在装睡！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.19,0:16:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶诶——！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.19,0:16:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 都翻白眼了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.48,0:16:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶诶——！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.94,0:16:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我涂上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.69,0:16:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶诶——！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.99,0:16:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.07,0:16:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶诶——！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.20,0:16:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.03,0:17:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶诶——！？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.12,0:17:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.20,0:17:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.29,0:17:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起昏迷 管制不纯异性交往
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.67,0:17:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更应该是身为教育者的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.04,0:17:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么呐！！ 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.55,0:17:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教育者啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.59,0:17:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位 是樱井老师的弟弟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.01,0:17:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.84,0:17:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.64,0:17:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.23,0:17:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.35,0:17:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是 教师吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.73,0:17:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这边！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.29,0:17:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\c&HD6A6FE&\pos(622,498)}与爱有关的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.02,0:18:10.69,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\bord6\blur10\pos(100,360)}外\N带
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.73,0:18:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一站是 时定站北口
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.52,0:18:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\pos(570,320)\c&H5F5A5A&}下车的乘\N客请按下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.48,0:18:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一站 停车
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.90,0:18:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫 不是下一站下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.99,0:18:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 你不觉得总想按下去么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.70,0:18:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H5F5A5A&\pos(570,320)}下车的乘\N客请按下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.95,0:18:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫 刚才也按了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.54,0:18:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才不是有人下嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.83,0:18:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就结果来说不是挺好的么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.39,0:18:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 帮了别人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.64,0:18:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 这里不也有人下嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.63,0:18:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干的漂亮！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.13,0:18:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 有没有日历啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.55,0:18:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是在壁橱里么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.36,0:18:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 博士～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.45,0:19:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 名乃 欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.82,0:19:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 差不多把我这个发条取下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.78,0:19:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我的学校生活来说是个障碍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.33,0:19:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天上体育课的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.87,0:19:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳高只能跳俯卧式的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.79,0:19:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踢球的时候也因为这个被判了好几次越位
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.00,0:19:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 可以取下来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.92,0:19:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.63,0:19:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 能拿下来的话就请早点说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.10,0:19:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道啦 现在给你取下来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.02,0:19:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春时代的每一天每一天都是很重要的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.44,0:19:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这样一来终于能过普通的高中生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.86,0:19:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就赶快吧 可以帮我取下来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.32,0:19:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,2000)}盯——
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.90,0:19:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.86,0:19:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.74,0:19:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.28,0:19:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照下来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.28,0:19:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}译注：日语中取下和照相音相同
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.12,0:19:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我晕～！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.70,0:19:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.25,0:19:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“照”一张相片什么的这种古老的笑话就算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.88,0:19:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.57,0:19:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.27,0:19:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个发条能拿下来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.37,0:20:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.81,0:20:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒～！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.02,0:20:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要开老的或者好的玩笑啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.43,0:20:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能取下来吗！？不能取下来吗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.19,0:20:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以取下来 可以取下来哟～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.86,0:20:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士可是取下过好多次发条的人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.94,0:20:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃的发条什么的很简单的…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.69,0:20:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照下来 啪…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.79,0:20:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金币 金币 金币 我飞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.70,0:20:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说 金币 金币
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.87,0:20:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金币…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.48,0:20:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说 我… 我我我我… 我飞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.08,0:20:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.08,0:20:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.50,0:20:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喘不… 喘不上来气了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.05,0:20:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.32,0:20:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 我今天跌倒的有点不自然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.68,0:20:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我… 那个… 做了些 手脚么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.22,0:20:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上昨天加了跌倒机能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.81,0:20:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞啊飞…×N
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.94,0:20:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我说我说！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.77,0:20:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种胡乱的机能是怎么回事啊！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.02,0:21:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要加上这种机能啊！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.19,0:21:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为好玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.45,0:21:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我晕～！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.16,0:21:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GOAL——
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.20,0:21:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会死…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.16,0:21:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去会跌倒到死的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.62,0:21:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 很有意思吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.92,0:21:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有意思！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.59,0:21:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发条可以先推迟一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.34,0:21:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把这个机能去掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.42,0:21:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 一百元
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.51,0:21:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}发射——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.24,0:23:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.35,0:23:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的余力的 全开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.76,0:23:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是油
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.59,0:23:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑话经常戳不中笑点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.59,0:23:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}注：{\fs30\fnＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7}すべる{\r\fs36}有戳不中笑点和滑的双关
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.19,0:23:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 但身为油也是没办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.18,0:23:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上司经常这样概括
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.43,0:23:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是油的上司啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.14,0:23:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话的日常是 第十六话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.73,0:23:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.95,0:22:01.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}ときにはなぜか大空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.92,0:22:08.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}旅してみたく　なるものさ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.14,0:22:16.89,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}気球に乗ってどこまでいこう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.19,0:22:24.90,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}風にのって野原を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.19,0:22:32.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}雲をとび越えどこまでもいこう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.99,0:22:42.04,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}そこになにかが待っているから
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.95,0:22:01.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}时而不知为何啊 在广阔天上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.92,0:22:08.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}尝试一次的旅行 心中这么想
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.14,0:22:16.89,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}让那气球载着我 可以去任何地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.19,0:22:24.90,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}让那风载着我 穿越那一片原野
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.19,0:22:32.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}飞越过层层云朵 可以去到任何地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.99,0:22:42.04,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}在那里有着什么在等着你来啦

Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.42,0:00:50.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.71,0:00:51.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.26,0:00:54.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.80,0:00:59.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}はい　言っちゃいましょ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.18,0:01:01.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}キミは　Best Best Friend!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.94,0:01:04.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.23,0:01:06.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと　ふざけてみたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.31,0:01:06.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.60,0:01:08.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　ふざけ返してくる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.73,0:01:10.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.48,0:01:11.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.15,0:01:12.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいったら　ありゃしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.53,0:01:13.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.86,0:01:15.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イヤなことあったって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.91,0:01:16.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.20,0:01:19.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}そっこー　忘れちゃうんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.32,0:01:19.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.91,0:01:20.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.62,0:01:22.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃんじゃん　やりましょー！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.66,0:01:25.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}２４時間　一緒でも　問題ない！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.12,0:01:27.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}まるで　双子か　親子か　クローンさいぼー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.50,0:01:30.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}これじゃ　恋愛する　必要とか　なくなくない？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.75,0:01:32.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}それと　これとは　全く全く　別問題！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.67,0:01:33.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.01,0:01:35.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}ケンカしちゃったときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.09,0:01:35.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.42,0:01:37.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}かなり凹んだときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.43,0:01:37.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.84,0:01:39.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}一人で　いたいよなときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.89,0:01:44.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}ふと気づけば　近くにいるしなばもろともー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.89,0:01:47.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんでだろ　{\r}そばにいたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.90,0:01:50.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}キミと一緒なら　{\r}時計１００倍速！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.77,0:01:53.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}楽しいな　{\r}楽しすぎるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.69,0:01:54.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}さすが　最強Friend!　{\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.40,0:01:55.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.53,0:01:57.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんなのよ　{\r}やっばいシンクロ感
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.53,0:02:00.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}いつも大騒ぎ　{\r}かなり　ご近所迷惑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.32,0:02:02.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何時？　{\r}えっとね　ヨロレイヒー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.33,0:02:03.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}わけわかんないない！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.62,0:02:06.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ソーレードーシーラー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.21,0:02:08.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像以上！なんていうか最高！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.71,0:02:09.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}あーだーこーだー言ってても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.92,0:02:11.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}友達　わっしょい！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.13,0:02:12.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.29,0:02:13.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.84,0:02:17.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ちゃちゃら　ちゃらちゃちゃーん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.42,0:00:50.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.71,0:00:51.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.26,0:00:54.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.80,0:00:59.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}来 说出口来！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.18,0:01:01.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}你就是 Best Best Friend！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.94,0:01:04.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.23,0:01:06.31,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 跟你胡闹一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.31,0:01:06.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.60,0:01:08.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加 回敬我大闹一番
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.73,0:01:10.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.48,0:01:11.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.15,0:01:12.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提 有多爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.53,0:01:13.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.86,0:01:15.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算发生了一些不快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.91,0:01:16.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.20,0:01:19.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}赶快 将这事情忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.32,0:01:19.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.91,0:01:20.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.62,0:01:22.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要 精神满满！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.66,0:01:25.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}24小时 都在一起 也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.12,0:01:27.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}简直像 双胞胎 或亲子 克隆细胞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.50,0:01:30.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这一来 陷入爱河 岂不就是 没必没必要？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.75,0:01:32.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}那件事 跟这件事 完全完全 两码事！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.67,0:01:33.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.01,0:01:35.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算我们吵架的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.09,0:01:35.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.42,0:01:37.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算非常低落的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.43,0:01:37.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.84,0:01:39.89,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算一人 深感寂寞的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.89,0:01:44.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}不经意间发现 身旁的你可同我生与死都相随
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.89,0:01:47.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}这是为何 {\r}想要在你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.90,0:01:50.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}如果和你在一起 {\r}时间100倍速飞逝！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.77,0:01:53.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真快乐呐 {\r}有点快乐的过头啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.69,0:01:54.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}不愧是 最强Friend！ {\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.40,0:01:55.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.53,0:01:57.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}搞什么哦 {\r}同步率快要破表
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.53,0:02:00.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}总是太过于兴奋 {\r}周围都 相当受到困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.32,0:02:02.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何时？ {\r}那个啊 哟啰咧咿呵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.33,0:02:03.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真是莫名其妙！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.62,0:02:06.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sol Re Do Ti La
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.21,0:02:08.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像之外！ 无论如何最棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.71,0:02:09.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}说那说这不管怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.92,0:02:11.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}都是朋友 哇塞！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.13,0:02:12.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.29,0:02:13.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.84,0:02:17.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ChaChaRa ChaRaChaChan


