[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-01 22:44:22
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 日常 第18話
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,45,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.42,0:00:47.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.71,0:00:48.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.26,0:00:51.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.80,0:00:57.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}はい　言っちゃいましょ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.18,0:00:58.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}キミは　Best Best Friend!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.94,0:01:01.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.23,0:01:03.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと　ふざけてみたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.31,0:01:03.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.60,0:01:05.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　ふざけ返してくる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.73,0:01:07.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.48,0:01:08.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.15,0:01:09.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいったら　ありゃしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.53,0:01:10.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.86,0:01:12.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イヤなことあったって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.91,0:01:13.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.20,0:01:16.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}そっこー　忘れちゃうんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.32,0:01:16.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.91,0:01:17.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.62,0:01:19.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃんじゃん　やりましょー！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.66,0:01:22.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}２４時間　一緒でも　問題ない！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.12,0:01:24.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}まるで　双子か　親子か　クローンさいぼー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.50,0:01:27.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}これじゃ　恋愛する　必要とか　なくなくない？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.75,0:01:29.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}それと　これとは　全く全く　別問題！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.67,0:01:30.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.01,0:01:32.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}ケンカしちゃったときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.09,0:01:32.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.42,0:01:34.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}かなり凹んだときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.43,0:01:34.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.84,0:01:36.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}一人で　いたいよなときも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.89,0:01:41.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}ふと気づけば　近くにいるしなばもろともー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.89,0:01:44.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんでだろ　{\r}そばにいたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.90,0:01:47.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}キミと一緒なら　{\r}時計１００倍速！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.77,0:01:50.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}楽しいな　{\r}楽しすぎるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.69,0:01:51.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}さすが　最強Friend!　{\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.40,0:01:52.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.53,0:01:54.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんなのよ　{\r}やっばいシンクロ感
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.53,0:01:57.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}いつも大騒ぎ　{\r}かなり　ご近所迷惑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.32,0:01:59.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何時？　{\r}えっとね　ヨロレイヒー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.33,0:02:00.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}わけわかんないない！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.62,0:02:03.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ソーレードーシーラー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.21,0:02:05.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像以上！なんていうか最高！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.71,0:02:06.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}あーだーこーだー言ってても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.92,0:02:08.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}友達　わっしょい！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.13,0:02:09.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:10.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.84,0:02:14.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ちゃちゃら　ちゃらちゃちゃーん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.42,0:00:47.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.71,0:00:48.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.26,0:00:51.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.80,0:00:57.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}来 说出口来！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.18,0:00:58.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}你就是 Best Best Friend！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.94,0:01:01.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.23,0:01:03.31,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 跟你胡闹一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.31,0:01:03.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.60,0:01:05.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加 回敬我大闹一番
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.73,0:01:07.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.48,0:01:08.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.15,0:01:09.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提 有多爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.53,0:01:10.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.86,0:01:12.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算发生了一些不快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.91,0:01:13.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.20,0:01:16.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}赶快 将这事情忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.32,0:01:16.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.91,0:01:17.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.62,0:01:19.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要 精神满满！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.66,0:01:22.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}24小时 都在一起 也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.12,0:01:24.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}简直像 双胞胎 或亲子 克隆细胞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.50,0:01:27.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这一来 陷入爱河 岂不就是 没必没必要？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.75,0:01:29.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}那件事 跟这件事 完全完全 两码事！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.67,0:01:30.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.01,0:01:32.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算我们吵架的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.09,0:01:32.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.42,0:01:34.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算非常低落的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.43,0:01:34.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.84,0:01:36.89,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算一人 深感寂寞的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.89,0:01:41.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}不经意间发现 身旁的你可同我生与死都相随
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.89,0:01:44.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}这是为何 {\r}想要在你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.90,0:01:47.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}如果和你在一起 {\r}时间100倍速飞逝！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.77,0:01:50.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真快乐呐 {\r}有点快乐的过头啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.69,0:01:51.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}不愧是 最强Friend！ {\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.40,0:01:52.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.53,0:01:54.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}搞什么哦 {\r}同步率快要破表
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.53,0:01:57.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}总是太过于兴奋 {\r}周围都 相当受到困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.32,0:01:59.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何时？ {\r}那个啊 哟啰咧咿呵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.33,0:02:00.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真是莫名其妙！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.62,0:02:03.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sol Re Do Ti La
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.21,0:02:05.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像之外！ 无论如何最棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.71,0:02:06.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}说那说这不管怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.92,0:02:08.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}都是朋友 哇塞！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.13,0:02:09.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:10.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.84,0:02:14.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ChaChaRa ChaRaChaChan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.10,0:00:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 大工吃茶店改装了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.44,0:00:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.36,0:00:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里这里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.07,0:00:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啊 变成咖啡馆了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.74,0:00:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.41,0:00:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前也来过了 所以美绪你可以先点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.12,0:00:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 是么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.62,0:00:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.00,0:00:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一杯大号的白巧克力摩卡星冰乐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.63,0:00:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 还要追加
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.29,0:00:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一杯加焦糖酱 榛子糖浆\N巧克力豆 额外打过的 小杯浓咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.85,0:00:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死去吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.60,0:00:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 小佑你去哪里？！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.09,0:02:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,催眠药
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.41,0:02:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对东云 没有效果
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.96,0:02:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时要用这个啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.88,0:02:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让氧化催化效果倍增
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.25,0:02:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且为保险起见还与麻醉剂进行配合的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.55,0:02:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,氧化君PLUS！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.44,0:02:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把这个给东云喝下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.26,0:02:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮的把她一口气捕获啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.85,0:02:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕获之后要怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.14,0:02:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做那种事情还有这种事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.56,0:02:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟哟哟哟哟…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.48,0:02:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎怎… 怎么办哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.61,0:02:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要用指南针啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.87,0:02:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 你会用指南针么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.80,0:02:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 会！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.62,0:02:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同学们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.16,0:02:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天这堂课变成自习了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.16,0:03:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 太好啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.88,0:03:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中村老师 又倒下了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.42,0:03:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是总倒下啊 中村
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.28,0:03:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹原 你为什么又翘了扫除啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.68,0:03:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把我自己的区域扫除过了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.06,0:03:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多没扫干净的灰尘哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.39,0:03:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.69,0:03:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点回到你那片区域去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.61,0:03:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 你为什么知道我在屋顶呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.74,0:03:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么蠢话！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.91,0:03:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不过是被这晴天吸引来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.36,0:03:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔溜跶溜跶顺便经过而已的！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.16,0:03:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…这样啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.83,0:03:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你特意费心真是抱歉呐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.67,0:03:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然还帮忙看了我的区域
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.55,0:03:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可不要误会哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.05,0:03:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是为了你呐！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.60,0:04:09.61,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs70\pos(1200,360)\fad(520,520)\blur10\bord2}抓\N娃\N娃\N机
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.42,0:04:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息日
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.00,0:04:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和麻衣约好了去邻市见面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.92,0:04:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像能免费得到点心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.76,0:04:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要吃到爽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.26,0:04:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要吃面包吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.72,0:04:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.05,0:04:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来的时候吃过了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.60,0:04:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狗啊… 怎么说呢… 有点犯规 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.15,0:04:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.65,0:04:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.99,0:04:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟 就快要到了 要不要站起来呐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.95,0:04:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.74,0:05:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}下一站
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.58,0:05:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs42}时定问屋町
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.29,0:05:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs42}时定问屋町
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.29,0:05:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好时机！！播音员！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.42,0:05:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs42}时定问屋町
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.92,0:05:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs42}时定问屋町到了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.00,0:05:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.67,0:05:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快下去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.88,0:05:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}请于右侧下车
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.51,0:05:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车内的各位
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.26,0:05:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.18,0:05:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛嘛嘛… 应该是从这边说再见呐！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.19,0:05:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍住忍住
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.11,0:05:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度就要惊慌失措可不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.82,0:05:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.24,0:05:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点那个急事！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.82,0:05:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～～真是的！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.03,0:05:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.91,0:05:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是再也不会见面的小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.62,0:05:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是邻市
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.66,0:05:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都不认识我呐！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.50,0:05:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在意不要在意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.29,0:05:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…话说怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.71,0:05:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在跟着我？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.01,0:05:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错觉错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.51,0:05:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天稍微有点过敏呐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.13,0:05:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.93,0:06:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前不是说出了车站就有一个大工汉堡店么…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.47,0:06:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.02,0:06:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣给我画的地图
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.68,0:06:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得 软趴趴的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.64,0:06:12.52,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs30\frz19.381\pos(378,275)}大工\N汉堡店
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.64,0:06:12.52,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs30\frz19.381\pos(424,458)}在这
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.10,0:06:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要赶紧问路吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.77,0:06:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.86,0:06:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.27,0:06:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.15,0:06:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大工汉堡店在哪…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.94,0:06:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我… 我说！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.65,0:06:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么从刚才开始就一直跟着我！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.20,0:06:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事会那什么哟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.11,0:06:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,著作权会怎么样的哟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.91,0:06:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大工汉堡店的话就在这后面哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.49,0:06:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要在那里跟别人碰面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.58,0:06:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的话我带你去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.01,0:06:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.89,0:06:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.89,0:06:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社团活动的原因迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.80,0:06:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好慢！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.64,0:06:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的跟别人碰面啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.93,0:06:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.69,0:06:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣还没来呢吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.69,0:06:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.11,0:06:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是倒霉日吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.69,0:07:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意想不到的丢人啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.99,0:07:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 算了吧 反正是邻市…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.12,0:07:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 乐观的看的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.37,0:07:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在好的层面上这也算是人生的预先演习吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.66,0:07:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 这份羞耻我会跨越过去的！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.38,0:07:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是什么我都会跨越过去的！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.34,0:07:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.80,0:07:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.80,0:07:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.76,0:07:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.05,0:07:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Trick or Treat
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.31,0:07:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…这样的话 那就没办法了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.39,0:07:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了得到点心…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.06,0:07:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.23,0:07:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Trick or Treat
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.56,0:07:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万圣节是上周哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.23,0:07:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,700)\bord0\shad4\c&HA19208&\4c&HF4F2F1&}乌{\c&H1C7644&}鸦 {\c&H923961&}是{\c&HF36CB3&}这{\c&H3EC39A&}个{\c&H493558&}样{\c&HD78B35&}子{\c&H6AC8B2&}的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.03,0:07:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs54\bord4\shad0\blur8\fad(500,500)\c&H000000&\pos(1201,100)}无\N论\N如\N何\N都
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.03,0:07:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs54\bord4\shad0\blur8\fad(500,500)\c&H000000&\pos(931,100)}必\N须\N要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.03,0:07:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs54\bord4\shad0\blur8\fad(500,500)\c&H000000&\pos(367,100)}从\N吓\N唬\N人\N的\N乌\N鸦\N旁\N边
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.03,0:07:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs54\bord4\shad0\blur8\fad(500,500)\c&H000000&\pos(60,100)}经\N过\N的\N时\N候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.87,0:07:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs54\bord4\shad0\blur8\fad(500,0)\c&H000000&\pos(386,140)}千\N万\N不\N可\N以
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.87,0:07:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs54\bord4\shad0\blur8\fad(500,0)\c&H000000&\pos(74,140)}躲\N避\N它\N的\N视\N线
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.83,0:07:54.79,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx95\pos(1100,550)\bord3\3c&HF9FAFD&}雪\N飘
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.83,0:07:54.79,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnArial\fs27\pos(1172,546)\bord3\3c&HF9FAFD&}flsnow
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.33,0:07:58.59,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs100\pos(800,360)\fad(520,0)\shad3\4c&H040200&\c&HF0F3F2&}睡\N\N觉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.13,0:08:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不太困
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.30,0:08:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说数跳过栅栏的羊的数量的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.01,0:08:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能睡着了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.22,0:08:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白啦 我试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.27,0:08:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只羊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.44,0:08:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才一只就睡着了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.27,0:08:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.65,0:08:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.19,0:08:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.40,0:08:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羊 还没跳过去呢吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.61,0:08:27.45,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs60\pos(760,360)\fad(520,0)\shad2\4c&H040200&\c&HF1F1F1&}志\N愿\N精\N神
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.87,0:08:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.08,0:08:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了 不愧是姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.25,0:08:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 这种事情 是笹原同学教给你的么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.21,0:08:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为 为什么我非得让他手把手的教啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.18,0:08:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 你们关系很好的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.68,0:08:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不哦 根本不！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.05,0:08:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岂止是根本不 简直就是根本不哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.10,0:08:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.89,0:08:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是之前不是帮他熨手帕来得么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.31,0:08:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是偶然在路上捡到的垃圾而已罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.36,0:09:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 是因为是笹原同学的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.90,0:09:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不是那么回事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.07,0:09:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是因为想要锻炼手臂肌肉的时候 正好看到那个熨斗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.07,0:09:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面凑巧有那块手帕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.04,0:09:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之类的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.41,0:09:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之类的事情啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.21,0:09:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好容易看穿…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.92,0:09:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是姐姐 你熨手帕的时候那么高兴来的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.84,0:09:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么蠢话啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.97,0:09:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 那个时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.34,0:09:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候 只是因为地球进入了光子带
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.45,0:09:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 听我说 昨天啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.24,0:09:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.24,0:09:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和大野君说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.58,0:09:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.42,0:10:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电车坐了两小时
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.42,0:10:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客车坐了一小时
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.34,0:10:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远离了都市的人山人海
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.84,0:10:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 终于来到了这偏僻的S村
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.36,0:10:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.11,0:10:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然心想着可能此生再也找不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.11,0:10:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我仍然不能完全放弃 那本很久以前就开始找寻的书
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.54,0:10:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将我那灰色的少女时代
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.41,0:10:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涂上了缤纷的色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.79,0:10:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被称作如梦似幻的那本书
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.71,0:10:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这 图书馆里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.26,0:10:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个时代 能读到那本书
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.02,0:11:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对和赠书人有着这样的机缘心怀着感激之情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.53,0:11:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿着那本书
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.57,0:11:15.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按捺着心中的激动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.54,0:11:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.96,0:11:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢的开启了这本书
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.92,0:11:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\c&HD6A6FE&\pos(622,498)}与爱有关的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.42,0:11:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 时间快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.55,0:11:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都确认一下写没写名字哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.55,0:11:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.76,0:11:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,9
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.02,0:11:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.18,0:11:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.35,0:11:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.48,0:11:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.44,0:11:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.44,0:11:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.69,0:11:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2——…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.07,0:11:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.37,0:11:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,0
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.24,0:12:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那请大家从后面传上来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.64,0:12:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万圣节 早就结束了哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.99,0:12:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这咖啡 有点不像咖啡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.49,0:12:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 不像咖啡？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.79,0:12:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.87,0:12:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我自己也不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.96,0:12:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说好呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.87,0:12:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是不像咖啡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.00,0:12:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说啦 你尝尝看？ 来来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不像咖啡什么的是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.34,0:12:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像咖啡！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.69,0:13:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.52,0:13:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于完成啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.11,0:13:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是Biscuit 2号
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.90,0:13:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Biscuit 2号
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.57,0:13:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 前段时间的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.24,0:13:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反应 好冷淡！！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.83,0:13:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 我想让你好好看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.54,0:13:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 之前我们也看过了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.41,0:13:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1号和2号是不同的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.79,0:13:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加 更～加厉害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.84,0:13:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是Biscuit 2号
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.92,0:13:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是东云博士做的Biscuit机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.01,0:13:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就如名字一样 动力源是饼干
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.64,0:13:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了饼干 我就能够劳动
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.10,0:13:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 差不多该给我饼干…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.19,0:13:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.31,0:13:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最后一个了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.91,0:14:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Biscuit 2号的特技是速读
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.58,0:14:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.41,0:14:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.50,0:14:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.21,0:14:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不吃惊呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.87,0:14:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我也能速读啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.00,0:14:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 为什么总是读得磨磨蹭蹭的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.17,0:14:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.26,0:14:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有普通人的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.14,0:14:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么了？ Biscuit 2号
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.27,0:14:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,书上文字太多了 有点犯困呐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.73,0:14:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是有点普通的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.07,0:14:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不说好厉害！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.78,0:14:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明博士非常厉害！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.49,0:14:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 因为那种事情生气的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.16,0:14:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是那种事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.48,0:14:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬要说 博士从一开始就非常厉害的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.33,0:14:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 博士我好像有点搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.37,0:14:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得并不是搞错了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.46,0:14:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 博士有多么厉害？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.13,0:14:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 可能是秩父连山程度的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.13,0:15:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那根本听不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.47,0:15:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那纳拉伯平原之类的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.47,0:15:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 更大点的比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.68,0:15:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 鲸鱼之类的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.39,0:15:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 可能是那个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.06,0:15:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为鲸鱼很大呐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.69,0:15:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很大呐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.27,0:15:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.53,0:15:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有“那样就行”之类的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.33,0:15:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有“这样就行”之类的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.04,0:15:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.84,0:15:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 准备了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.51,0:15:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备了双六
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.93,0:15:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 准备了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.05,0:15:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备了猜谜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.39,0:15:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜谜的话 和和气气的很有趣的吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.01,0:15:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 让公主开心的话就能得到一笔钱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.93,0:15:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是很有意思的娱乐活动呐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.31,0:15:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不时常有些乐趣可受不了的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.36,0:15:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.36,0:16:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才 球是放进了这边的 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.95,0:16:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际是 在这边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.20,0:16:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错啊 66号
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.16,0:16:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然有这种特技啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.41,0:16:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上 偷偷的以王室专属魔术师为目标来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.29,0:16:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那样的话 你可就安宁了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.21,0:16:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.88,0:16:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我燃起来了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.46,0:16:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要得到那一笔钱！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.30,0:16:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 时间到了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.98,0:16:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安静
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.85,0:16:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad0\pos(751,170)\frz354.392\c&H0E171D&}侍\N从
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.19,0:16:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 按照刚才发下去的签的顺序开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.61,0:16:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到一号的人 上前来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.44,0:16:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我开始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.82,0:16:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 直接就从66号开始吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.36,0:16:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定要拿那笔钱了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.32,0:16:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专属魔术师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.37,0:16:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住你的梦想哦 66号！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.33,0:16:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.00,0:16:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.42,0:17:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 球在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.51,0:17:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要成为 专属魔术师…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.01,0:17:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.52,0:17:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到二号的人 上前来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.64,0:17:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于要到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.81,0:17:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将我的名声让世人知道的时刻！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.65,0:17:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我把这危机化为机会！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.48,0:17:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}谁啊 哦诶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.53,0:17:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.74,0:17:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幽默的四号
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.99,0:17:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.32,0:17:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的大笑话的话肯定能行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.32,0:17:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四号 请允许我来演出
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.50,0:17:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.80,0:17:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}拿到三号的人 上前来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.46,0:17:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到… 竟然连四号
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.88,0:17:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 没关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.80,0:17:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.64,0:17:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才说 猜谜什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.10,0:17:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.22,0:17:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟然会这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.89,0:17:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我的长处就只有猜谜了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.85,0:18:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时一定要让公主说出正确答案…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.15,0:18:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 绝对不允许出错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.03,0:18:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要出一个特别简单的问题…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.57,0:18:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我是6号
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.07,0:18:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请允许我给公主出个谜！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.20,0:18:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽… 虽说是面包
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.25,0:18:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不能吃的面包是什～～么呐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.34,0:18:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个问题有两个选项！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.42,0:18:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1是煎锅 2是菠萝包
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.42,0:18:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}煎锅：日文中即为Fry Pan的日式念法，Pan与日文的面包同音
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.38,0:18:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 是哪项！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.01,0:18:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.56,0:18:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.90,0:18:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这是正确答案！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.61,0:18:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.15,0:18:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无悔恨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.65,0:18:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.08,0:18:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.16,0:18:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连猜谜大师也滚蛋啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.37,0:18:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.33,0:18:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我… 我是七号
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.50,0:19:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请允许我说一下全部的奥运会举办城市
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.13,0:19:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.17,0:19:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的勇气 我们不会忘记的哦 七号！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.72,0:19:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.76,0:19:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有谁能够让公主高兴么！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.51,0:19:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.89,0:19:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来想来啦啦队女孩的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.48,0:19:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个笨蛋 我还准备用屁股折断一次性筷子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.35,0:19:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备来南京玉帘的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.35,0:19:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs42}南京玉帘：日本的一种街头表演
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.19,0:19:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是要来把卷心菜切成细丝的哟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.44,0:19:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们全员… 都要被消灭了…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.20,0:19:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶哦诶…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.50,0:19:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我忘了的话可不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.75,0:19:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.88,0:19:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那副诙谐的样子就能看出来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.63,0:19:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是幽默届无人能出其右的谐星
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.76,0:19:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诙谐13
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.76,0:19:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\pos(689,656)}Thirteen
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.47,0:19:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我来一个起死回生的表演
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.30,0:19:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改变一下这场面的气氛吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.22,0:20:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 13号！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.60,0:20:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么说都太危险了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.90,0:20:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们还以为我只是来跳一支天鹅湖的舞的么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.36,0:20:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 仔细看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.16,0:20:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的幽默这种东西由我来教给…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.41,0:20:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.56,0:20:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吧——！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.79,0:20:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诙谐13～～！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.79,0:20:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\pos(597,656)}Thirteen
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.25,0:20:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧…为什么连我都…！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.13,0:20:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 五号
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.50,0:20:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让我们等到什么时候啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.80,0:20:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快出来！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.63,0:20:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快出去！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.17,0:20:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五号那家伙！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.09,0:20:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.80,0:20:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.13,0:20:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是！！ 这是我帽子的号啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.97,0:20:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.80,0:20:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.47,0:20:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦… 哦诶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.60,0:20:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五号 不是你么…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.35,0:20:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.19,0:20:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 五号！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.23,0:20:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多赶紧出来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.44,0:20:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是哪个家伙！？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.62,0:21:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.49,0:21:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.50,0:21:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个 谁都可以啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.66,0:21:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.75,0:21:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.58,0:21:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么挣扎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.71,0:21:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.17,0:21:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.23,0:21:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.31,0:21:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管有几条命 都不够啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.69,0:21:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种任性的娱乐活动…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.86,0:21:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧玩儿蛋去吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.84,0:21:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去走廊里站着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.28,0:23:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\move(1390,710,-2420,710)}我是为你送上甜点一刻的追加了一小杯加焦糖酱榛子糖浆巧克力豆额外打过的浓咖啡的大号的白巧克力摩卡星冰乐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.21,0:23:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话日常是第十九话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.36,0:23:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.97,0:22:04.77,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}ある日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.85,0:22:09.40,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}パパとふたりで語り合ったさ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.94,0:22:13.65,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}この世に生きる喜び
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.65,0:22:16.32,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}そして悲しみのことを
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.36,0:22:19.24,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}グリーン　グリーン
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.41,0:22:23.37,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}青空には小鳥が歌い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.24,0:22:26.12,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}グリーン　グリーン
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.37,0:22:30.29,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}丘の上には　ララ　緑がもえる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.79,0:22:32.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}その時
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.67,0:22:37.26,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}パパが言ったさ　ぼくを胸に抱き
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.72,0:22:44.18,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}つらく悲しいときにも　ラララ　泣くんじゃないと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.14,0:22:47.02,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}グリーン　グリーン
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.22,0:22:51.27,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}青空にはそよ風吹いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.11,0:22:53.94,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}グリーン　グリーン
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.19,0:22:58.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}丘の上には　ララ　緑がゆれる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.61,0:23:01.61,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}緑がひろがる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.12,0:23:05.08,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}緑がひろがる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.58,0:23:18.67,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\blur3}緑がひろがる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.97,0:22:04.77,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}某一天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.85,0:22:09.40,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}和爸爸两个人聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.94,0:22:13.65,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}关于活在这世上的喜悦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.65,0:22:16.32,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}还有悲伤的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.36,0:22:19.24,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}Green Green
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.41,0:22:23.37,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}蓝天之上小鸟在歌唱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.24,0:22:26.12,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}Green Green
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.37,0:22:30.29,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}那山丘之上啊 啦啦 一片绿色在萌芽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.79,0:22:32.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.67,0:22:37.26,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}爸爸说了啊 拥抱我的胸膛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.72,0:22:44.18,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}难过悲伤的时候 啦啦啦 千万不要哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.14,0:22:47.02,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}Green Green
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.22,0:22:51.27,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}蓝天之上微风轻轻地吹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.11,0:22:53.94,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}Green Green
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.19,0:22:58.11,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}那山丘之上啊 啦啦 一片绿色在摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.61,0:23:01.61,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}一片绿色蔓延开来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.12,0:23:05.08,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}一片绿色蔓延开来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.58,0:23:18.67,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)\blur3}一片绿色蔓延开来


