[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-01 23:04:02
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 日常 第17話
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,45,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.70,0:00:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.95,0:00:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便去一趟防火水槽好么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.87,0:00:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.04,0:00:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那哪是女高中生该“顺便”去的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.37,0:00:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了对了 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.25,0:00:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去的时候要不要顺便去趟大工咖啡店？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.30,0:00:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点餐系统什么的有些变化
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.01,0:00:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对麻衣来说可能有些难吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.76,0:00:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.64,0:00:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以教你各种各样的事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.03,0:00:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻… 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.95,0:00:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.37,0:00:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Asymmetry
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.37,0:00:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}注：非对称
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.29,0:00:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 虽说是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.62,0:00:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是唯心式非对称哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.12,0:00:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超越了时髦的经典了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.12,0:01:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚我是在装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.13,0:01:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投球太过全力了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.30,0:01:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.22,0:01:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.27,0:01:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都是赢家啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.06,0:01:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天在…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.65,0:01:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣的一方呐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.56,0:03:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的饭菜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.55,0:03:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么好呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.97,0:03:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,葱好像便宜一些
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.18,0:03:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要用葱做点菜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.31,0:03:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是博士她
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.69,0:03:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不喜欢吃葱啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.65,0:03:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～ 名乃～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.87,0:03:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.45,0:03:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃你看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.45,0:03:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抓到一只乌鸦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.00,0:03:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.50,0:03:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.63,0:03:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很危险啊 手会被啄到的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.80,0:03:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.09,0:03:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.39,0:03:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.70,0:04:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.75,0:04:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不在这里么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.80,0:04:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道什么时候围巾没了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.05,0:04:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是乌鸦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.43,0:04:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后 请您记住我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.89,0:04:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸亏是一只懂礼貌的乌鸦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.64,0:04:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是乌鸦嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.52,0:04:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙您夸奖 是我的光荣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.02,0:04:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要喝草莓牛奶么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.02,0:04:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要喝吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.15,0:04:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝的话很可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.16,0:04:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蚊子？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.66,0:04:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.58,0:04:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我们杀虫什么的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.87,0:04:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.12,0:04:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不过是在做该做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.96,0:04:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是乌鸦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.80,0:05:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.38,0:05:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生 围巾哪去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.55,0:05:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有围巾的话就不知道你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.43,0:05:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来听听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.22,0:05:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.52,0:05:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.27,0:05:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是想要我的围巾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.07,0:05:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.86,0:05:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是你的吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.37,0:05:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 难道你把阪本先生的围巾给乌鸦带上了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.09,0:05:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 真不光彩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.65,0:05:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那样的话阪本先生就很可怜了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.38,0:05:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 我去做去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.84,0:05:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.26,0:05:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.10,0:05:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是Biscuit 1号
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.64,0:05:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟围巾没关！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.85,0:05:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说博士
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.35,0:06:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Biscuit 1号 有什么机能呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.65,0:06:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌鸦 问得好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.65,0:06:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有Rocket Punch机能
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.61,0:06:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那来了哦——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.11,0:06:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1 2
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.28,0:06:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发射 光当！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.71,0:06:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.29,0:06:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该给阪本先生做 做围巾了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.96,0:06:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.38,0:06:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为还有左手的啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.01,0:06:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1 2
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.09,0:06:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发射 光当！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.14,0:06:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀死…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.47,0:06:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这些家伙杀死！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.44,0:06:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.48,0:06:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真的是非常开心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.69,0:06:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有点过于淘气了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.15,0:06:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个围巾就请还给阪本先生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.99,0:06:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只有很短的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.57,0:06:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但能说人类的话我很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.62,0:06:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌鸦…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.66,0:07:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走 乌鸦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.94,0:07:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.54,0:07:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有机会的话再见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.63,0:07:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 大家保重
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.22,0:07:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,See you again！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.60,0:07:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌鸦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.35,0:07:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌鸦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.64,0:07:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我拿走啦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.90,0:07:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\c&HD6A6FE&\pos(622,498)}与爱有关的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.03,0:07:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦… 课长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.11,0:07:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.24,0:07:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.57,0:07:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.62,0:07:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.95,0:07:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不信任我么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.37,0:07:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.79,0:07:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.08,0:07:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全面信任课长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.79,0:07:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那就助我一臂之力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.51,0:07:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.48,0:12:19.48,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\pos(800,360)\shad3\4c&HE2DEE5&}体\N育\N馆\N后\N1
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.94,0:12:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天在体育馆后面挖了一个陷阱还放进去了黏合剂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.36,0:12:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这封信把她叫出来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.15,0:12:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她掉到陷阱里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.94,0:12:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs36\shad0\bord0\c&H2E2E2E&\pos(442,389)\frz13.348}Dear\N\h\h东云 名乃 大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.46,0:12:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天把你捕获哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.20,0:12:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云名乃…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.88,0:12:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.82,0:12:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的！！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.37,0:13:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到 樱井诚竟是樱井老师的弟弟啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.46,0:13:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做点什么 问出来点樱井老师的讯息
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.97,0:13:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.72,0:13:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能玩围棋足球吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.85,0:13:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.31,0:13:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 樱井
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.15,0:13:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.53,0:13:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有现在 在交往的男朋友吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.11,0:13:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,No Future!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.66,0:13:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.49,0:13:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这个男人 我这个男人…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.08,0:13:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.20,0:13:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.24,0:13:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是没有… 倒是没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.75,0:13:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.75,0:14:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.46,0:14:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好啦——！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.75,0:14:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好勒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.92,0:14:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好勒～～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.88,0:14:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个——…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.24,0:14:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.05,0:14:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才就当我没说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.01,0:14:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.59,0:14:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在玩围棋足球吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.89,0:14:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…我倒是在玩
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.26,0:14:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.72,0:14:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢我家的老姐么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.19,0:14:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说… 说什么蠢话哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.23,0:14:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是身为围棋足球部的前辈才问一下的啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.61,0:14:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师 你也有玩过围棋足球吗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.57,0:14:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那必须的哟！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.91,0:14:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高中可是MVP来的哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.20,0:14:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.04,0:14:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我们围棋足球部现在没有顾问
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.71,0:14:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果来做我们的顾问的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.92,0:14:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于我家老姐的事我可以全面协助哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.96,0:14:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢…不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.26,0:14:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了并不是… 喜欢嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.72,0:14:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不来做顾问的话 我就将老师喜欢姐姐的事情传出去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.39,0:14:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.60,0:14:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.68,0:14:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来做顾问吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.52,0:15:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.77,0:15:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不来做吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.19,0:15:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.19,0:15:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.86,0:15:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.48,0:15:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顾问好麻烦…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.65,0:15:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 大家听我说啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.78,0:15:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}这就行动了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.15,0:15:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要… 要去追咯！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.24,0:15:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.45,0:15:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在体育馆后面 中之条君被埋起来了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.20,0:15:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.33,0:15:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你马上来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.29,0:15:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 高崎先生他啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.04,0:15:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.84,0:15:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着啊… 听好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.05,0:15:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.97,0:15:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中之条啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.64,0:15:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没被埋着！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.39,0:15:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.47,0:15:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啦！！说不定是一杆进洞！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.18,0:15:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.22,0:15:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是头发被剃光了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.69,0:15:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.44,0:15:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画上去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.02,0:15:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.73,0:15:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试试
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.48,0:15:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.23,0:15:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.86,0:15:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.82,0:15:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 怎么回事啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.53,0:15:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶 喝茶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.65,0:15:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起被埋起来 管理暴露他人隐私的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.20,0:15:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更应该是身为教育者的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.70,0:16:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么呐！！ 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.54,0:16:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教育者啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.66,0:16:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高崎老师！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.70,0:16:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.37,0:16:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有说哦——
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.25,0:16:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说那个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.87,0:16:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顾问 等着你来当！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.75,0:16:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这家伙～～！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.55,0:16:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安中！！走吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.67,0:16:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.88,0:16:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.80,0:16:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是 教师吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.68,0:16:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这边！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.06,0:16:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.64,0:16:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是顺势而为
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.27,0:16:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过把头发剃下来了真是抱歉呐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.89,0:16:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去帮帮他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.19,0:16:36.52,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\shad3\4c&HE2DEE5&\pos(1100,360)}体\N育\N馆\N后\N2
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.85,0:16:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正他也不知道是我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.28,0:16:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.46,0:16:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}啊咧？啊咧咧…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.32,0:16:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这什么啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.32,0:16:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.61,0:16:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.41,0:16:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.45,0:16:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.58,0:16:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动不了啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.33,0:16:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.20,0:16:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.49,0:16:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头发…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.54,0:16:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎怎怎怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.71,0:16:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.50,0:16:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.92,0:16:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头发…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.34,0:16:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,swim swim
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.20,0:17:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼鲨鱼啪嗒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.04,0:17:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼鲨鱼啪嗒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.14,0:17:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话就是这样哒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.10,0:17:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad5\4c&HBBC1BC&\c&H44A030&\fad(0,1000)}琪{\c&H12C6E7&}琪 {\c&H1900B9&}是{\c&H8476F6&}这{\c&H9E9250&}个{\c&H4C6356&}样{\c&H8945C9&}子{\c&HB2AD76&}的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.29,0:17:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.97,0:18:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.68,0:18:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吐槽你的！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.81,0:18:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底 本来就是麻衣不好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.61,0:18:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机械似的不停的装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.36,0:18:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直一直 都是我在吐槽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.49,0:18:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话就会陷入装傻与吐槽的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.33,0:18:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无限循环？！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.12,0:18:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是少女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.91,0:18:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 本该是闭月羞花的少女哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.17,0:18:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.09,0:18:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连像普通女高中生该有的对话都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.13,0:18:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今天开始 一定不会吐槽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.97,0:18:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意志比钻石都坚硬啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.35,0:18:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.64,0:18:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 早上…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.85,0:18:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,W眼镜！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.85,0:18:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\pos(545,655)}双重
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.86,0:18:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强烈！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.77,0:18:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天好强烈！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.98,0:18:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有今天格外强烈！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.32,0:19:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不能输！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.86,0:19:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我——
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.70,0:19:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之间要有所改变！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.20,0:19:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻衣 selamat pagi
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.20,0:19:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}注：印尼语早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.83,0:19:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 现在就是让我们的女生对话之花绽放的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.29,0:19:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.71,0:19:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的“筋肉挽歌”看了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.76,0:19:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.67,0:19:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪哪哪 哪边？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.10,0:19:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜 眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.85,0:19:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么高频的装傻是怎么回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.27,0:19:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直像是在等着我的吐槽…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.69,0:19:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.19,0:19:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能吐槽哦 小佑！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.28,0:19:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是陷阱！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.15,0:19:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊水上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.53,0:19:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带了两副眼镜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.57,0:19:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田中这混蛋——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.24,0:19:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将我的吐槽…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.66,0:19:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有我被允许吐的… 最高级槽给！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.54,0:19:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 不对不对
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.83,0:19:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.00,0:19:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那并不是我的吐槽啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.25,0:19:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.63,0:20:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天第一堂课是国语来的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.05,0:20:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.34,0:20:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来理科的中村好像倒了哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.80,0:20:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 没关系吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.72,0:20:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对了 今天第一堂课是国语来的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.56,0:20:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对！ 刚才不是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.27,0:20:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好危险——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.52,0:20:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这姑娘为什么同样的台词说了两次？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.40,0:20:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.86,0:20:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超可怕啊 这姑娘！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.74,0:20:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.49,0:20:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值日生 喊号
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.15,0:20:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起立
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.61,0:20:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.62,0:20:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请左
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.79,0:20:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 开始上课了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.00,0:20:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}开启第82页哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.29,0:20:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请左什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.58,0:20:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请左什么的算什么啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.84,0:20:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且全员完全无视啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.46,0:20:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那… 有人想读一下么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.38,0:20:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.72,0:20:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻… 麻衣！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.10,0:20:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 水上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.26,0:20:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.52,0:21:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}山在阴影中很是寂静
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.81,0:21:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而… 而且
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.94,0:21:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}村中灯火点点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.44,0:21:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在读就说明——
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.69,0:21:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}初次来的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.49,0:21:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在读就说明…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.49,0:21:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说明…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.78,0:21:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说明…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.08,0:21:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)}全背下来了啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.73,0:21:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.19,0:21:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吐槽什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.15,0:21:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.78,0:21:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服 啊——
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.59,0:22:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说话这么大声 对不起啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.35,0:22:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去走廊站着！！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.39,0:22:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 这样就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.19,0:22:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 这是我的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.19,0:22:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.99,0:22:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也因为这是麻衣的道路——
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.53,0:22:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.83,0:22:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实从今天早晨开始
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.00,0:22:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就带了隐形眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.17,0:22:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜 不是没意义嘛！！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.93,0:22:58.93,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\shad2\pos(150,360)\4c&HE8EAEB&}被\N炉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.73,0:23:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.69,0:23:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好好盖被睡觉的话会感冒的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.28,0:23:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.53,0:23:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再稍微一会就好…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.12,0:23:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一会？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.04,0:23:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被耍了！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.97,0:24:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.81,0:25:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.06,0:25:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本先生也要进被子里睡哦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.36,0:25:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果 最后还是带走了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.45,0:25:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是黑桃3！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.07,0:25:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩大富豪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.80,0:25:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是最小的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.81,0:25:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要是发起革命的话
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.72,0:25:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一下子就变成最大的了！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.82,0:25:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是男人的话就一定要以下克上为目标哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.39,0:25:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话的日常是第十八话
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.37,0:25:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.59,0:23:40.77,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}真赤な太陽　沈む砂漠に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.18,0:23:47.36,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}大きな怪獣が　のんびり暮らしてた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.69,0:23:50.65,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}ある朝　目覚めたら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.03,0:23:57.24,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}遠くにキャラバンの鈴の音聞こえたよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.62,0:24:00.49,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}思わず叫んだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.79,0:24:07.17,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}海が見たい　人を愛したい
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.42,0:24:16.18,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,800)\blur3}怪獣にも　心はあるのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.72,0:24:22.64,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}出かけよう　砂漠すてて
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.93,0:24:32.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,800)\blur3}愛と海のあるところ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.57,0:24:42.58,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}あたらしい太陽は燃える
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.74,0:24:53.01,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,800)\blur3}愛と海のあるところ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.59,0:23:40.77,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}在一片通红的太阳西沉的沙漠里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.18,0:23:47.36,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}一头很大的怪兽悠闲的度日
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.69,0:23:50.65,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}某一个早晨 从睡眠中醒来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.03,0:23:57.24,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}听到了远远传来的一阵驼铃声
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.62,0:24:00.49,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}不假思索的喊出了口
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.79,0:24:07.17,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}好想去看海  好想爱上人们
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.42,0:24:16.18,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,800)\blur3}就算是怪兽 也有美好心灵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.72,0:24:22.64,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}出去远行吧  离开这片沙漠
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.93,0:24:32.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,800)\blur3}到那有爱与海的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.57,0:24:42.58,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur3}有一轮新的太阳熊熊燃烧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.74,0:24:53.01,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,800)\blur3}在那有爱与海的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.42,0:01:28.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.71,0:01:29.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.26,0:01:32.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.80,0:01:38.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}はい　言っちゃいましょ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.18,0:01:39.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}キミは　Best Best Friend!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.94,0:01:42.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.23,0:01:44.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと　ふざけてみたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.31,0:01:44.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.60,0:01:46.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと　ふざけ返してくる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.73,0:01:48.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.48,0:01:49.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居心地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.15,0:01:50.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいったら　ありゃしない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.53,0:01:51.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.86,0:01:53.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イヤなことあったって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.91,0:01:54.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.20,0:01:57.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}そっこー　忘れちゃうんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.32,0:01:57.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.91,0:01:58.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.62,0:02:00.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃんじゃん　やりましょー！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.66,0:02:03.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}２４時間　一緒でも　問題ない！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:05.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}まるで　双子か　親子か　クローンさいぼー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.50,0:02:08.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,655)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}これじゃ　恋愛する　必要とか　なくなくない？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.75,0:02:10.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}それと　これとは　全く全く　別問題！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.67,0:02:11.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.01,0:02:13.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}ケンカしちゃったときも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.09,0:02:13.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.42,0:02:15.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}かなり凹んだときも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.43,0:02:15.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,660)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.84,0:02:17.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}一人で　いたいよなときも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.89,0:02:22.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}ふと気づけば　近くにいるしなばもろともー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.89,0:02:25.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんでだろ　{\r}そばにいたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.90,0:02:28.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}キミと一緒なら　{\r}時計１００倍速！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.77,0:02:31.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}楽しいな　{\r}楽しすぎるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.69,0:02:32.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}さすが　最強Friend!　{\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.40,0:02:33.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ななななななな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.53,0:02:35.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}なんなのよ　{\r}やっばいシンクロ感
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.53,0:02:38.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}いつも大騒ぎ　{\r}かなり　ご近所迷惑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.32,0:02:40.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何時？　{\r}えっとね　ヨロレイヒー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.33,0:02:41.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,710)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}わけわかんないない！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.62,0:02:44.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ソーレードーシーラー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.21,0:02:46.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像以上！なんていうか最高！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.71,0:02:47.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}あーだーこーだー言ってても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.92,0:02:49.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}友達　わっしょい！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.13,0:02:50.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上々　友情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.29,0:02:51.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事　まじ　快調！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.84,0:02:55.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ちゃちゃら　ちゃらちゃちゃーん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.42,0:01:28.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.71,0:01:29.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.26,0:01:32.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.80,0:01:38.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}来 说出口来！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.18,0:01:39.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}你就是 Best Best Friend！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.94,0:01:42.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Bright!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.23,0:01:44.31,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 跟你胡闹一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.31,0:01:44.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Shine!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.60,0:01:46.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加 回敬我大闹一番
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.73,0:01:48.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.48,0:01:49.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.15,0:01:50.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提 有多爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.53,0:01:51.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Why
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.86,0:01:53.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算发生了一些不快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.91,0:01:54.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Fine
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.20,0:01:57.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}赶快 将这事情忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.32,0:01:57.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}Lan Lan Lan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.91,0:01:58.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.62,0:02:00.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要 精神满满！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.66,0:02:03.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}24小时 都在一起 也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:05.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}简直像 双胞胎 或亲子 克隆细胞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.50,0:02:08.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,65)\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这一来 陷入爱河 岂不就是 没必没必要？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.75,0:02:10.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}那件事 跟这件事 完全完全 两码事！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.67,0:02:11.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.01,0:02:13.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算我们吵架的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.09,0:02:13.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Down
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.42,0:02:15.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算非常低落的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.43,0:02:15.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\pos(640,60)}Shock
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.84,0:02:17.89,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}就算一人 深感寂寞的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.89,0:02:22.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H36F063&\4c&H36F063&}{\fad(0,1000)}不经意间发现 身旁的你可同我生与死都相随
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.89,0:02:25.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}这是为何 {\r}想要在你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.90,0:02:28.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}如果和你在一起 {\r}时间100倍速飞逝！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.77,0:02:31.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,800)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真快乐呐 {\r}有点快乐的过头啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.69,0:02:32.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}不愧是 最强Friend！ {\r}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.40,0:02:33.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.53,0:02:35.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}搞什么哦 {\r}同步率快要破表
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.53,0:02:38.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}总是太过于兴奋 {\r}周围都 相当受到困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.32,0:02:40.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,1000)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}今何时？ {\r}那个啊 哟啰咧咿呵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.33,0:02:41.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,10)}{\c&HC48DEC&\4c&HC48DEC&}真是莫名其妙！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.62,0:02:44.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sol Re Do Ti La
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.21,0:02:46.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}想像之外！ 无论如何最棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.71,0:02:47.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}说那说这不管怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.92,0:02:49.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}都是朋友 哇塞！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.13,0:02:50.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}上上 友情！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.29,0:02:51.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}万事 真正 顺利！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.84,0:02:55.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD040BE&\4c&HD040BE&}ChaChaRa ChaRaChaChan


