[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-03 13:28:01
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 日常 第12話
Original Script: 雪飄工作室
Original Translation: 愛蘇喵x石頭xtt
Original Editing: zwc
Original Timing: zhbconan
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,58,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,53,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.81,0:01:08.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}たった今　初めて気づいた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.48,0:01:11.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋に落ちたのだなー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.15,0:01:13.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h キミ☆　キミ☆　キミ☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.69,0:01:15.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意識せざるをえません！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.65,0:01:18.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}なんか　いつもと違う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.19,0:01:17.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.28,0:01:20.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}キミと　ぎこちない会話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.74,0:01:19.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.95,0:01:23.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}まさか　いや　片思い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.41,0:01:22.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両思い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.74,0:01:25.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やばい！　視線合っちゃった！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.16,0:01:29.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}なになに！？このドキドキ！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.38,0:01:35.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路　ぐっちゃぐちゃ　混線…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.13,0:01:41.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}こんなこと　初めてだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.80,0:01:47.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}熱でもあるのかなー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.47,0:01:50.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急転直下　いらっしゃた　恋心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.35,0:01:52.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっちゅうま　顔　発火で　まっかっか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.94,0:01:55.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}バ·バ…バカな！？　手が震えるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.61,0:01:58.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが　俗に言う　「恋」　なの！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.36,0:02:00.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}やややっちゃった　会話　噛みまくり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.95,0:02:03.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気まずい沈黙　マミムメモ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.61,0:02:06.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}キミの　気持ち　知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.20,0:02:04.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キミの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.28,0:02:08.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.16,0:02:12.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！　{\r}いつもの通学路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.08,0:02:15.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}ピカピカ光る　{\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.46,0:02:17.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}空も飛べそうさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.21,0:02:20.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.81,0:01:08.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}就在刚刚 才第一次注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.48,0:01:11.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陷入恋情了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.15,0:01:13.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h 是你☆  是你☆  是你☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.69,0:01:15.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全部都是你！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.65,0:01:18.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}总觉得 和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.19,0:01:17.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.28,0:01:20.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}我与你 慌慌张张的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.74,0:01:19.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.95,0:01:23.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}难道说 不对 单相思
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.41,0:01:22.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.74,0:01:25.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！ 跟他的眼睛对上了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.16,0:01:29.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}什么什么！？心里小鹿乱撞！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.38,0:01:35.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路 黏黏糊糊乱糟糟 串线…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.13,0:01:41.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这样的事情 第一次遇到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.80,0:01:47.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}是不是患上感冒了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.47,0:01:50.35,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急转直下 悄无声息来的 春心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.35,0:01:52.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一会的时间 脸 像着火 通红通红的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.94,0:01:55.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}笨·笨…笨蛋吗！？ 手正在发抖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.61,0:01:58.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 俗话说的 “爱” 的啦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.36,0:02:00.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}要要要要坏菜了啊 对话 咬到舌头了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.95,0:02:03.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难为情的沉默 āōēīū
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.61,0:02:06.28,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}想知道 你现在 心里所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.20,0:02:04.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.28,0:02:08.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.16,0:02:12.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！ {\r}好像上学走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.08,0:02:15.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}亮闪闪的发光 {\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.46,0:02:17.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}感觉好像能上天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.21,0:02:20.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.12,0:00:05.62,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1020,1020)\blur10\bord2\pos(800,360)}好\N夏\N天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.79,0:00:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs60\bord0\shad0\c&HFDF0D9&\pos(815,154)}凉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.79,0:00:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs60\bord0\shad0\pos(863,552)\c&H2330F4&}售罄
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.59,0:00:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀… 好热好热…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.67,0:00:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太热了——
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.43,0:00:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田中君 从刚才开始…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.97,0:00:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就光在说好热哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.77,0:00:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就已经够热的了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.52,0:00:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不停的说热的话会变得更热哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.23,0:00:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁止说“好热”！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.23,0:00:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK OK
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.94,0:00:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀… 好夏天好夏天…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.94,0:00:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热… 真的好夏天呐…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.49,0:00:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么哒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.82,0:00:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过可真的是好夏天！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.83,0:00:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也太夏天了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.16,0:00:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好夏天！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.04,0:00:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好夏天好夏天…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.33,0:00:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.75,0:00:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能揍他了…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.08,0:00:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 好夏天…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.58,0:00:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好夏天呐！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.88,0:00:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是——
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.09,0:00:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好夏天！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.09,0:02:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SHINY~
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.86,0:02:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不管什么看起来都是这么的耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.75,0:02:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空气也是 人们也是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.66,0:02:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 就连这教室都是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.42,0:02:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.34,0:02:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天 我终于做作业了啦——
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.98,0:02:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要给美绪看看…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.85,0:02:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,……啊咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.93,0:02:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.10,0:02:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧咧咧咧咧咧…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.85,0:03:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咧… 咧… 咧…？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.27,0:03:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木——有！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.28,0:03:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对不对不对不对
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.24,0:03:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能是那样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.41,0:03:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易 难得做一次作业的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.12,0:03:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.66,0:03:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥为啥为啥！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.83,0:03:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥木有了啊！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.83,0:03:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 看一下别人的不就行了嘛?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.12,0:03:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美～绪…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.34,0:03:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.05,0:03:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下哦 等下哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.51,0:03:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的作业
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.59,0:03:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是卷子——！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.34,0:03:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉——呦——喂——呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.85,0:03:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.48,0:03:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这大早上的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.73,0:03:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作业…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.27,0:03:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.65,0:03:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.94,0:03:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外星人的大侵略…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.57,0:03:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊 又忘记了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.44,0:03:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少瞧不起我啊！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.69,0:03:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是做完了忘记带来了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.57,0:03:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 才没有瞧不起你呐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.70,0:03:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作业是语文卷子吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.10,0:03:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是夹在哪里了哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.70,0:03:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细找找看？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.50,0:04:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就刚刚还找了好几遍呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.46,0:04:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对… 已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.21,0:04:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.34,0:04:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.17,0:04:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦——
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.90,0:04:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MY GOD！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.05,0:04:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大福展览会是个神马玩意——！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.43,0:04:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展览会是个… 什么玩意哟…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.77,0:04:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.10,0:04:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.31,0:04:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上讲桌那找一下 说不定会有卷子哟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.94,0:04:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧不是吧！！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.94,0:04:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.24,0:04:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶——！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.82,0:04:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.07,0:04:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可恶——！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.87,0:04:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去取么！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.95,0:04:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来不及了哦！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.75,0:04:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也得——
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.71,0:04:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去取！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.18,0:04:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 要上课了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.89,0:04:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到座位上去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.85,0:05:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咕噜*6
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.10,0:05:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转吧转吧转吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.44,0:05:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越急越要淡定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.90,0:05:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又被罚站了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.28,0:05:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么像这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.99,0:05:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次每次都把作业忘记了呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.66,0:06:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天更是 明明好不容易做完了 结果还是忘了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.66,0:06:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊你个大笨蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.48,0:06:30.48,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\pos(800,360)\bord2\blur10}名\N片
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.23,0:06:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阪本…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.69,0:06:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请收下我的名片
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.20,0:06:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\c&H020202&\frz354.726\pos(690,243)}博 士
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.82,0:06:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.03,0:06:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该咋办？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.83,0:06:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是咋回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.04,0:06:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该咋办！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.67,0:06:53.67,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs75\fad(520,520)\bord3\blur8\pos(1150,360)}自\N动\N贩\N卖\N机
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.30,0:07:00.01,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn黑体\fs36\c&HC94A3C&\b1\bord2\pos(211,168)}运动汽水
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.30,0:07:00.01,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn黑体\fs51\b1\bord2\shad0\c&H9A85D8&\3c&H767575&\pos(495,227)}H{\fs30}汽水{\c&H9B87CA&}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.30,0:07:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs51\bord3\shad0\c&HC0E8E1&\pos(788,211)\3c&H718ED5&}苹果醋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.30,0:07:00.01,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\pos(1085,301)\c&HDCD6D9&\3c&H10375E&\b0}BLACK
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.30,0:07:00.01,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\fn黑体\pos(641,523)\c&H0D2F92&}新发售          新发售
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.30,0:07:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\bord1\shad0\c&HF7EAE3&\3c&H5B4737&\pos(731,655)}凉                    凉                     凉                     凉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.93,0:07:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.56,0:07:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？ 立花美里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.23,0:07:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.90,0:07:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不过是因为出了新商品 在犹豫要买哪一个而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.49,0:07:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.91,0:07:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 这边的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.78,0:07:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能听你说的呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.20,0:07:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商品 很难喝…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.37,0:07:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以选旁边的商品比较好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.83,0:07:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰你了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.38,0:07:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是因为你推荐才买的呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.94,0:08:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord3\shad0\c&H524754&\3c&HCDCCD7&\frz30\pos(294,234)}射击
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.94,0:08:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord3\shad0\c&H524754&\3c&HCDCCD7&\pos(530,107)\frz30}展览会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.94,0:08:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21\shad0\bord0\c&H42414A&\frz17.518\pos(826,243)}大\N盘\N400\N元
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.94,0:08:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\shad0\bord2\c&H5877C3&\3c&HE2D1B6&\frz30\pos(967,230)}炒面
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.45,0:08:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,附近搭了几个摊子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.53,0:08:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以去看了看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.12,0:08:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说目标都是射击
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.89,0:08:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在电视上看过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.87,0:08:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以今天非常期待！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.21,0:08:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说如此 才带了500元啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.17,0:08:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.59,0:08:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 一次500万元哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.63,0:08:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,LUCKY 正好500元
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.17,0:08:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然也想吃炒面…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.13,0:08:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但毕竟今天是为了这个来的呐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.48,0:08:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有奶糖和茄子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.06,0:08:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.86,0:08:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这些么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.57,0:08:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有是什么话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.57,0:08:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这放的可都是名牌哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.54,0:08:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 仅有的一点钱也已经交出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.28,0:08:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能带那东西回去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.76,0:08:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.71,0:09:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一上来就瞄着贵的东西可不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.34,0:09:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个可不容易被打下来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.89,0:09:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵…？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.47,0:09:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要先瞄准要掉下来的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.60,0:09:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要掉下来的什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.10,0:09:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的不只有奶糖这一个选择了么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.86,0:09:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\shad0\bord0\pos(471,623)\c&H123774&}浓\N厚\N牛\N奶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.57,0:09:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\shad0\bord0\pos(471,623)\c&H9595AE&}浓\N厚\N牛\N奶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.86,0:09:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\shad0\bord0\c&H123774&\pos(795,623)}大\N工\N谨\N制
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.57,0:09:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\shad0\bord0\c&H123774&\pos(795,623)\c&H9595AE&}大\N工\N谨\N制
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.86,0:09:17.57,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad3\c&HDFF7FA&\4c&H2F3A56&\pos(633,555)}奶糖
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.57,0:09:18.73,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\bord0\shad3\c&HDFF7FA&\pos(633,555)\4c&HD3D4DD&}奶糖
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.03,0:09:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.91,0:09:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来 奶糖也完全黏在上面了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.08,0:09:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再有几毫米就掉下来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.04,0:09:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姑娘 你技术很不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.33,0:09:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 是现役职业枪手么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.50,0:09:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑哒！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.10,0:09:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然这茄子纹丝不动啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.64,0:09:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦 怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.89,0:09:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一副无精打采的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.43,0:09:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是觉得我们耍花招了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.44,0:09:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们虽然店铺破破烂烂的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.06,0:10:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神饱满和不耍花招可是素有评定的！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.90,0:10:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对不对 这绝对是有什么猫腻啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.76,0:10:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥！？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.55,0:10:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说… 那个那个 快看快看！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.47,0:10:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钉子 能看见钉子哦 钉子！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.97,0:10:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就是骗人的么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.60,0:10:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说… 为什么什么话都不说了啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.32,0:10:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 这样是不可以的吧？！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.74,0:10:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你不还精神满满的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.15,0:10:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么看来奶糖也动了手脚了吧？！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.08,0:10:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装什么睡啊你！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.79,0:10:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就剩一发了我该瞄什么啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.40,0:11:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也别来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.78,0:11:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是啥啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.74,0:11:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得很帅的东西！！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.71,0:11:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪～～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.76,0:11:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔了哦～～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.69,0:12:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NICE CATCH！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.90,0:12:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！ SUPER BALL！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.91,0:12:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得很帅的东西！！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.09,0:12:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！ 好可惜！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.57,0:12:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,WOW！！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.62,0:12:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！ SWEETS DREAM
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.17,0:13:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.26,0:13:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久没来游乐园了 好高兴呐——
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.91,0:13:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是来对了呢~
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.68,0:13:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想喝果汁 把钱包给我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.06,0:13:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对哈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.52,0:13:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放在我这里保管来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.43,0:13:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 抱歉呐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.85,0:13:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得自己拿着的话会丢的～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.31,0:13:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.94,0:13:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.94,0:13:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.28,0:13:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧咧咧咧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.36,0:13:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧… 啊咧咧咧咧咧…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.28,0:13:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 啊咧…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.66,0:13:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实… 应该是放在这里了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.62,0:13:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像只有小佑的钱包丢了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.18,0:13:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 去失物招领处的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.80,0:13:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会找到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.06,0:14:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多少钱啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.56,0:14:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4016元
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.98,0:14:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真详细呐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.35,0:14:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(600,410)\bord0\shad0\c&H1E2941&}失物招领处
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.35,0:14:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(1085,127)\c&HCFD7E0&}兔子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.81,0:14:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.61,0:14:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想找一个茶色的钱包 里面放有蛇皮…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.90,0:14:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.86,0:14:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 幸好在这找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.37,0:14:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 一时间都不知所措了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.00,0:14:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在播报一条寻人启事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.63,0:14:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位身着牛仔短裤牛仔衬衣带着牛仔帽的女孩在找妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.34,0:14:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相关人士请前往走失儿童中心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.04,0:15:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\shad0\bord0\c&H00020E&\pos(394,482)}坟\N墓
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.04,0:15:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最怕鬼屋了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.42,0:15:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来啦——！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.85,0:15:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 开始拍了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.85,0:15:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn黑体\fs45\an7\bord2\shad0\c&HA5B8CB&\3c&H828688&\pos(112,227)}冰\N淇\N淋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.23,0:15:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn黑体\fs45\an7\bord2\shad0\c&HA5B8CB&\3c&H828688&\pos(26,229)}冰\N淇\N淋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.21,0:15:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好3个 是带走吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.38,0:16:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.89,0:16:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.72,0:16:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我这个 这个和这个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.39,0:16:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个 不好意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.93,0:16:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您可以说出名字么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.73,0:16:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我是樱井
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.94,0:16:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不是那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.36,0:16:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是吗 不好意思！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.49,0:16:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫泉！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.61,0:16:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱井泉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.32,0:16:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.36,0:16:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是因为那个是姓才问你的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.99,0:16:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人一直都说我的姓和名听起来都像姓哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.00,0:16:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.47,0:16:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问名字是问商品名的那个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.38,0:16:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 商品名是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.09,0:16:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我不太明白…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.99,0:16:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不是 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.67,0:16:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之不好意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.18,0:16:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\bord2\shad0\c&HD1C8D0&\3c&H827275&\frz10.618\pos(802,114)}家庭餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.18,0:16:49.18,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\fn黑体\b0\bord2\c&HBFB0BF&\3c&H534662&\pos(838,628)}和\N风\N展\N览\N会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.56,0:16:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.18,0:16:54.19,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\bord2\blur6\pos(55,360)}筷\N子\N架
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.72,0:16:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饱了吃饱了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.25,0:16:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就等甜点登场了～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.02,0:16:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.28,0:17:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那我也来吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.88,0:17:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好啦～！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.72,0:17:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.81,0:17:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.23,0:17:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是麻衣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.02,0:17:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑怎么样？ 做好了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.40,0:17:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹤…？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.45,0:17:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃～快看快看～！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.79,0:17:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士也试着带上了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.35,0:17:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我们就配成对了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.81,0:17:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.27,0:18:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士今天是名乃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.44,0:18:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可以叫我博士哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.98,0:18:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 小名乃～！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.05,0:18:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.56,0:18:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 已经够了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.43,0:18:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 名乃 刚才你叫我博士了是吧？！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.14,0:18:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 因为你不是已经把发条拿下来了么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.94,0:18:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才就是稍微休息一下而已～！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.66,0:18:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是博士名乃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.32,0:18:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.21,0:18:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 不对…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.38,0:18:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小名乃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.21,0:18:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一起玩游戏么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.96,0:18:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好哦 玩什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.76,0:18:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来玩博士是我 我是博士的交换游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.51,0:18:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要玩！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.72,0:18:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 博士 不对…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.60,0:18:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小名乃请把发条装上！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.56,0:18:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.81,0:18:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 因为我是博士 请把我的发条拿下来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.69,0:18:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.23,0:19:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 玩些什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.94,0:19:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩卡牌么～？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.15,0:19:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\shad0\bord0\c&H135BCB&\frz354.811\pos(908,171)}小点心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.15,0:19:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs54\shad0\bord0\frz354.811\pos(836,382)\c&HDF8868&}一点{\c&H322CD3&}Q
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.70,0:19:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 零食真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.49,0:19:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是我非常珍惜的零食！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.04,0:19:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.33,0:19:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.25,0:19:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.92,0:19:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫名其妙嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.34,0:19:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士是名乃没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.38,0:19:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但名乃是博士的话就能吃点心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.38,0:19:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那名乃你就是名乃吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.97,0:19:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,螃蟹…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.22,0:19:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那既然我变回名乃了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.19,0:19:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就去买晚饭的菜了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.19,0:19:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士我也要去！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.82,0:19:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会买零食哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.49,0:19:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我买鲨鱼巧克力和草莓果汁嘛～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.70,0:19:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不买
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.65,0:19:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买嘛～～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.36,0:19:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不买
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.00,0:19:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦诶！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.97,0:19:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忘了我的饭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.75,0:19:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs42}鲨鱼巧克力和草莓果汁嘛～～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.33,0:19:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东云家 今天也很和睦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.08,0:20:03.25,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,0)\bord4\blur15\pos(800,360)}闲\N时\N游\N戏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.75,0:20:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\bord0\shad0\pos(947,128)\c&HDEDED7&}大家的街上\N{\c&H5E5C4F&}有大工汉堡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.75,0:20:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\bord0\shad0\c&H727473&\pos(903,288)}美味！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.92,0:20:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始说英文的话就输了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.05,0:20:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.30,0:20:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 刚才美绪说英语了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.22,0:20:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说START的话就SAFE哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.43,0:20:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那说START之前 先把英文说个够哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.82,0:20:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那么多英语么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.54,0:20:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.54,0:20:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.57,0:21:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碳酸会唰的一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.99,0:21:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睁开眼睛的话心情变得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.75,0:21:27.75,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(520,520)\shad2\pos(80,360)\3c&HD3E1E9&\4c&HD2E4ED&}一\N不\N小\N心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.34,0:21:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡着了…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.80,0:21:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哟 没有KISS睡美人就醒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.28,0:21:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.48,0:21:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问我为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.91,0:23:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 主人！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.29,0:23:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是汽水喵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.71,0:23:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会将变得美味的魔法咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.29,0:23:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,融到这些泡泡里哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.38,0:23:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话的日常是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.72,0:23:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十三话！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.93,0:23:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.75,0:22:07.67,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}朝起きて　歯を磨いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.92,0:22:10.67,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あっという間　午後10時
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.05,0:22:13.97,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　たくさん　笑ったなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.13,0:22:16.72,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}たくさん　ときめいたなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.26,0:22:20.18,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}友達と　バカみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:23.10,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}騒いでる　時にも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.43,0:22:26.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}チラチラって　目が合う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.56,0:22:29.15,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}…偶然、だよね。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.36,0:22:32.61,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋なんて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.82,0:22:35.78,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キャラじゃないんだもんっ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.95,0:22:41.79,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ねえ　あしたも会えるよね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:44.87,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}まぶたを　閉じると
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.12,0:22:48.08,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キラキラ　キミだらけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.25,0:22:51.38,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　楽しかったね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.55,0:22:55.80,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あー　恋　してんだなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.85,0:23:03.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}うれしいな　うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.98,0:23:06.77,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}はじめまして　こいごころ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.10,0:23:09.98,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あした　まだ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.23,0:23:12.65,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.36,0:23:17.41,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ゆめで　すぐ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.03,0:23:23.58,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.75,0:22:07.67,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}早晨睡醒后 起床刷牙来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.92,0:22:10.67,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}不知不觉间 已到晚十点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.05,0:22:13.97,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天也遇到 很多欢乐事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.13,0:22:16.72,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}也有非常多 刺激与紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.26,0:22:20.18,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}和闺中密友 像笨蛋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:23.10,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}大声吵又闹 偶尔会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.43,0:22:26.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶尔瞥向你 四目便相接
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.56,0:22:29.15,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}这也不过是 偶然事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.36,0:22:32.61,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋什么的难以说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.82,0:22:35.78,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}因为我不是这样的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.95,0:22:41.79,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}呐 我们明天 也会相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:44.87,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}将我的双眼 合上了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.12,0:22:48.08,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}脑海中只有 亮晶晶的你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.25,0:22:51.38,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天的我也 开心又愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.55,0:22:55.80,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}啊 陷入恋爱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.85,0:23:03.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}真的好开心 真的好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.98,0:23:06.77,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}第一次见面 我的爱慕心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.10,0:23:09.98,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}到明天的话 我们又见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.23,0:23:12.65,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.36,0:23:17.41,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}在梦中很快 我们会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.03,0:23:23.58,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}现在晚安吧


