[Script Info]
;  This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
;  For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;  go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;  or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;  
;  Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
;  http://www.anime-fansubs.org
;  
;  For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
;  or email gabest@freemail.hu
;  
;  Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
;  
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-03-02 12:25:58
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通_GBK,56,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,3,2,30,30,20,1
Style: TEXT,华康宋体W3-A,90,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00868686,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,58,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: XD,草檀斋毛泽东字体,66,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,48,&H00E69B47,&H00F3F3F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00E69B47,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通_GBK,53,&H00E69B47,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DEC0A1,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,3,8,30,30,10,1
Style: EDJP,ＤＦ華康明朝体W5,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.10,0:00:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 那开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.78,0:00:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头 剪刀 布
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.56,0:00:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.15,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\pos(640,160)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}格\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\an8\fs27}格力高：猜拳胜者根据规则上台阶的游戏。出石头赢则边说“格力高（GU RI KO）”边上三\N个台阶 ；出剪刀赢则边说“巧克力（CHI YO KO RE I/E TO)”边上六个台阶 ；出布赢则边说\N“菠萝（PA I NA TSU PU RU）“边上六个台阶。最先到达最上面的台阶等规定地点的人获胜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.15,0:00:10.15,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\pos(640,160)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}\h\h\h\h力\h\h\h\h
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.31,0:00:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 那从我开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.65,0:00:10.15,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\pos(640,160)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&}\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h高
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.18,0:00:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs27}注释：菠萝
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.18,0:00:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,PA·I·NA·TSU·PU·RU
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.39,0:00:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头 剪刀 布
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.63,0:00:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.50,0:00:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦 规定好了一次一个台阶的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.41,0:00:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.52,0:00:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GU·RI·KO
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.98,0:00:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…的 附赠品
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.00,0:00:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.36,0:00:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.47,0:00:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么随便加东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.38,0:00:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？我就是加了个普普通通的“附赠品”嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.56,0:00:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 麻衣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.83,0:00:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一半一半
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.83,0:00:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 这样也行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.76,0:00:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你要是这么来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.82,0:00:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也启动我自己的规则了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.96,0:00:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头剪刀布
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.24,0:01:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 接下来是麻衣了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.05,0:01:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CHI·YO·TA
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.47,0:01:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NI·KE·RA·HA·TO·HO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.17,0:01:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RA·SU·TE·NO·HA·TE·KI
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.12,0:01:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RA·TO·NA·RI·HA·SHI·TE·TO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.76,0:01:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复活的咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.25,0:03:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.16,0:03:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 妈妈 不是跟你说了7点叫我起床的么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.72,0:03:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.85,0:03:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\bord0\shad0\c&H212122&\frz30.555\pos(291,351)}美\N绪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.85,0:03:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\bord0\shad0\c&H212122&\frz30.555\pos(326,569)}我\N去\N和\N町\N内\N会\N的\N人\N们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.85,0:03:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\bord0\shad0\c&H212122&\frz30.555\pos(194,488)}踢\N藤\N球\N去\N了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.85,0:03:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs33\bord0\shad0\c&H212122&\frz30.555\pos(183,614)}妈\N妈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.85,0:03:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}町内会：类似于国内的街道委员会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.49,0:03:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤 藤球
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.85,0:03:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.43,0:03:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天还是值日生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.45,0:03:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闹钟也是 为什么偏偏今天没电了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.80,0:03:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 没电了就事先告诉我一声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.26,0:03:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个白痴傻瓜！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.26,0:03:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}スカポンタン：1976《时间飞船》里大姐头约尼训斥部下的经典台词
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.69,0:03:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 以最后一圈的速度冲刺的话 说不定能…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.49,0:04:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 刚才
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.23,0:04:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个可怕的东西！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.48,0:04:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且好像 来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.66,0:04:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么什么什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.03,0:04:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个短跑员
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.87,0:04:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 在 追我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.66,0:04:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超过去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.02,0:04:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.15,0:04:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.86,0:05:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个木鱼 是你掉的么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.70,0:05:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是金木鱼么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.33,0:05:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要被干掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.52,0:05:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不做点什么的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.33,0:05:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要被干掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.35,0:05:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.43,0:05:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的时候是熊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.31,0:05:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而有的时候也是 熊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.72,0:05:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.76,0:05:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的真面目是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.88,0:05:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱 抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.30,0:06:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锵 正确答案是姐姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.34,0:06:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着美绪的校服所以不知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.82,0:06:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真有趣…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.77,0:06:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大早就能见到如此精湛的螺旋突刺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.06,0:06:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是很出色的一击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.57,0:06:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不是 我也很辛苦的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.53,0:06:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关掉闹钟也费了很大劲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.88,0:06:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你是犯人啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.95,0:06:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别别 别那么生气嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.91,0:06:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 用这些钱请你吃拉面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.91,0:06:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}野口：野口英世 一千日元纸币上的头像
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.91,0:06:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的野口！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.00,0:06:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CHI·YO·TA
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.29,0:06:36.25,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&\pos(1220,360)}咒\N语
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.50,0:06:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NI·KE·RA·HA·TO
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.41,0:06:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HO·RA·SU·TE·NO·HA·TE·KI
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.75,0:06:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RA·TO·NA·RI·HA·SHI·TE·TO
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.39,0:06:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\bord0\shad0\c&HE2E2E2&\pos(640,150)}请输入复活的咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.14,0:06:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\bord0\shad0\c&HE2E2E2&\pos(640,410)}咒语错误
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.07,0:06:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 鲨鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.78,0:07:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.41,0:07:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.03,0:07:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 博士你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.66,0:07:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 那片云朵 好像鲨鱼！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.62,0:07:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 哪一片啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.79,0:07:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.42,0:07:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好帅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.72,0:07:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.31,0:07:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.25,0:07:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.29,0:07:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你买来了哦 牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.57,0:07:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\an8}注释：特浓4.5是牛奶产品
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.57,0:07:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 4.5 4.5
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.58,0:07:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs39}呐 牛奶 4.5 牛奶 4.5
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.72,0:07:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 特浓的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.91,0:07:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是怎么了 突然想喝牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.58,0:07:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是因为啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.03,0:08:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有瑞士卷哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.56,0:08:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 你怎么随便改造啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.11,0:08:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有瑞士卷哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.60,0:08:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫名其妙！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.99,0:08:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名乃 4.5牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.46,0:08:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么4.5啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.53,0:08:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我非得手腕里带着瑞士卷生活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.58,0:08:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉凉的真好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.16,0:08:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是这个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.53,0:08:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 出去了要是这副样子被别人看到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.06,0:08:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 咕噜咕噜咕噜 咕噜噜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.64,0:08:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.14,0:08:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.19,0:08:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我也想吃点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.15,0:09:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.42,0:09:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.20,0:09:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 请
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.87,0:09:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.67,0:09:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.42,0:09:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞士卷我也想…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.20,0:09:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 那名乃就来点小甜面包
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.03,0:09:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.27,0:09:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.56,0:09:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啊 按错了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.24,0:09:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就 就说了为什么要做这种东西啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.77,0:09:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得要是因为内部原因在外面启动了的话会怎样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.24,0:09:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.70,0:09:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.58,0:09:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}徒手格斗专家太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.16,0:09:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs39\blur2}对啊对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.83,0:09:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3}啊 好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.46,0:10:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音乐播放机能也想加上呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.17,0:10:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.71,0:10:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么变成改造方向了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.05,0:10:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请仔细听着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.34,0:10:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.61,0:10:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.87,0:10:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.30,0:10:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小甜面包
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.62,0:10:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.72,0:10:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士你都已经吃了瑞士卷了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.90,0:11:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.95,0:11:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便吧 反正还有年轮蛋糕！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.20,0:11:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧 这次会从哪里出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.62,0:11:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面？ 下面？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.17,0:11:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请 请一开始就全都放在冰箱里！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.14,0:11:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.94,0:11:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先出石头 接下来是布
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.32,0:11:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使出力量 石头剪刀布
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.36,0:12:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好困啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.72,0:12:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美～绪～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.61,0:12:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 满脸笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.79,0:12:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笔记给我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.68,0:12:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道作业又忘做了么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.26,0:12:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 真是难为情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.99,0:12:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这样的话考试又会吃苦头哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.64,0:12:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.93,0:12:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次 就这一次
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.49,0:12:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一次了 拜托了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.19,0:12:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 之前也这么说来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.12,0:12:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫一言既出驷马难追！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.75,0:12:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 都说了你已经说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.78,0:12:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 是 是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.75,0:12:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.58,0:12:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这一次了哦 真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.87,0:13:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦 该带的东西就是美绪你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.58,0:13:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 刚才说的东西完成了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.17,0:13:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这样 抄完了马上还给你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.40,0:13:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的么 给我看看给我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.53,0:13:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 感觉我好像忘了什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.99,0:13:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上 做完作业之后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.43,0:13:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做完作业之后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.19,0:13:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.71,0:13:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像画了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.29,0:13:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.19,0:13:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像画了什么画
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.82,0:13:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘了擦了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.65,0:13:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs39}那样不行哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.83,0:13:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才忘了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.10,0:13:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.71,0:13:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.88,0:13:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.14,0:13:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.38,0:13:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来我也忘了写作业了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.21,0:13:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 真是头疼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.05,0:13:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 笔记先还给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.39,0:13:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.68,0:14:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.72,0:14:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了 你看了也没什么用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.51,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.10,0:14:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不要这样嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.10,0:14:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说了下一次我会自己做的么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.58,0:14:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.32,0:14:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 让你等了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.41,0:14:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.20,0:14:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了啊 这下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.53,0:14:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种画要是被看见了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.01,0:14:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定会被投来奇怪的眼光
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.41,0:14:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且会看到那幅画的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.06,0:14:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偏偏是小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.83,0:14:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的传播速度可是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.59,0:14:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音速！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.64,0:14:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.01,0:14:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本 是语文的笔记哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.81,0:14:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数学的是这本
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.14,0:14:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这本 上面写着数学哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.08,0:14:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不 不是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.86,0:14:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.32,0:14:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子好疼啊！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.54,0:15:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.72,0:15:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很快就会抄完的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.50,0:15:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.75,0:15:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.27,0:15:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是被看到了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.58,0:15:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.09,0:15:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的高中生活就
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.59,0:15:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.72,0:15:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑 那本笔记！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.64,0:15:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我花一千日元买下来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.15,0:15:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么跑掉了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.15,0:15:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.86,0:15:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.90,0:15:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本笔记…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.28,0:15:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本笔记…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.63,0:15:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会爆炸的！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.91,0:15:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.11,0:15:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本跑不过小佑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.17,0:15:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生要 完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.04,0:15:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 我的人生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.01,0:16:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来我很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.18,0:16:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然也有点不快的事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.75,0:16:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总的来说 是很幸福的人生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.68,0:16:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.58,0:16:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生要完了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.23,0:16:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和男人们的盛宴一起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.07,0:16:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.15,0:16:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.93,0:16:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.67,0:16:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.95,0:16:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,样子啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.54,0:16:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.61,0:16:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃起来！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.45,0:16:52.91,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs45\pos(588,473)\c&H4C4C57&}椰\N\N果
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.45,0:16:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}西班牙语：Nata De Coco
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.99,0:17:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这样 还是够不到
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.32,0:17:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.35,0:17:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走廊里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.43,0:17:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要跑！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.63,0:17:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说… 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.24,0:17:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.87,0:18:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 从后面把笔记传上来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.12,0:18:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后忘了写作业的家伙赶紧报上名来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.82,0:18:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然一时不知道该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.46,0:18:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但好在平安无事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.15,0:18:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来我平稳的日常就能够回来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.72,0:18:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有擦掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.59,0:18:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 长野原
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.46,0:18:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\bord0\shad0\c&H444548&\frx4\fry348\frz18.496\pos(857,445)}目标\h\h\h\N与青春一起\N挥洒汗水\h
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.57,0:18:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.09,0:18:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作业
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.79,0:18:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘做了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.68,0:18:32.68,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx95\pos(1095,150)}雪\N飘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.68,0:18:32.68,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnArial\fs27\pos(1173,150)}flsnow
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.59,0:18:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.18,0:18:35.39,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&\pos(60,360)}收\N拾
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.55,0:18:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 稍微帮我收拾一下房间里的垃圾可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.70,0:18:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对博士来说可能还有点太早了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.45,0:18:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.67,0:19:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.92,0:19:09.17,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\shad1\4c&HF7F4F2&\pos(500,360)}学\N生\N指\N导
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.92,0:19:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}那个时候 我跟那个家伙说了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.90,0:19:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs36}说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.76,0:19:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.97,0:19:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安中同学 有时间么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.89,0:19:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.80,0:19:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(560,417)\c&H49514D&}走\N廊\N里\N请\N勿\N焦\N躁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.46,0:19:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.14,0:19:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.35,0:19:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想 那个发带 是不是有点太大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.70,0:19:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小兔兔 什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.75,0:19:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小甜面包也很好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.31,0:19:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.83,0:19:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs36\bord0\shad0\c&H343232&\pos(722,367)}促\N销\N中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.83,0:19:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21\bord0\shad0\c&H343232&)\pos(439,559)}令人怀念的小甜面包
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.83,0:19:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21\bord0\shad0\c&H343232&)\pos(490,589)}每包三个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs39\bord2\shad0\c&H4C4AB5&\pos(161,538)\frz9.669}每\N包\N55\N个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H3D3941&\pos(456,330)}超大的份量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\bord0\shad0\c&H3D3941&\frz11.175\pos(567,561)}店长推荐{\fs36\b1}超人气
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs33\bord0\shad0\c&H3D3941&\frz322.431\pos(837,522)}超甜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21\bord0\shad0\c&H3D3941&\pos(732,617)}小甜面包家庭装
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.93,0:19:54.68,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx95\pos(1095,150)\frz26.682}雪\N飘
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.93,0:19:54.68,TEXT,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnArial\fs27\frz26.682\pos(1159,112)}flsnow
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.12,0:20:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹原
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.50,0:20:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底有没有身为文化节执行委员的责任感啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.10,0:20:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再稍微认真点考虑能怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.85,0:20:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是非常认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.55,0:20:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为演剧部部长 我可是经常很起作用的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.48,0:20:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情你都不知道么 立花美里哟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.53,0:20:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不知道呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.99,0:20:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好甜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.45,0:20:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我听着！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.61,0:20:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了 这里是要决定文化节上演的节目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.78,0:20:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你的演剧部也没什么关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.79,0:20:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换了一个牌子么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.04,0:20:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要跟这家伙组成一组啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.63,0:20:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道不错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.22,0:20:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那边剑道部的大赛也快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.90,0:21:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 真不该做文化节的执行委员啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.45,0:21:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你这家伙 看什么漫画啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.61,0:21:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不赶紧提出个方案的话 都回不了家了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.37,0:21:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 因为这是新刊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.25,0:21:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连一个想法都没有么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.62,0:21:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我提出来的品葡萄酒大赛不可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.78,0:21:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.59,0:21:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驳回哦 驳回
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.92,0:21:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对驳回
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.69,0:21:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 笹原
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.94,0:21:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊 从刚才就开始 到底在干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.28,0:21:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 以为进入解决阶段了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.14,0:21:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样弄之后…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.42,0:22:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹原你要干嘛？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.30,0:22:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑去上趟厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.47,0:22:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.47,0:22:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天她心情好像相当不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.64,0:22:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是觉得品葡萄酒大赛已经很不错了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.60,0:22:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那个家伙从一开始就完全提不出方案
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.57,0:22:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 说出来的话下次说不定连小命都没了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.41,0:22:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 我提不出方案的话就回不去了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.95,0:22:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要我将思考水平降到和庶民一样么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.25,0:22:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 还是稍微认真点考虑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.95,0:23:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你这种人 才没有想法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.13,0:24:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,900)\pos(652,493)\c&H0A0A0A&\shad0\bord0\K100}只{\K100}言{\K100}片{\K100}语
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.15,0:24:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是亚细亚的纯真啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.77,0:24:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是小甜面包
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.38,0:24:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在关西地区不是很常见
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.18,0:25:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多人不知道该读Amashoku还是Kanshoku呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.68,0:25:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一回是第三回
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.74,0:25:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.19,0:01:47.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}たった今　初めて気づいた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.86,0:01:50.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋に落ちたのだなー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.53,0:01:53.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h キミ☆　キミ☆　キミ☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.07,0:01:54.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意識せざるをえません！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.03,0:01:57.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}なんか　いつもと違う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.53,0:01:56.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.66,0:02:00.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}キミと　ぎこちない会話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.12,0:01:59.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.33,0:02:03.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}まさか　いや　片思い
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.79,0:02:01.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両思い
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:05.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やばい！　視線合っちゃった！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.54,0:02:09.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}なになに！？このドキドキ！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.76,0:02:14.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路　ぐっちゃぐちゃ　混線…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.51,0:02:21.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}こんなこと　初めてだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.18,0:02:26.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}熱でもあるのかなー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.86,0:02:29.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急転直下　いらっしゃた　恋心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.73,0:02:32.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっちゅうま　顔　発火で　まっかっか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.32,0:02:34.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}バ·バ…バカな！？　手が震えるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが　俗に言う　「恋」　なの！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.74,0:02:40.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}やややっちゃった　会話　噛みまくり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.33,0:02:43.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気まずい沈黙　マミムメモ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.00,0:02:45.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}キミの　気持ち　知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.58,0:02:44.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キミの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.67,0:02:48.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.54,0:02:51.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！　{\r}いつもの通学路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.46,0:02:54.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}ピカピカ光る　{\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.84,0:02:57.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}空も飛べそうさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.55,0:03:00.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}カカカタ☆カタオモイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.19,0:01:47.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H54A6FA&\4c&H54A6FA&}就在刚刚 才第一次注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.86,0:01:50.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是陷入恋情了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.53,0:01:53.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H46D6C4&\4c&H46D6C4&}24h 是你☆  是你☆  是你☆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.07,0:01:54.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满脑子想的全部都是你！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.03,0:01:57.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB198E7&\4c&HB198E7&}总觉得 和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.53,0:01:56.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.66,0:02:00.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HAB5D6D&\4c&HAB5D6D&}我与你 慌慌张张的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.12,0:01:59.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.33,0:02:03.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5742BB&\4c&H5742BB&}难道说 不对 单相思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.79,0:02:01.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:05.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了！ 跟他的眼睛对上了！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.54,0:02:09.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}什么什么！？心里小鹿乱撞！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.76,0:02:14.89,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}思考回路 黏黏糊糊乱糟糟 串线…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.51,0:02:21.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}这样的事情 第一次遇到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.18,0:02:26.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H1FD9FB&\4c&H1FD9FB&}是不是患上感冒了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.86,0:02:29.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H274888&\4c&H274888&}急转直下 悄无声息来的 春心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.73,0:02:32.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一会的时间 脸 像着火 通红通红的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.32,0:02:34.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HEAD48A&\4c&HEAD48A&}笨·笨…笨蛋吗！？ 手正在发抖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 俗话说的 “爱” 的啦！？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.74,0:02:40.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H94C061&\4c&H94C061&}要要要要坏菜了啊 对话 咬到舌头了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.33,0:02:43.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难为情的沉默 āōēīū
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.00,0:02:45.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F82E4&\4c&H8F82E4&}想知道 你现在 心里所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.58,0:02:44.04,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.67,0:02:48.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8F5F31&\4c&H8F5F31&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.54,0:02:51.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD299B3&\4c&HD299B3&}初恋！！ {\r}好像上学走的路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.46,0:02:54.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H5275F2&\4c&H5275F2&}亮闪闪的发光 {\r}I DO fall in love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.84,0:02:57.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB0AE4F&\4c&HB0AE4F&}感觉好像能上天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.55,0:03:00.31,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H8992F0&\4c&H8992F0&}单单单恋☆单恋一枝花
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.51,0:23:27.43,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}朝起きて　歯を磨いて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.51,0:23:27.43,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}早晨睡醒后 起床刷牙来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.68,0:23:30.43,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あっという間　午後10時
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.68,0:23:30.43,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}不知不觉间 已到晚十点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.81,0:23:33.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　たくさん　笑ったなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.81,0:23:33.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天也遇到 很多欢乐事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.89,0:23:36.48,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}たくさん　ときめいたなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.89,0:23:36.48,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}也有非常多 刺激与紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.02,0:23:39.94,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}友達と　バカみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.02,0:23:39.94,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}和闺中密友 像笨蛋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.11,0:23:42.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}騒いでる　時にも
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.11,0:23:42.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}大声吵又闹 偶尔会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.19,0:23:46.20,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}チラチラって　目が合う
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.19,0:23:46.20,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}偶尔瞥向你 四目便相接
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.32,0:23:48.91,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}…偶然、だよね。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.32,0:23:48.91,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}这也不过是 偶然事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.12,0:23:52.37,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋なんて言えない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.12,0:23:52.37,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}初恋什么的难以说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.58,0:23:55.54,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キャラじゃないんだもんっ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.58,0:23:55.54,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}因为我不是这样的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.71,0:24:01.54,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ねえ　あしたも会えるよね？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.71,0:24:01.54,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}呐 我们明天 也会相见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.79,0:24:04.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}まぶたを　閉じると
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.79,0:24:04.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}将我的双眼 合上了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.88,0:24:07.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}キラキラ　キミだらけ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.88,0:24:07.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}脑海中只有 亮晶晶的你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.01,0:24:11.14,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今日も　楽しかったね
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.01,0:24:11.14,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}今天的我也 开心又愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.30,0:24:15.56,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あー　恋　してんだなぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.30,0:24:15.56,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}啊 陷入恋爱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.61,0:24:23.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}うれしいな　うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.61,0:24:23.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}真的好开心 真的好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.73,0:24:26.53,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}はじめまして　こいごころ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.73,0:24:26.53,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}第一次见面 我的爱慕心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.86,0:24:29.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}あした　まだ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.86,0:24:29.74,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}到明天的话 我们又见面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.99,0:24:32.41,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.99,0:24:32.41,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}现在晚安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.12,0:24:37.16,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}ゆめで　すぐ　あえるね
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.12,0:24:37.16,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,200)\blur3}在梦中很快 我们会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.79,0:24:43.34,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}おやすみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.79,0:24:43.34,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,500)\blur3}现在晚安吧

